<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-04-05T06:04:13+00:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Wrestling With Johners</title><subtitle>Pro Wrestling podcast with news, reviews and debate from WWE, NXT, NXT:UK, AEW, NJPW, Indy Wrestling and so much more. Listen to Wrestling With Johners on Apple Podcasts, Google Podcasts, Spotify, Podbean, Podcast Addict, Castbox, YouTube or wherever you get your podcasts.</subtitle><author><name>John Scott</name></author><entry><title type="html">Ep118 - WRESTLEMANIA 36 Predictions (with Lexi Helms - Grappucino Thoughts)</title><link href="/podcasts/EP118/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep118 - WRESTLEMANIA 36 Predictions (with Lexi Helms - Grappucino Thoughts)" /><published>2020-04-04T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-04-04T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP118</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP118/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">WrestleMania Edition - 2 Min BRAINBUSTER Quiz (Bonus Ep w/ Mags @BadlandsPod)</title><link href="/podcasts/EP117/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="WrestleMania Edition - 2 Min BRAINBUSTER Quiz (Bonus Ep w/ Mags @BadlandsPod)" /><published>2020-04-03T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-04-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP117</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP117/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep116 - WWF WrestleMania IX Retro Review (with Mike ‘Maddog’ Angus TNT Ring Announcer)</title><link href="/podcasts/EP116/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep116 - WWF WrestleMania IX Retro Review (with Mike ‘Maddog’ Angus TNT Ring Announcer)" /><published>2020-04-02T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-04-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP116</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP116/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Wrestling In Isolation</title><link href="/articles/Wrestling-In-Isolation/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Wrestling In Isolation" /><published>2020-03-29T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-03-29T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/Wrestling%20In%20Isolation</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/Wrestling-In-Isolation/">&lt;p&gt;I posted this on my own Facebook the other day but I thought it would be worth sharing the sentiment into the WWJ Universe along with some other random thoughts and observations on wrestling during the current global crisis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“During this whole crisis everyone is going to be massively impacted whether it’s their health, their families or their bank balances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are a load of local businesses out there who will likely not fall under the umbrella of government support, similarly there will be local groups, artists, musicians etc who can no longer earn an income simply by doing what they do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, as you know since you can see my page I’m a big wrestling fan and in particular I have a passion for local independent wrestling. These companies run show to show and with having to cancel shows the income goes away. So, if you can please still support them. I understand everyone will be hit in the wallet, but if you can spare a little it’ll go a long way to securing the future once this all blows over.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It doesn’t have to be wrestling, it could be a local band or an artist or photographer but if you can help please do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-03-29/tom-hinckley.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;tom&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know a lot of people in British Wrestling and can’t say 1 person needs help more than the next but thinking purely locally and with the relationship we’ve built over the last few years, and the fact that Thomas Basnett is a genuinely good guy, running a quality promotion and is really passionate about it - which encourages and motivates - so if you can please support Wrestling In Hinckley&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can give a donation or they are also selling figures and luchador masks - even if you buy something and then sell it on eBay once life returns to normal - trust me kids always want action figures and luchador masks! Check out the website below for more detail&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://wrestlinginhinckley.bigcartel.com/&quot;&gt;https://wrestlinginhinckley.bigcartel.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or if you want to generalise a bit check out Turnbuckle TV so for £3.99 a month you can check out tonnes and tonnes of content all of which supports wrestling in general.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-03-29/ttv.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;ttv&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are a lot of wrestling companies around who will be desperate for your support, or maybe you can buy some merch from your favourite stars. At this point every little helps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now for some random thoughts on wrestling in the current climate…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My passion for wrestling has been somewhat rekindled in recent weeks, I’m not sure why if I am honest, maybe it’s the influence of some people around me, maybe its having Mania on the horizon I really don’t know. I thoroughly enjoyed Raw this week though the old matched shown were both memorable, story line development was good and the live matches were decent – in particular Ricochet &amp;amp; Alexander Vs Andrade &amp;amp; Garza (I LOVE what they are doing with Garza btw but that’s for another article all together)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have to say I am strangely looking forward to Wrestlemania this year, I admit it is going to be very strange probably pre-recorded and without an audience, and potentially taking place at multiple locations but the line up is pretty strong across the board. In truth there isn’t really a single match that I am disinterested in at this point – some I am obviously looking forward to more than others and I am firmly on the fence about Styles/Taker as I really don’t know how well The Deadman can perform now and adding the latest stipulation I feel is just to cover that fact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not overly concerned by The Fiend vs Cena or Roman vs Goldberg, certainly not as much as I would have been had the opponents been switched. I think Cena has proven he is keen to put people over as he slowly slips away from being an active competitor, and whilst neither The Fiend nor Bray Wyatt need putting over I think with the Firefly Funhouse returning this week there could be some fun build towards  the match and a victory would be a big scalp to help the Fiend to get back on track and back to his amazing, creepy ways going forward from Mania.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although since they are still using the pirate theme, I maintain that they have severely missed a trick by not making use of #Wrestlemaniarrrrrrrr&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-03-29/randy.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;randy&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How freaking AWESOME has Randy Orton been since the Royal Rumble?? I am not his biggest fan in general but every segment regarding him and Edge has been gold. Even in the weeks after the attack on Edge where Orton barely said anything, he was amazing and the silence was explosive and really built the crowd reaction. I am really looking forward to their match at Mania – Edge has always been one of my favourite Superstars and in effectively an empty arena match the Last Man Standing stipulation could see them have some fun with the surroundings – plus with them both referencing Mick Foley it’ll be interesting to see what influence his style has on the match – could we see a return of the burning table?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The highlight so far of that feud though, has to be the promo Edge did when he returned to Raw last week – with an empty arena and therefore no crowd to interact with, no cheap pops, nothing… he delivered an intense monologue culminating in setting the challenge for a Last Man Standing match. The delivery was pretty much perfect from tone, pacing, body language etc it should be used as a tutorial for upcoming wrestlers who need to learn how to tell or sell a story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of great promos, I think Cody Rhodes has probably cemented himself as THE best on the mic lately and – in spite of that tattoo – he is rapidly rising up my list of favourite wrestlers. I feel like he understands the theatre of the industry – the promo to open Dynamite on March 18, the first show with no live audience was captivating. Cody was able to eloquently address to situation in the world and the impact on the shows as well as recapping what has been happening with The Elite and building to Blood &amp;amp; Guts, he was really captivating and engaging and yet again proving his quality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-03-29/support.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;support&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s it for me, for now…. Stay safe, stay indoors, watch loads of wrestling and keep listening to Wrestling with Johners! And don’t forget you can follow me on Twitter at @mattbasedwres01&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>matt-bayliss</name></author><summary type="html">I posted this on my own Facebook the other day but I thought it would be worth sharing the sentiment into the WWJ Universe along with some other random thoughts and observations on wrestling during the current global crisis.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep115 - WWF WrestleMania VIII Retro PPV Review (with Chris &amp;amp; Nick BBGWPod)</title><link href="/podcasts/EP115/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep115 - WWF WrestleMania VIII Retro PPV Review (with Chris &amp; Nick BBGWPod)" /><published>2020-03-28T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-03-28T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP115</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP115/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep114 - 2 Min BRAINBUSTER Quiz (Bonus Ep w/ B.J Mining4Mayhem Pod)</title><link href="/podcasts/EP114/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep114 - 2 Min BRAINBUSTER Quiz (Bonus Ep w/ B.J Mining4Mayhem Pod)" /><published>2020-03-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-03-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP114</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP114/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep113 - Interview with FRANKIE T (In Partnership With IW</title><link href="/interviews/podcasts/EP113/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep113 - Interview with FRANKIE T (In Partnership With IW" /><published>2020-03-24T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-03-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/interviews/podcasts/EP113</id><content type="html" xml:base="/interviews/podcasts/EP113/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">WrestleMania 36 Update | 2 Days at WWE PC &amp;amp; Other Locations | Indy Promotions &amp;amp; WrestleCon</title><link href="/WrestleMania-36-Update-2-Days-at-WWE-PC-Other-Locations-Indy-Promotions-WrestleCon/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="WrestleMania 36 Update | 2 Days at WWE PC &amp; Other Locations | Indy Promotions &amp; WrestleCon" /><published>2020-03-22T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-03-22T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/WrestleMania%2036%20Update%20%202%20Days%20at%20WWE%20PC%20%20Other%20Locations%20%20Indy%20Promotions%20%20WrestleCon</id><content type="html" xml:base="/WrestleMania-36-Update-2-Days-at-WWE-PC-Other-Locations-Indy-Promotions-WrestleCon/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep112 – MATT HARDY in AEW | The Exalted One Unveiled | Two Day Mania Update | NXT Recap (with B.J – Mining 4 Mayhem Podcast)</title><link href="/podcasts/EP112/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep112 – MATT HARDY in AEW | The Exalted One Unveiled | Two Day Mania Update | NXT Recap (with B.J – Mining 4 Mayhem Podcast)" /><published>2020-03-21T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-03-21T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP112</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP112/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep111 – Will Mania Be Cancelled? | NXT &amp;amp; AEW Dynamite Recap | Your Questions (with Lexi Helms – Grappuchino Thoughts)</title><link href="/podcasts/EP111/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep111 – Will Mania Be Cancelled? | NXT &amp; AEW Dynamite Recap | Your Questions (with Lexi Helms – Grappuchino Thoughts)" /><published>2020-03-14T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-03-14T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP111</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP111/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>