<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-03-29T13:14:46+00:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Wrestling With Johners</title><subtitle>Pro Wrestling podcast with news, reviews and debate from WWE, NXT, NXT:UK, AEW, NJPW, Indy Wrestling and so much more. Listen to Wrestling With Johners on Apple Podcasts, Google Podcasts, Spotify, Podbean, Podcast Addict, Castbox, YouTube or wherever you get your podcasts.</subtitle><author><name>John Scott</name></author><entry><title type="html">Wrestling In Isolation</title><link href="/articles/Wrestling-In-Isolation/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Wrestling In Isolation" /><published>2020-03-29T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-03-29T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/Wrestling%20In%20Isolation</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/Wrestling-In-Isolation/">&lt;p&gt;I posted this on my own Facebook the other day but I thought it would be worth sharing the sentiment into the WWJ Universe along with some other random thoughts and observations on wrestling during the current global crisis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“During this whole crisis everyone is going to be massively impacted whether it’s their health, their families or their bank balances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are a load of local businesses out there who will likely not fall under the umbrella of government support, similarly there will be local groups, artists, musicians etc who can no longer earn an income simply by doing what they do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, as you know since you can see my page I’m a big wrestling fan and in particular I have a passion for local independent wrestling. These companies run show to show and with having to cancel shows the income goes away. So, if you can please still support them. I understand everyone will be hit in the wallet, but if you can spare a little it’ll go a long way to securing the future once this all blows over.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It doesn’t have to be wrestling, it could be a local band or an artist or photographer but if you can help please do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-03-29/tom-hinckley.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;tom&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know a lot of people in British Wrestling and can’t say 1 person needs help more than the next but thinking purely locally and with the relationship we’ve built over the last few years, and the fact that Thomas Basnett is a genuinely good guy, running a quality promotion and is really passionate about it - which encourages and motivates - so if you can please support Wrestling In Hinckley&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can give a donation or they are also selling figures and luchador masks - even if you buy something and then sell it on eBay once life returns to normal - trust me kids always want action figures and luchador masks! Check out the website below for more detail&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(https://wrestlinginhinckley.bigcartel.com/)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or if you want to generalise a bit check out Turnbuckle TV so for £3.99 a month you can check out tonnes and tonnes of content all of which supports wrestling in general.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-03-29/ttv.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;ttv&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are a lot of wrestling companies around who will be desperate for your support, or maybe you can buy some merch from your favourite stars. At this point every little helps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now for some random thoughts on wrestling in the current climate…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My passion for wrestling has been somewhat rekindled in recent weeks, I’m not sure why if I am honest, maybe it’s the influence of some people around me, maybe its having Mania on the horizon I really don’t know. I thoroughly enjoyed Raw this week though the old matched shown were both memorable, story line development was good and the live matches were decent – in particular Ricochet &amp;amp; Alexander Vs Andrade &amp;amp; Garza (I LOVE what they are doing with Garza btw but that’s for another article all together)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have to say I am strangely looking forward to Wrestlemania this year, I admit it is going to be very strange probably pre-recorded and without an audience, and potentially taking place at multiple locations but the line up is pretty strong across the board. In truth there isn’t really a single match that I am disinterested in at this point – some I am obviously looking forward to more than others and I am firmly on the fence about Styles/Taker as I really don’t know how well The Deadman can perform now and adding the latest stipulation I feel is just to cover that fact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not overly concerned by The Fiend vs Cena or Roman vs Goldberg, certainly not as much as I would have been had the opponents been switched. I think Cena has proven he is keen to put people over as he slowly slips away from being an active competitor, and whilst neither The Fiend nor Bray Wyatt need putting over I think with the Firefly Funhouse returning this week there could be some fun build towards  the match and a victory would be a big scalp to help the Fiend to get back on track and back to his amazing, creepy ways going forward from Mania.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although since they are still using the pirate theme, I maintain that they have severely missed a trick by not making use of #Wrestlemaniarrrrrrrr&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-03-29/randy.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;randy&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How freaking AWESOME has Randy Orton been since the Royal Rumble?? I am not his biggest fan in general but every segment regarding him and Edge has been gold. Even in the weeks after the attack on Edge where Orton barely said anything, he was amazing and the silence was explosive and really built the crowd reaction. I am really looking forward to their match at Mania – Edge has always been one of my favourite Superstars and in effectively an empty arena match the Last Man Standing stipulation could see them have some fun with the surroundings – plus with them both referencing Mick Foley it’ll be interesting to see what influence his style has on the match – could we see a return of the burning table?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The highlight so far of that feud though, has to be the promo Edge did when he returned to Raw last week – with an empty arena and therefore no crowd to interact with, no cheap pops, nothing… he delivered an intense monologue culminating in setting the challenge for a Last Man Standing match. The delivery was pretty much perfect from tone, pacing, body language etc it should be used as a tutorial for upcoming wrestlers who need to learn how to tell or sell a story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of great promos, I think Cody Rhodes has probably cemented himself as THE best on the mic lately and – in spite of that tattoo – he is rapidly rising up my list of favourite wrestlers. I feel like he understands the theatre of the industry – the promo to open Dynamite on March 18, the first show with no live audience was captivating. Cody was able to eloquently address to situation in the world and the impact on the shows as well as recapping what has been happening with The Elite and building to Blood &amp;amp; Guts, he was really captivating and engaging and yet again proving his quality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-03-29/support.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;support&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s it for me, for now…. Stay safe, stay indoors, watch loads of wrestling and keep listening to Wrestling with Johners! And don’t forget you can follow me on Twitter at @mattbasedwres01&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>matt-bayliss</name></author><summary type="html">I posted this on my own Facebook the other day but I thought it would be worth sharing the sentiment into the WWJ Universe along with some other random thoughts and observations on wrestling during the current global crisis.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep115 - WWF WrestleMania VIII Retro PPV Review (with Chris &amp;amp; Nick BBGWPod)</title><link href="/podcasts/EP115/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep115 - WWF WrestleMania VIII Retro PPV Review (with Chris &amp; Nick BBGWPod)" /><published>2020-03-28T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-03-28T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP115</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP115/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep114 - 2 Min BRAINBUSTER Quiz (Bonus Ep w/ B.J Mining4Mayhem Pod)</title><link href="/podcasts/EP114/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep114 - 2 Min BRAINBUSTER Quiz (Bonus Ep w/ B.J Mining4Mayhem Pod)" /><published>2020-03-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-03-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP114</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP114/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep113 - Interview with FRANKIE T (In Partnership With IW</title><link href="/interviews/podcasts/EP113/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep113 - Interview with FRANKIE T (In Partnership With IW" /><published>2020-03-24T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-03-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/interviews/podcasts/EP113</id><content type="html" xml:base="/interviews/podcasts/EP113/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">WrestleMania 36 Update | 2 Days at WWE PC &amp;amp; Other Locations | Indy Promotions &amp;amp; WrestleCon</title><link href="/WrestleMania-36-Update-2-Days-at-WWE-PC-Other-Locations-Indy-Promotions-WrestleCon/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="WrestleMania 36 Update | 2 Days at WWE PC &amp; Other Locations | Indy Promotions &amp; WrestleCon" /><published>2020-03-22T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-03-22T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/WrestleMania%2036%20Update%20%202%20Days%20at%20WWE%20PC%20%20Other%20Locations%20%20Indy%20Promotions%20%20WrestleCon</id><content type="html" xml:base="/WrestleMania-36-Update-2-Days-at-WWE-PC-Other-Locations-Indy-Promotions-WrestleCon/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep112 – MATT HARDY in AEW | The Exalted One Unveiled | Two Day Mania Update | NXT Recap (with B.J – Mining 4 Mayhem Podcast)</title><link href="/podcasts/EP112/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep112 – MATT HARDY in AEW | The Exalted One Unveiled | Two Day Mania Update | NXT Recap (with B.J – Mining 4 Mayhem Podcast)" /><published>2020-03-21T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-03-21T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP112</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP112/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep111 – Will Mania Be Cancelled? | NXT &amp;amp; AEW Dynamite Recap | Your Questions (with Lexi Helms – Grappuchino Thoughts)</title><link href="/podcasts/EP111/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep111 – Will Mania Be Cancelled? | NXT &amp; AEW Dynamite Recap | Your Questions (with Lexi Helms – Grappuchino Thoughts)" /><published>2020-03-14T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-03-14T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP111</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP111/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep110 - WWE Elimination Chamber 2020 Full Review (with Brian H. Waters)</title><link href="/podcasts/EP110/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep110 - WWE Elimination Chamber 2020 Full Review (with Brian H. Waters)" /><published>2020-03-09T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-03-09T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP110</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP110/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Interview with WILL AUSTIN (Coastal Championship Wrestling)</title><link href="/interviews/podcasts/EP109/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Interview with WILL AUSTIN (Coastal Championship Wrestling)" /><published>2020-03-06T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-03-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/interviews/podcasts/EP109</id><content type="html" xml:base="/interviews/podcasts/EP109/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">This time with an extra-large shot of sarcasm and venom syrup!</title><link href="/articles/Super-Grappuchino-Thoughts/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="This time with an extra-large shot of sarcasm and venom syrup!" /><published>2020-03-04T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-03-04T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/Super%20Grappuchino%20Thoughts</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/Super-Grappuchino-Thoughts/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;because-adding-super-in-front-of-something-makes-it-more-excitable&quot;&gt;Because adding super in front of something makes it more… excitable?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-03-04/goldberg1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;goldberg&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seriously though…. Oh boy… Where do I start with this one? The original article I had planned, has been promptly pushed out of the way to allow for what you’re about to read. Normally when I write these articles, I strive to be as balanced and as open minded as possible, usually admitting my biases early on to allow you, the reader, to discuss your opinions etc. This time…  I can’t guarantee that it will be. I guess adding that last sentence is my attempt to keep some of that balance in tow and to make you aware that this may not be as well researched as other articles I write. There may be more venom in this article than others. For this I make no apologies. You’ve been warned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-03-04/pulling-hair.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;pulling-hair&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Irrespective of your feelings towards the Saudi PPVs, I watched Super Showdown whilst I still can, before the rumoured changes to the WWE Network kick in. That and because, for once, I could watch a PPV at a convenient time and not have to stay up ridiculously late to do so (I’ll discuss this more at a later date); and because it’s Wrestlemania season and feel that I should attempt to at least bring myself up to speed with the events on main roster. Whilst we had some good moments - from Bailey vs. Naomi; the potential Undertaker vs. AJ Styles match at Wrestlemania; to the OC vs The Viking Raiders (granted, this was on the preshow); these were moments that made Super Showdown tolerable. As per the norm with WWE, Super Showdown felt like an extended episode of Raw, with added sprinkles of SmackDown! Albeit, with a depleted roster – whatever their reason for not competing. These are all overshadowed by the way the show ended.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-03-04/showdown.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;showdown&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before we get to that, there are a few points that I want to raise. We need to discuss the Ricochet/ Lesnar match. Being honest, I don’t remember much from the match itself. I remember Mike Rome (the announcer) potentially mixing Brock and Ricochets’ names – I’m sure he said “Brickochet”; Ricochet bumping like a madman; and the result. That’s it… Ricochet is one of the most talented and beloved wrestlers to ever lace a pair of boots (in my humble opinion) and deserves to be treated with a little more respect. Whilst I am excited to see the predicted Lesnar vs. McIntyre at Wrestlemania, the match between Ricochet and Lesnar could have been booked better. If we look at Tyler Bate vs. Walter from NXTUK Takeover: Cardiff, this is a master class in having a David vs. Goliath match, which put people on the edge of their seats and made them, for that moment, no matter how brief, suspend their belief. Whilst I know Lesnar and Ricochet wouldn’t have lasted as long as Tyler Bate vs. Walter, someone with the talent that Ricochet has could have been made to look strong, but ultimately succumbing to the beast that is Brock Lesnar. This wouldn’t have damaged either party, and would have paved the way for Ricochet to look credible if he were to challenge for the title in the future. Alternatively, McIntyre could have got involved somehow (via video package if he didn’t want to appear in Saudi) to help plant the seeds for Wrestlemania.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, we need to discuss the fact that The Undertaker hardly acknowledged the Tuwaiq Trophy after winning it. Without doubt, The Undertaker is one of the greatest of all time. He’s had a career that spans close to 30 years. He’s done everything that can be done in the company. And, it is easy to argue that making a big deal out of the trophy would be out of character for The Undertaker, but doesn’t lack of acknowledgement undermine the trophy itself? Especially as this potentially could have been used as a prop to further the potential feud between AJ and The Undertaker. I appreciate that the creation of this trophy is merely to please the Saudi audience, just like the Greatest Royal Rumble Title, the Tag Team Turmoil World Cup and the WWE World Cup (as a footie fan, both are weird to me). Unless future Saudi PPVs are going to be comprised of matches in which these are defended – which would be amazing as it wouldn’t interfere with the main roster - what is the point in creating something that will never be defended? History tells us that some titles were created to keep individuals happy, such as the European Title being created for the British Bulldog, but even this was defended.  I’m sure others will agree that this is the perfect metaphor for the show itself – something nice and shiny, but it’s something no one particularly wants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-03-04/undertaker.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;undertaker&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, this is not why you’ve read so far into this. So, strap yourself in. We’re about to address the elephant in the room. Goldberg is the new universal champion. Goldberg defeated The Fiend in less than 3 minutes. This now means that Goldberg is the only man in WWE history to hold a world title in 4 decades (1998, 2003, 2017 and 2020). The Fiend was taken out by 4 spears and one (and I’m choosing my words carefully) disappointing jackhammer. Let’s sit with these two bits of information for a few seconds. Anger gone? No? I’m still going to proceed…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-03-04/triggered.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;triggered&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, to be somewhat composed it’s important to say, I have no issue with Goldberg. By all accounts and from the TV footage I’ve seen, he’s a genuinely nice man and does a lot for charity. I would be a liar if I didn’t admit that the child in me is overjoyed – I loved Goldberg in WCW. I have so many happy memories watching WCW with family members and bonding over our love for him. We celebrated when he beat Hogan in 1998 to win his first world title. I was so upset when he lost it… I was so happy when he finally showed up in WWE in 2003 and went on to win the World Heavyweight Championship (I was also really, really, unhappy that he was taken out by someone who’s going into the Hall of Fame this year…). I was overjoyed when he went into the hall of fame, and even when he returned. Whilst it may have not been the greatest (due to an accident on his part), past storylines have proven that Goldberg can return to wrestling without being in the title picture. At least he would still prove to his son that he can achieve anything and present his son with the opportunity to see him perform (if that is indeed the true motive of Goldbergs’ return). It’s also important to note that Goldbergs’ age is not a factor in my upset. Goldberg turned 53 in December.  Chris Jericho turned 49 in November and is the current AEW Champion. I adore Le Champion. It is the fact that we have yet another part time, and in my opinion, undeserving champion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Similarly, I also have no issue with The Fiend losing the title, it must happen at some time or another. That’s the nature of professional wrestling. You win titles and lose them. As wrestling fans, we’ve come to accept this. For me, what is so jarring about this loss, is WHO beat him. If this was a decade ago, it could have been believable – especially as Wyatt was relatively new to the industry, and it would have been a nice way to see Goldberg go out on top. Yet, with the amount of talent at WWEs’ disposal and they choose to have their most compelling Main Roster character lose to a part time superstar? Surely it would have made more sense to have The Fiend lose the title to the next big thing on SmackDown? Especially as The Fiend has previously been booked as unstoppable (from what I’ve seen anyway). The question is, where does The Fiend go from this loss? Especially if the rumours are true and he will face John Cena (again) at Wrestlemania, rather than challenge for the title he’s lost? The Fiend deserves a Wrestlemania moment that makes up for the god-awful match he had against Orton a few years ago. To be fair, I’d like to see The Fiend take on Alistair Black (granted he’s on Raw like) or Bobby Roode (He’ll NEVER be Robert to me) or even Shinsuke Nakamura. Hell, I’d even take Bo Dallas. All of these are people I’ve never seen Bray Wyatt / The Fiend go against before (although you guys will let me know if I’m wrong). These are matches worthy of being on the Wrestlemania Card and could help establish new ‘top stars’ to help establish SmackDown Live! as must see tv. Not to mention helping the blue brand truly be the ‘land of opportunity’.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whilst we’re talking about Wrestlemania, if the rumours are true, I frankly don’t want to see Goldberg vs. Reigns for the title. Essentially, it comes down to spear vs spear. If this is the case, lets add Edge into it. Hell, lets add Batista into it too. Battle of the spears – winner takes all. Because if this is the road WWE are going down, why not go all in? 3 Hall of Famers against the Big Dog. Trying to get back to some level of seriousness, Reigns being out of the title picture has been wonderful – and frankly, he doesn’t need to be at this moment in time. If creative really wanted to give Reigns another Wrestlemania Moment, surely having him represent SmackDown Live in a 3-way Raw vs. SmackDown vs. NXT match would be better? That way, he could claim that he should be the number one contender as he proved SmackDown is the best brand. Or he could claim that SmackDown really is his yard and offer some sort of groundwork for the inevitable post mania shake up? For example, should the Velveteen Dream be called up (please, no, give him the NXT Title first lads) Reigns could easily play the cocky heel and say something along the lines of “I beat &lt;em&gt;insert name here&lt;/em&gt; and sent them back to NXT. You won’t be any different, son”. And if Goldberg has nothing to do over Wrestlemania weekend, I can think of a Bro who has been very vocal about him on social media. Simply put, I want to see Matt Riddle vs. Goldberg. This match would be money – especially as its clear they don’t like each other. This fact alone means no title needs to be near it. Imagine what could happen during this match and how many headlines this could generate. Granted, this takes a lot of professional restraint on behalf of both parties, but surely, I cannot be the only one that is desperate for this match to happen?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the biggest issues I have with Goldberg winning is the implications for RAW and SmackDown Live. These are considered the two “Top Shows” in WWE and are now led by champions who are part time. It can be argued that this makes these shows must watch to see if the champion shows up. I disagree. I feel that if the company cannot be bothered to have a full-time champion, why should I bother investing my time caring for who has it? Or who the next challenger is? Earlier, I wrote that part time champions don’t deserve it. Why? Because if you’re a champion, you are the best at what you do. You represent a promotion and its values. As champion, you should be proud to hold the title bestowed onto you. You take that title everywhere with you (see Pete Dunne and the NXTUK Title). How can you do this if you’re part time? It is no secret that TV viewership is down, as are ticket sales and PPV buy rates. Could all the above be a factor? I asked this in my last piece, but what impact does a part-time champion have on staff morale?  What message does this send to the full-time members of the roster? What message does it send to the fans, both casual and die-hard, about the top titles in the company? Surely, I can’t be the only one who asks these questions?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another issue is that Goldberg has experienced bad booking decisions and their impact. If you cast your mind back to how his WCW streak ended, there were fans who were just as upset as they are today. If memory serves me correctly, in the Monday Night Wars series on the Network, Goldberg is clearly unhappy at the decision to end his streak in WCW when it did. Similarly, he was also booked appallingly in 2003 by WWE and by the time 2004 came, fans were happy to see him go, especially as it felt like he was only there for his paycheck. Surely, he must have known that it wasn’t the right time for The Fiends’ title reign to come to an end, in such a lack lustre way and at a glorified house show. The only circumstances I can see the need for this to be done was if Bray was injured in some way. It comes to something when Scott Hall is posting on Twitter that he should ‘Dust off this taser’.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This may seem like I’m jumping on the bandwagon and joining other members of the IWC who are up in arms over this. This could be the last time we see Goldberg as an active competitor with the title. But fans have every right to be. It’s no secret that wrestling fans are some of the most avid, passionate and opinionated around. Can you really blame us? Even if we choose to miss NXT or SmackDown Live, we devote 5 hours of our lives each week to watching WWE programming. If we go to the extreme and take in RAW, SmackDown Live, NXT and NXTUK that’s 8 hours of WWE Programming a week. Not to mention the amount of content available on the Network and via alternative outlets such as podcasts – off the top of my head, I can mention 5. Then, there is the amount of merchandise available to fans. I am slightly ashamed to admit this, but I have close to £80 worth of gingerbread ornaments for my Christmas tree. Whilst that amount wasn’t spent all at once, sitting here and doing a quick estimate has made my stomach drop slightly. Not to mention the amount I’ve spent on the Network since 2015 (although, I do not regret having it whilst I was in hospital as it kept me entertained and took my mind off of being ill and in hospital). Despite the amount of time and money the fans part with, the WWE seemingly chooses to ignore them. It is easy to list examples here, and I’m sure you can think of your own. This is the company that once bragged about being “worldwide leader of sports and entertainment”. The company that gave us the Attitude and Ruthless Aggression eras. That made names like Hulk Hogan, The Rock and John Cena into household names – transitioning from Wrestling into pop culture in some way, shape or form. So, the question is, what happened? Whilst its easy to point the finger of blame at the obvious individuals, but please consider the following - the most obvious person for this is allegedly the same person that suggested Rhea Ripley vs Charlotte Flair for Wrestlemania… if you believe the dirt sheets that is. Whilst we now live in an era where there are so many alternatives available to us, and their content is accessible 24/7, for some fans, you never really forget or get over your first love.  It is simply not an option to “go elsewhere”, especially as NXT has proven it can get things so right. Case and point – I’ll probably stay up for NXT Takeover: Tampa rather than Wrestlemania 36. If I don’t, social media will actively be avoided until I watch it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-03-04/goldberg.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;sgoldberg&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In times like these it is easy to play fantasy booker. It is easy to have 20/20 vision and be able to use the fan reaction we see to influence the matches and outcomes suggested. It’s easy to plan things out without the influences of the likes of performer egos, contracts, politics and the omniscient Vinnie Mac. In all honesty, I didn’t expect Super Showdown to be amongst the calibre of a Wrestlemania X-7 or an NXT Takeover or even a Wrestle Kingdom. Super Showdown was merely a ‘filler’ show to fulfil the requirements of the Saudi deal. I guess that what I expected from this show was to have the seeds planted for Wrestlemania in what is a glorified house show. To a degree, I got what I expected, but not what I wanted. It is comforting to know that I am not alone in being upset over how it ended. I don’t know if I will go to the extremes of cancelling the network, because there two reasons for me to keep it. Had I written this article at 9pm last night (27/02/2020), this article would have been an expletive filled, nonsensical rant that may have been difficult to read. I have had to resist the temptation to rant and include expletives in this one too. Writing this and going on the journey of emotions has been cathartic to say the least. Having reviewed what has been written, I questioned what I felt. The answer was simple – its frustration. I’m frustrated that such silly decisions can be made. I’m frustrated for the full-time members of the WWE Rosters. I’m frustrated for those who are about to be called up from NXT. I’m frustrated that WWE think that it is ok to continuously upset the fans. But the biggest frustration we’ve yet to discuss… Where did the Blue Universal Title come from when The Fiend didn’t walk out with it?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>lexi-helms</name></author><summary type="html">Because adding super in front of something makes it more… excitable?</summary></entry></feed>