<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-09-26T21:13:48+00:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Wrestling With Johners</title><subtitle>Pro Wrestling podcast with news, reviews and debate from WWE, NXT, NXT:UK, AEW, NJPW, Indy Wrestling and so much more. Listen to Wrestling With Johners on Apple Podcasts, Google Podcasts, Spotify, Podbean, Podcast Addict, Castbox, YouTube or wherever you get your podcasts.</subtitle><author><name>John Scott</name></author><entry><title type="html">The latest Bobby Fish/Impact Wrestling update!</title><link href="/alliance-pro-wrestling-network/videos/The-latest-Bobby-FishImpact-Wrestling-update/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The latest Bobby Fish/Impact Wrestling update!" /><published>2022-09-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-09-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/alliance-pro-wrestling-network/videos/The%20latest%20Bobby%20FishImpact%20Wrestling%20update</id><content type="html" xml:base="/alliance-pro-wrestling-network/videos/The-latest-Bobby-FishImpact-Wrestling-update/"></content><author><name>lewis-carlan</name></author><category term="alliance-pro-wrestling-network" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ring Around the Jabroni Tournament of Champions round 3</title><link href="/bucklebomb-entertainment/videos/Ring-Around-the-Jabroni-Tournament-of-Champions-round-3/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ring Around the Jabroni Tournament of Champions round 3" /><published>2022-09-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-09-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/bucklebomb-entertainment/videos/Ring%20Around%20the%20Jabroni%20Tournament%20of%20Champions%20round%203</id><content type="html" xml:base="/bucklebomb-entertainment/videos/Ring-Around-the-Jabroni-Tournament-of-Champions-round-3/"></content><author><name>bucklebomb-entertainment</name></author><category term="bucklebomb-entertainment" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Green Phantom &amp;amp; Slik Jack Connection to POLI</title><link href="/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/Green-Phantom-Slik-Jack-Connection-to-POLI/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Green Phantom &amp;amp; Slik Jack Connection to POLI" /><published>2022-09-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-09-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/Green%20Phantom%20%20Slik%20Jack%20Connection%20to%20POLI</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/Green-Phantom-Slik-Jack-Connection-to-POLI/"></content><author><name>jofo-in-the-ring</name></author><category term="jofo-in-the-ring" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Was Chris Jericho Winning ROH Title a good idea?</title><link href="/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/Was-Chris-Jericho-Winning-ROH-Title-a-good-idea/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Was Chris Jericho Winning ROH Title a good idea?" /><published>2022-09-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-09-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/Was%20Chris%20Jericho%20Winning%20ROH%20Title%20a%20good%20idea</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/Was-Chris-Jericho-Winning-ROH-Title-a-good-idea/"></content><author><name>jofo-in-the-ring</name></author><category term="jofo-in-the-ring" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">LLL At Denver Taco Fest 2022</title><link href="/lucha-libre-and-laughs/videos/LLL-At-Denver-Taco-Fest-2022/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="LLL At Denver Taco Fest 2022" /><published>2022-09-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-09-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/lucha-libre-and-laughs/videos/LLL%20At%20Denver%20Taco%20Fest%202022</id><content type="html" xml:base="/lucha-libre-and-laughs/videos/LLL-At-Denver-Taco-Fest-2022/"></content><author><name>lucha-libre-and-laughs</name></author><category term="lucha-libre-and-laughs" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Issue 37 Shows of September 10-16, 2022</title><link href="/articles/Issue-37-Shows-of-September-10-16,-2022/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Issue 37 Shows of September 10-16, 2022" /><published>2022-09-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-09-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/Issue%2037%20Shows%20of%20September%2010-16,%202022</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/Issue-37-Shows-of-September-10-16,-2022/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png&quot; alt=&quot;pro darin&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;wxw-we-love-wrestling-34&quot;&gt;wXw We Love Wrestling 34&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As promised, I’m kicking things off with two belated recaps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 34th episode of wXw We Love Wrestling took place on June 12, 2022 at the Turbinenhalle in Oberhausen, Germany, hours after the previous episode occurred.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-09-26/wxwlovewrestling34.png&quot; alt=&quot;wxw love wrestling 34&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Besides the aftermath of Broken Rules which took place on both episode of We Love Wrestling at the same venue, this episode also had Ahura returning to wXw after being suspended due to his actions at wXw Anniversary XXI. Plus, like CM Punk after getting suspended due to his “pipebomb” back in mid-2011, Ahura returned with one of wXw’s belts which was the wXw Shotgun Championship (that Maggot currently holds). Harras had a contract set up for Ahura, and Ahura looked at it before handing the microphone back to the Director of Sports.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Harras attempted to speak until the mic went out, and while he and ring announcer Thomas Giesen were attempting to fix it, Ahura—behind their backs—switched contracts before he and Harras signed it; Harras then looked at it and realized that he and Ahura signed a contract for a match with a shot at the wXw Unified World Wrestling Championship on the line. I may not have gotten this far yet due to a break I took last month before coming back, but I’m curious to see how the match between Harras and Ahura went.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seven matches took place on this episode of We Love Wrestling. To me, it was a lukewarm episode when it came to watching the matches, but my favorite match of the episode would have to go to the opener between Maggot and Sebastian Suave for the wXw Shotgun Championship. I was pretty sure that something would happen, regardless of whether or not Harras had something up his sleeve, in the opener but I was mistaken. It was a good way to kick off the episode, especially after seeing Maggot doing whatever it takes to retain the title and Suave—regardless of how the fans of Maggot got under his skin—showing what he had in store for the champion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the match results from Oberhausen…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-maggot-defeated-sebastian-suave-to-retain-the-wxw-shotgun-championship&quot;&gt;Match #1: Maggot defeated Sebastian Suave to retain the wXw Shotgun Championship.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After Maggot hit Suave with the Crucifixion for two, he missed with the spear; Suave went for an emerald frosion until Maggot blocked it before Suave sat down on him for two. Then, Maggot came back with a spear for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-michael-knight-defeated-hektor-invictus-with-a-full-throttle-into-a-gts&quot;&gt;Match #2: Michael Knight defeated Hektor Invictus with a Full Throttle into a GTS.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both men shook hands afterwards, then Knight—who was interviewed by Andy Jackson—said that Bobby Gunns kept him focused and that they were still planning on winning the wXw Tag Team Championship. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-3-levaniel--jurn-simmons-defeated-michael-schenkenburg--tristan-archer-w-nikita-charisma&quot;&gt;Match #3: Levaniel &amp;amp; Jurn Simmons defeated Michael Schenkenburg &amp;amp; Tristan Archer (w/ Nikita Charisma).&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before the match started, Levaniel praised Simmons for defeating Vincent Heisenberg at Broken Rules, and that things would go differently with him focused and motivated before introducing the fans to his tag team partner. Early in the match, Levaniel blind tagged in and got Simmons peeved. Near the end, Archer attempted to hit Simmons with the wXw Unified World Wrestling Championship belt until Levaniel stopped him and almost hit Simmons with the belt. Simmons fought Archer out of the ring before Schenkenburg hit him with a Michinoku driver for two. Then, after Charisma pretended to be Triple H at ringside (water spit and all), Schenkenburg went for the Pedigree until Simmons him with a running knee and a piledriver for the win.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the match, Simmons shooed Archer and Rott und Flott to the back, then—in an interview by Andy Jackson—called Archer a “jackass” before vowing to win back the championship, telling him “your ass is mine.” He then turned to Levaniel and said that if he interfered, “your ass is mine too.” &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-4-baby-allison-defeated-iva-kolasky-to-retain-the-wxw-womens-championship&quot;&gt;Match #4: Baby Allison defeated Iva Kolasky to retain the wXw Women’s Championship.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Allison has a new theme song that sounds like a cross between Silverchair and Nine Inch Nails. During the match, Iva went for a leg drop, but missed and got in a leg split before tripping her opponent and having her in the same position; the two then threw strikes at each other while in leg splits afterwards. After Iva grabbed the bottom rope to get out of the cravat, Allison hit her with a spear before putting her back in the cravat and making her submit. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-5-psycho-mike-defeated-jacob-crane-in-almost-five-minutes&quot;&gt;Match #5: Psycho Mike defeated Jacob Crane in almost five minutes.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Crane refused to be bodyslammed in the beginning, darting to two corners before Mike got his hands on him. Then, Mike offered him a €5 bill, and Crane took it before countering a bodyslam with a rollup for two. Mike was then finally able to bodyslam Crane four times until Crane paid off the €5 after he attempted to bodyslam him some more. Mike slammed Crane four more times, then attempted to hit him with a fifth slam until Crane tapped out. Post-match, Mike hit him with another bodyslam behind the referee’s back, then hit him with one more slam and pinned him before being chased to the back. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-6-peacock-main-event-masha-slamovich-defeated-orsi&quot;&gt;Match #6 (Peacock main event): Masha Slamovich defeated Orsi.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Masha won on wXw for the first time ever after hitting Orsi with a package piledriver. After the match, Masha told Andy Jackson that she demanded to be in wXw Femme Fatale. My score: &lt;strong&gt;2.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-amboss-defeated-jonathan-gresham-peter-tihanyi-the-rotation--elijah-blum&quot;&gt;Main event: Amboss defeated Jonathan Gresham, Peter Tihanyi, the Rotation &amp;amp; Elijah Blum.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tihanyi’s back was worked on during the match, ditto the Rotation’s left hand which was taped. (Tihanyi had a sore back after fighting Axel Tischer on the previous episode of We Love Wrestling.) After beating down Gresham, Tihanyi and the Rotation at ringside, Amboss had Blum’s back against the wall; Laurance Roman wore down Blum with a crossface, the Arrows of Hungary hit him with the Crossfire, and Robert Dreissker hit him with the Dreissker Bomb for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;wrestlemania-launch-party&quot;&gt;WrestleMania Launch Party&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yep, I also did a recap of this event mainly because it made it to Peacock days after it occurred.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The WrestleMania Launch Party took place on August 11, 2022 at the SoFi Stadium in Los Angeles, California in the United States; it is the same venue that will host WrestleMania on April 1-2, 2023. Days before making it to Peacock, the Launch Party was shown on WWE’s social media platforms including YouTube.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-09-26/wrestlemania_launch_party.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;wrestlemania_launch_party&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wrestlers—including those that completed as you’ll see shortly—and celebrities were in attendance for this event; among them were—in order of appearance—comedian Gabriel “Fluffy” Iglesias, James T. Butts Jr. (mayor of Los Angeles), Bianca Belair, Becky Lynch, rap artist and actor Snoop Dogg, Santos Escobar, Valerie Loureda (who is currently a developmental wrestler for the company), Roxanne Perez, YouTube celebrity JoJo Siwa, Liv Morgan, Seth “Freakin’” Rollins, Los Angeles Rams cheerleaders, Medal of Honor recipients, members of the Woody Williams Foundation, the Usos, the Los Angeles Chargers drumline, Rampage the Ram (mascot for the L.A. Rams), and the Los Angeles Lakers cheerleaders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I decided to check out this event mostly for the matches that took place; originally, I thought that the WrestleMania Launch Party was going to be a press conference hyping the premium live event before seeing that there were matches included. Aside from moments that occurred involving the celebrities and wrestlers, there were three matches that took place. My favorite of the three would have to go to the main event match between Los Lotharios and the Street Profits; those two teams showed what they’re capable of especially on the main roster, and it was a good back and forth bout between the two teams from start to finish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the match results from Los Angeles…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-raquel-rodriguez-defeated-nikki-ash&quot;&gt;Match #1: Raquel Rodriguez defeated Nikki A.S.H.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Near the end, Raquel hit Nikki with a corkscrew Vader bomb and then went for the Texana Bomb (f.k.a. the Chingona Bomb) until Nikki countered with a hurricanrana before getting caught using the ropes for leverage while pinning her. Then, Nikki went for a snap swinging neckbreaker (which she used earlier to get the win), but Raquel countered with the Texana Bomb for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-theory-defeated-ricochet&quot;&gt;Match #2: Theory defeated Ricochet.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This match was made after Theory (nowadays going back to his full name Austin Theory) interrupted Seth “Freakin’” Rollins who was talking about WrestleMania. Ricochet came to the ring with the Los Angeles Rams cheerleaders. After Theory hit Ricochet with a torture rack bomb for two, he took a selfie until Ricochet rolled him up for two. Then, Ricochet hit Theory with a recoil and took a selfie while on the top rope before missing on a shooting star press attempt; this led to Theory using the ref as a shield before hitting his opponent with a throat thrust followed by the A-Town Down for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-the-street-profits-w-rampage-the-ram-defeated-los-lotharios&quot;&gt;Main event: The Street Profits (w/ Rampage the Ram) defeated Los Lotharios.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Montez Ford and Angelo Dawkins came to the ring drinking C4 Energy which sponsored the Launch Party. Also, Gabriel Iglesias joined Kayla Braxton and Corey Graves—who were also hosts of the event—on commentary. (Kayla also worked as the ring announcer for the event.) After taking down Angel at ringside, the Street Profits won after a sit out spinebuster by Dawkins followed by the From the Heavens by Ford to Humberto. Ford and Dawkins celebrated with Rampage, cheerleaders from the Los Angeles Rams and the Los Angeles Lakers, and the Los Angeles drumline afterwards. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;icw-fight-club&quot;&gt;ICW Fight Club&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that getting belated recaps is out of the way, let’s head to the GPWA in Glasgow, Scotland in the United Kingdom for an episode of ICW Fight Club.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, it is confirmed that ICW Whit’s Occurrin’ WILL be shown next week on Peacock (or WWE Network for those of you that live outside the United States). As noted in the last issue, it took place on the same night as Clash At the Castle in the same city—Cardiff, Wales—where the WWE premium live event occurred.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Besides Kez Evans defending the ICW World Heavyweight Championship against Grado and the Kings of the North defending the ICW Tag Team Championship against Lou King Sharp &amp;amp; Krieger in a street fight, but we will also see Moxie Malone fight Molly Spartan for the ICW Women’s Championship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Putting next week aside, we learned on this week’s episode of ICW Fight Club that Charles Vyce and Ian Skinner parted ways with Thatcher Wright, and are no longer part of Thatcher’s Cabinet. We then saw Wright in Glasgow asking people to join him, but he ended up getting berated by those that he asked; this included those that aren’t fans of Margaret Thatcher whom Wright praises as we’ve seen ever since his character was born last year in ICW. I know this sounds ridiculous, but I can picture Wright bringing in Progress wrestler Spike Trivet since the “sovereign lord” also gets the “[f-bomb] the Tories” chant from the fans just like Wright and his then-members—Vyce and Skinner—of the Cabinet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-09-26/icwfightclub.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;icw_fight_club&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Four matches took place this week on Fight Club, and my favorite out of the four would have to go to the main event between Craig Anthony and Leyton Buzzard. In this match, not only did we see Buzzard proving himself ever since winning the Square Go! briefcase just like he did in other matches such as the Super Smokin’ Thunderdome at Barred II and fighting BT Gunn in a King of Insanity match recently at Shug’s Hoose Party 7, but also Anthony—despite being out of action for over a year—showing no signs of the metaphoric ring rust. It was a great back and forth bout even with an ending that somehow surprised Buzzard more than it surprised his opponent (even though Anthony was recovering per se). Other than that, it was still a great match from start to finish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the match results from Glasgow…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-moxie-malone-defeated-angel-hayze&quot;&gt;Match #1: Moxie Malone defeated Angel Hayze.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moxie attacked Angel at ringside before the match started until the two fought into the ring. After Moxie rolled to the ropes quickly while Angel had her in a guillotine, Angel took a page out of Chris Ridgeway’s playbook by hitting her with a running punt for two until Moxie hit her with a snap swinging neckbreaker for two; Moxie then got frustrated, grabbed a steel chair from under the ring, and hit Angel in the ribs with it until Angel fought back and took the chair. Suddenly, a distorted video appeared on the screen, and it appeared to have ADM sending a message; Angel saw the video until Moxie made her submit to a sleeper/bodyscissors combo. Post-match, Moxie—in a backstage interview by Cal Wolfe (hopefully I spelled her name right; if not, then I apologize) who debuted on Fight Club last week—announced that she was going after Molly Spartan for the ICW Women’s Championship at Whit’s Occurrin’. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-mikey-divine-vs-rabu-romero-ended-in-a-no-contest-in-two-and-a-half-minutes&quot;&gt;Match #2: Mikey Divine vs. Rabu Romero ended in a no contest in two and a half minutes.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This match was made by “Jackie Polo” and Denise with the winner becoming the “Polo Promotions” graduate. (There have been “Polo Promotions” segments for a few weeks on ICW Fight Club, and started off with four people that not only included Divine and Romero—who both compete as Casino Brutale by the way—but also a male wrestler named Jamie and a woman whose name I forgot unfortunately. Jamie was the first to be eliminated despite acing a written test, and the female participant was the next to be eliminated.) K.O.E. ran in and attacked both Divine and Romero, and the referee threw the match out (instead of calling a double disqualification for some reason). Post-match, Adam and Marcus King demanded a spot in “Polo Promotions”, and “Polo” told them “Show me more!”; K.O.E. did so by beating down Casino Brutale some more, and Denise welcomed them to “Polo Promotions.” &lt;strong&gt;No score.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-3-sheikh-el-sham-defeated-theo-doros&quot;&gt;Match #3: Sheikh El Sham defeated Theo Doros.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before the match started, Doros threw a fit after Simon Cassidy announced that he was the “self-proclaimed ICW Zero G championship contender”; then, as soon as the bell rang, Doros threw a fit after the fans poked fun of his mother as if Saqib Ali and Chris Toal were in the audience. Near the end, Doros went for the Fall From Olympus elbow drop until El Sham hit him with a Frankensteiner for two; Doros exposed a middle turnbuckle, and then sent him into the steel and then DDT’d him for two until El Sham won with a spear. After the match, El Sham looked confused after seeing fans cheering for him, but then—probably turning babyface—decided to celebrate with them before leaving. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-craig-anthony-defeated-leyton-buzzard&quot;&gt;Main event: Craig Anthony defeated Leyton Buzzard.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Buzzard worked on Anthony’s left arm and then, after Anthony missed a moonsault and hit the guardrail earlier, his lower back. Anthony attempted to send a message to Kez Evans by hitting Buzzard with the Kez Dispenser until Buzzard countered with a sharpshooter before “The Natural” punched out of it. Then, towards the end, Buzzard hit Anthony with a Death Valley driver for two, and then went for the Buzzkiller until the two exchanged rollups. Anthony then hit Buzzard with a gourdbuster-like Pedigree for two, and then took off his arm pad and went for a discus forearm until Buzzard hit him with a super kick. Suddenly, Evans came into the ring and waited for Anthony to get up while equipped with brass knuckles until Buzzard stopped him and hit the champion with the Buzzkiller; this led to Anthony recovering and defeating his distracted opponent with the discus forearm. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4.25/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;nxt&quot;&gt;NXT&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, we head to Orlando, Florida in the United States for an episode of NXT.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This episode marked the one-year anniversary of NXT’s “2.0” era (or “multicolored” era as I often call it). Not only did we get to see highlights from last year to last week’s episode, but also what all “2.0” competitors (including those that have very little to no “black and gold” in their veins) in store that night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I first saw NXT’s “2.0” era begin last year, I thought it was a breath of fresh air; it was as if, regardless of what was different about it besides the logo and arena changes, I traveled back to 2012 when NXT turned from a competition show to a brand. It was indeed nice to be introduced to many then-new names not just on NXT, but also on 205 Live and—nowadays—NXT: LVL UP; it was also good to see them clash with the “black and gold” originals prior to either heading to the main roster or another company such as AEW and Impact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the last issue, I said that I voted for a steel cage match (that kicked off this week’s episode), Wes Lee to fight for the NXT North American Championship, and Bron Breakker as the best superstar of the “2.0” era. Believe it or not, all three of my predictions came true that night, even though Lee was unable to compete as you’ll see in the results shortly (and was replaced by someone whom I thought was going to stay on SmackDown after seeing him at Clash At the Castle).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, as the show came to a close, there was a video package narrated by Shawn Michaels who thanked us for watching NXT including their “2.0” era and then said the well-known catchphrase—especially for this brand—“We Are NXT.” The NXT 2.0 logo was then  shown…before “2.0” faded away as the logo changed from multicolored to black and gold! Does this mean a possible change, as well as revival, for that brand? Am I wrapping up my time as calling NXT the “multicolored” brand?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay, now that I’m done asking multiple questions as if Ask.com went back to being “Ask Jeeves”, let’s take a look at the matches that took place. Before I get to that, I thought that Sol Ruca was debuting on NXT this week, but it turns out that she’s coming to NXT at a later date; my apologies for the mistake I made.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-09-26/nxt_pretty_deadly.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;pretty_deadly&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seven matches took place, and four of them were—like most matches throughout the multicolored era—short lived. Three matches were longer as well as enjoyable in my opinion. Out of the three matches that I enjoyed, my favorite would have to go to the opening match that took place inside a steel cage…and no, it has nothing to do with me voting for it. Me being self-centered aside, the steel cage opener was Pretty Deadly defending the NXT Tag Team Championship against the Creed Brothers. It was a great hard-hitting battle, showcasing what both teams had in store as well as how they were able to metaphorically cut the ring in half, “divide and conquer” tactics (including using the mesh as a weapon) and all. Plus, I kind of figured that what happened at Worlds Collide would come into play near the end, but other than that, it was still a great way to kick off this week’s episode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the NXT results from Orlando…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-pretty-deadly-defeated-the-creed-brothers-in-a-steel-cage-match-to-retain-the-nxt-tag-team-championship&quot;&gt;Match #1: Pretty Deadly defeated the Creed Brothers in a steel cage match to retain the NXT Tag Team Championship.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After Elton Prince and Kit Wilson hit Julius with a superplex from the top of the cage, they attempted to hit Brutus with the same maneuver on the top rope until the Creed Brothers turned it into a Doomsday Device with the Brutus Ball (diving cannonball) on the way down. Suddenly, Damon Kemp climbed up the cage and Julius fought him off before it was revealed that he was handcuffed to the top of the cage. While Julius struggled to free himself, Pretty Deadly hit Brutus with Spilled Milk for a near fall, until the handcuffed Julius held onto Wilson while Brutus had Prince in an ankle lock before Wilson freed himself and broke the hold. Then, Pretty Deadly hit Brutus with the second Spilled Milk for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-fallon-henley-w-josh-briggs-brooks-jensen--mason-the-night-howler-ramirez-defeated-lash-legend-in-two-minutes&quot;&gt;Match #2: Fallon Henley (w/ Josh Briggs, Brooks Jensen &amp;amp; Mason “The Night Howler” Ramirez) defeated Lash Legend in two minutes.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ramirez is a patient supported by Connor’s Cure. Fallon won after hitting Lash with a springboard bulldog (ala Trish Stratus) followed by a shining wizard. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-3-the-super-diva-quincy-elliott-defeated-sean-gallagher-in-a-minute-and-a-half&quot;&gt;Match #3: “The Super Diva” Quincy Elliott defeated Sean Gallagher in a minute and a half.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Elliott’s entrance saw him sitting on a slowly rotating director’s chair before heading to the ring; he also wore gear that paid homage to King Mabel. Elliott won after hitting Gallagher with a Banzai drop (ala Rikishi). &lt;strong&gt;No score.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-4-cameron-grimes--joe-gacy-w-the-dyad-defeated-stacks--tony-dangelo&quot;&gt;Match #4: Cameron Grimes &amp;amp; Joe Gacy (w/ the Dyad) defeated Stacks &amp;amp; Tony D’Angelo.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This match was originally Grimes taking on Stacks and D’Angelo by himself; it was made because Grimes refused to get help from the Schism and the D’Angelo Family, and that he decided not to have a tag team partner for this bout. The Schism came to the ring with Gacy becoming his tag team partner during the match; Grimes refused to tag him in until Gacy did so later on. After Grimes and Gacy argued towards the end, D’Angelo and Stacks went after the two until they fought back; it ended with Gacy hitting Stacks with a handspring clothesline. After the match, Grimes read Gacy the riot act until the Dyad beat him down before Gacy hit him with the handspring clothesline. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 0.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-5-nikkita-lyons--zoey-stark-defeated-arianna-grace--kiana-james&quot;&gt;Match #5: Nikkita Lyons &amp;amp; Zoey Stark defeated Arianna Grace &amp;amp; Kiana James.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After Zoey hit Arianna with her flipping GTS (now known as the Z360), Nikkita hit her with a jumping heel kick followed by a leg split leg drop for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-6-hank-walker-defeated-javier-bernal-in-three-minutes&quot;&gt;Match #6: Hank Walker defeated Javier Bernal in three minutes.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This match was made after Bernal poked fun of Walker for being a security guard. Walker came into the ring without a theme song, and looked as if he had butterflies in his stomach. He won after splashing Bernal in a corner followed by a running crossbody. The current NXT theme song (“Down South” by Wale featuring Yella Beezy and Maxo Kream) played after Walker won. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-solo-sikoa-defeated-carmelo-hayes-w-trick-williams-to-become-the-new-nxt-north-american-champion&quot;&gt;Main event: Solo Sikoa defeated Carmelo Hayes (w/ Trick Williams) to become the new NXT North American Champion.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hayes and Williams attacked their elected opponent Wes Lee backstage, and then said that Lee wouldn’t make it to the ring because he “can’t handle being the A-champion”. Then, Sikoa came into the ring and reminded Hayes “I got next.” Sikoa’s left knee was worked on, after Williams slammed it on the apron, during the match. Near the end, Sikoa knocked Williams off the apron and then countered Hayes’ springboard maneuver with a spinning uranage before winning with a top rope splash. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;nxt-lvl-up&quot;&gt;NXT: LVL UP&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Staying in Orlando, we wrap things up with NXT: LVL UP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This episode wasn’t really one of my favorites, mainly because I wanted to see more from all of the wrestlers that were in action  this week regardless of how long or short their matches usually are on NXT: LVL UP. I did however pick “the best of the worst” which were the opener and closer, both involving the current and future members of NXT’s women’s roster; the opener was between Tatum Paxley &amp;amp; Ivy Nile and Sloane Jacobs &amp;amp; Erica Yan, and the closer was between Amari Miller and Indi Hartwell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the NXT: LVL UP results from Orlando…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-tatum-paxley--ivy-nile-defeated-sloane-jacobs--erica-yan&quot;&gt;Match #1: Tatum Paxley &amp;amp; Ivy Nile defeated Sloane Jacobs &amp;amp; Erica Yan.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tatum wore a face protector because of an injury she sustained at an NXT house show (and not due to a training injury like Nigel McGuinness said on commentary); her face was still worked on however. The team of Tatum and Ivy won after an assisted top rope cross-armed splash onto Sloane. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-duke-hudson-defeated-bronco-nima-w-lucien-price-with-a-running-boot&quot;&gt;Match #2: Duke Hudson defeated Bronco Nima (w/ Lucien Price) with a running boot.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My score: 0.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-indi-hartwell-defeated-amari-miller&quot;&gt;Main event: Indi Hartwell defeated Amari Miller.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amari went for a roundhouse kick, but Indi caught her and hit her with a spinebuster for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;next-time&quot;&gt;Next time…&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Along with two shows that have “NXT” in their names, I’m looking back at ICW Whit’s Occurrin’. Will there be a belated recap or two as well? Probably.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For my newsletters as well as any articles that are on the Wrestling With Johners website, the website is wrestlingwithjohners.com/articles&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For just my newsletters along on the WWJ website, it is wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/pro-darin/&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading! Feel free to comment! I’ll see you next time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Photos shown in the newsletter are from WWE, ICW and wXw.)&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>pro-darin</name></author><category term="articles" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Issue 38 Shows of September 17-23, 2022</title><link href="/articles/Issue-38-Shows-of-September-17-23,-2022/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Issue 38 Shows of September 17-23, 2022" /><published>2022-09-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-09-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/Issue%2038%20Shows%20of%20September%2017-23,%202022</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/Issue-38-Shows-of-September-17-23,-2022/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png&quot; alt=&quot;pro darin&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;progress-chapter-137-the-deadly-viper-tourcodename-copperhead&quot;&gt;Progress Chapter 137: The Deadly Viper Tour—Codename: Copperhead&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Again, I’m kicking things off with a belated recap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 137th chapter of Progress Wrestling took place at the O2 Academy in Sheffield, England in the United Kingdom; it served as the first event of the Deadly Viper Tour.
Eight matches were on the card; half of them were championship matches, and the other half were exhibition matches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-09-26/Deadly_Viper_Copperhead.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;deadly_viper_copperhead&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In two of the exhibition matches, we saw two Japanese pro wrestlers take part in those bouts. One was Konosuke Takeshita—whom we’ve seen recently in AEW besides DDT Pro-Wrestling—taking on rising star Leon Slater, and the other was Pro Wrestling Noah competitor Hayata who took on veteran Dean Allmark. Both Takeshita and Hayata were definitely amazing in their Progress appearances (ditto their opponents), and ended up being my favorite exhibition matches of the chapter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I noted, there were also four championship matches. My favorite championship match, as well as my favorite match of the chapter, goes to the three-way dance for the Progress Atlas Championship; originally scheduled to be Luke Jacobs defending the belt against Man Like Dereiss, Mark Davis—who is one half of the tag team Aussie Open—returned to Progress and was added to the bout thus making it a triple threat match. I wasn’t sure what Jacobs vs. Dereiss would be like if the last-minute addition didn’t occur, but on the other hand, this triple threat match didn’t disappoint me one bit. Not only did it show what Dereiss and Davis are capable of in singles competition besides tag team competition, but how Jacobs defies the odds when it comes to competing in other matches such as this three-way bout even with gold on the line.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the match results from Sheffield…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-the-sunshine-machine-defeated-the-greedy-souls-to-retain-the-progress-tag-team-championship&quot;&gt;Match #1: The Sunshine Machine defeated the Greedy Souls to retain the Progress Tag Team Championship.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TK Cooper’s left shoulder was taped. Both teams went at it seconds before the bell rang. Near the end, Danny Jones attempted to give Chuck Mambo either a powerbomb or a piledriver on the apron until Mambo blocked that attempted before he and Cooper hit Jones with the Designated Driver on the apron. Then, Cooper came back in the ring and hit Brendan White with a scissors kick for the win. After the match, the Sunshine Machine said that they were happy to have “the tools” because “the Sunshine Machine rules.” &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-gene-munny-defeated-maggot&quot;&gt;Match #2: Gene Munny defeated Maggot.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Munny came into the ring with the “Gene Munny Championship” belt, and had ring announcer and MC Simon Miller announce that he lives 15 minutes away from Sheffield and is the “undisputed Gene Munny champion of Gene Munny”; he ended up getting streamers afterwards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As soon as the match began, Munny declared that he had his big boy pants off until Maggot ripped the nipple tape off of him. During the match, Munny attempted to splash Maggot in a corner but missed and hit the referee instead; the two then helped up the referee until he fell back down and decided to continue competing. A minute or so later, Maggot helped up the referee on the apron until Munny accidentally knocked him off. A female referee (whom I believe was part of NXT UK) ran in after Maggot countered a top rope maneuver that Munny attempted with a cutter for two. Later, Maggot accidentally poked the female referee in the eyes while kicking out of Munny’s pin attempt, and then pretended that he was hit by Munny’s title until Munny refused; the two wrestlers then played hot potato with the belt before throwing it to the female referee who was then ejected by the original referee used for the bout. Afterwards, Munny won with the Ainsley Lariat. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-3-lana-austin-defeated-raven-creed-and-eliza-alexander-in-a-triple-threat-match&quot;&gt;Match #3: Lana Austin defeated Raven Creed and Eliza Alexander in a triple threat match.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the match began, Raven immediately went after Lana until Eliza blindsided her; Eliza would also have Lana help her double team Raven later on. The end of the match saw Eliza hit Raven with a running knee to the face, and then Lana hit Eliza with a discus forearm before pinning Raven for the win. Post-match, Eliza beat down Lana before storming off. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-4-konosuke-takeshita-defeated-leon-slater&quot;&gt;Match #4: Konosuke Takeshita defeated Leon Slater.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the match, Takeshita fought Slater into the audience and hit his seated opponent with a running boot, sending him into more empty seats. Takeshita picked up the win after countering Slater’s top rope maneuver with a clothesline before hitting him with a running knee strike. After the match, Takeshita showed respect to Slater, and then the 0121 came and—after Dan Maloney helped him up—praised him both in the ring and on commentary; Slater received a standing ovation just like Takeshita did. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-5-luke-jacobs-defeated-man-like-dereiss-and-mark-davis-in-a-triple-threat-match-to-retain-the-progress-atlas-championship&quot;&gt;Match #5: Luke Jacobs defeated Man Like Dereiss and Mark Davis in a triple threat match to retain the Progress Atlas Championship.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After Jacobs picked up a two count after hitting Dereiss with the Burning Lariat, Dereiss ducked the second lariat attempt and hit him with a cutter until Davis went after the two. Near the end, Davis sent Jacobs in the corner until Jacobs popped up with a Burning Lariat for two before Davis put him in an ankle lock; Jacobs got out of the hold before putting Davis in a sleeper which was then broken by Dereiss who hit the two with the Four Fiddy. Dereiss then hit Jacobs with a powerbomb for two, and then hit Davis with a tope at ringside before coming back in where he missed with the Four Fiddy, allowing Jacobs to win with the Burning Lariat. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4.25/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-6-hayata-defeated-dean-allmark&quot;&gt;Match #6: Hayata defeated Dean Allmark.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hayata came to the ring with the GHC Junior Heavyweight Championship belt. After Allmark hit Hayata with the Ruby Cutter and the Clash Driver for a near fall, Hayata hit him with a handspring elbow and an implant DDT; Hayata then won with the Headache running hurricanrana. Post-match, Hayata showed respect to Allmark, and Allmark gave him a handshake and raised the winner’s arm. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-7-laura-di-matteo-defeated-kanji-by-disqualification-kanji-is-still-the-progress-womens-champion&quot;&gt;Match #7: Laura di Matteo defeated Kanji by disqualification; Kanji is still the Progress Women’s Champion.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before the match started, Laura offered Kanji a handshake, but instead slapped the champion. After Laura got out of Kanji’s triangle choke with a rollup for two and Kanji fought out of Laura’s Veni Vidi Vici attempt, Laura brought in a steel chair until Kanji rolled her up for two. Laura choked down the champion and then put her arm in the chair; she attempted to stop the chair closed onto Kanji’s arm until Kanji moved out of the way. Kanji attempted to get her arm free until the chair hit Laura, causing the referee to declare Laura the winner via DQ. Afterwards, Kanji argued with the referee until both she and Laura brawled before the crew people separated the two. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-big-damo-defeated-chris-ridgeway-to-become-the-new-progress-world-champion&quot;&gt;Main event: Big Damo defeated Chris Ridgeway to become the new Progress World Champion.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the match, Damo fought Ridgeway in the crowd, and then hit his seated opponent with a clothesline; he then had him sit on a fan’s lap before the fans (including one Ridgeway sat on) moved out of the way for Damo’s cannonball through the chairs. Ridgeway worked on Damo’s left leg later on even before sitting on a chair and using Damo as a footrest (just like he did to both Warren Banks and Dean Allmark in previous chapters). After Damo hit Ridgeway with the Belfast Blitz (Vader bomb) for two, Ridgeway dodged the second Belfast Blitz attempt and sent him into the post before hitting him with a sliding knee for two followed by hitting him with the Coup de Grace twice for two and then—after some slaps and a stomp—a brainbuster for another two. Towards the end, Ridgeway hit Damo with a running punt, but missed on the second punt before Damo hit him with the Wasteland (ala Wade Barrett), a senton and the second Belfast Blitz for two; Damo then hit him with a shotgun dropkick, some clubbing blows to the back and then the third Belfast Blitz—to the back—for the win.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the match, Damo said that he made a to-do list for his pro wrestling career despite winning a title not being one of them, then told the ring crew to “bring the [f-bombing] beers in”; some cans of beer were thrown in and Damo drank some to celebrate his win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;icw-whits-occurrin&quot;&gt;ICW Whit’s Occurrin’?!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Belated recaps aside, we’re staying in the United Kingdom, but this time, we’re heading to the Y Plas Nightclub in Cardiff, Wales for ICW Whit’s Occurrin’?!
Whit’s Occurrin’?! took place on September 3, 2022, the same night that Clash At the Castle took place in Cardiff; unlike Clash At the Castle which took place at 6PM in the United Kingdom, this ICW event took place at midnight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-09-26/icw_whits_occurin.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;icw_whits_occurin&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There were eight matches that took place that night; four of them were championship matches, and the other four were exhibition matches including an Insane Rules match (which saw a returning ICW regular post-match). For the exhibition matches, I enjoyed the match between Andy Wild and BT Gunn; it was definitely great to see both ICW veterans clash in the ring, from Wild showing that he was focused—after Jason Reed decided to collaborate with Coach Trip as we’ve seen lately on Fight Club—to Gunn coming close to cementing his heel turn even after putting his King of Insanity match with Leyton Buzzard in the rearview. In the end, it was the “Dad Bod God” that defeated ICW’s King of Insanity…which of course had the non-winner pissed off afterwards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for the championship matches, one of them became my favorite match of Whit’s Occurrin’?!; it was the ladder match for the ICW Zero-G Championship, between Daz Black and Luke Kyro, that started off the event with a bang. The back-to-back ladder matches that Black had in two separate events were indeed spectacular, and to me, this ladder match was as good as the last one he had at Shug’s Hoose Party 7. Both he and Kyro gave their all in this match, and in the end, it was Black who retained the title.
Here are the match results from Cardiff…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-daz-black-defeated-luke-kyro-in-a-ladder-match-to-retain-the-icw-zero-g-championship&quot;&gt;Match #1: Daz Black defeated Luke Kyro in a ladder match to retain the ICW Zero-G Championship.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The match was originally scheduled to be a regular one-on-one match until—before the match started—Black pointed out that his belt was hanging from the ceiling, thus making it a ladder match. Several spots in this bout included Kyro jumping from one ladder to another and hitting Black with a sunset flip powerbomb, Black nailing a Spanish fly from both ladders, Kyro bridging a ladder from a corner to another ladder and hitting Black with the Kyroscope onto the bridging ladder, and Black hitting Kyro with a frog splash from the top of a ladder. The end of the match saw Black knocked Kyro off the ladder, climbing up both ladders, and grabbing the title for thew in. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-andy-wild-defeated-bt-gunn&quot;&gt;Match #2: Andy Wild defeated BT Gunn.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the match began, Gunn offered Wild a handshake, but suckered him with a kick to the gut. After exchanging maneuvers such as Wild’s cutter (that countered a midair maneuver that Gunn went for), Gunn’s TMNT flatliner, Wild’s double underhook backbreaker, and Gunn’s bicycle kick, Gunn climbed to the top rope until Wild threw him off and hit him with a cutter from the middle rope; Wild would then win with the Dad Bomb. Post-match, Gunn hit Wild with a super kick and a roundhouse kick before leaving. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-3-the-greedy-souls-defeated-lj-cleary--martin-steers&quot;&gt;Match #3: The Greedy Souls defeated LJ Cleary &amp;amp; Martin Steers.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was Steers’ ICW debut. After Steers hit Brendan White with a springboard cutter and a shooting star press—while Cleary took down Danny Jones at ringside—for two, the Greedy Souls came back and White catapulted Steers into White who hit him with a spinning uranage for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-4-jackie-polo-defeated-jack-jester-in-an-insane-rules-match&quot;&gt;Match #4: “Jackie Polo” defeated Jack Jester in an Insane Rules match.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DCT wore a singlet that had the Union Jack plastered all over it. A small “Big Shiny” (that Jester brandished in the beginning), a few oranges that “Polo” juggled earlier, a staple gun, a flyer for Whit’s Occurrin’?!, Big Shiny wrapped with barbed wire, a chair, and a polo mallet came into play in this match. (A crutch was also pulled out from under the ring, but wasn’t used as a weapon for some reason.) During the match, “Polo” talked to Billy Kirkwood—who was on commentary with ring announcer Simon Cassidy—while fighting Jester until Jester fought back. Also, “Polo” got busted open after Jester stapled the flyer to his forehead. Towards the end, Jester attempted to hit “Polo” with a steel chair until “Polo” beat him down with the mallet for the win. After the match, “Polo” beat down Jester with the mallet some more until all of the sudden, Sha Samuels ran in and attacked “Polo” out of the ring! Then, Samuels said that he wasn’t missing the biggest weekend in British wrestling, telling the “mugs” to “wait ‘til you see me now” before reuniting with Jester as the Kinky Party. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-5-molly-spartan-defeated-moxie-malone-to-retain-the-icw-womens-championship&quot;&gt;Match #5: Molly Spartan defeated Moxie Malone to retain the ICW Women’s Championship.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moxie went for a sleeper/bodyscissors combo (that she has used to win matches recently) until Molly powered out of the attempt before winning with a spear. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-6-glasgow-grindhouse-defeated-kings-of-the-north-in-a-cardiff-street-fight-to-become-the-new-icw-tag-team-champions&quot;&gt;Match #6: Glasgow Grindhouse defeated Kings of the North in a Cardiff Street Fight to become the new ICW Tag Team Champions.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both teams fought before the bell rang, and then fought into the crowd and the venue’s bar; some beer was spat into the faces of Bonesaw and Damien Corvin during the brawl, and there was also a spot where Lou King Sharp dove onto the Kings of the North from the counter. As the action was brought back into the ring, Sharp and Krieger brought a table into the ring until Bonesaw knocked Sharp off the top rope before Corvin put him through a table with a uranage for two. Towards the end, Corvin attempted to hit Krieger with a knockout punch, but missed and hit Bonesaw, leading to the Glasgow Grindhouse hitting him with a dropkick/Black Hole Slam combo for two; then, after Corvin spat in the face of Krieger, Krieger hit him with a powerbomb before Sharp picked up the win with the Tadpole Splash. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-7-leyton-buzzard-defeated-craig-anthony&quot;&gt;Match #7: Leyton Buzzard defeated Craig Anthony.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was a rematch from the episode of Fight Club prior to Whit’s Occurrin’?! During the match, Anthony clotheslined Buzzard into the audience, and then hit him with a top rope crossbody in the crowd. After Anthony hit Buzzard with a top rope powerslam for two, Buzzard countered a springboard maneuver with the Buzzkiller and then won with the X Marks the Spot. Both men showed respect to each other afterwards. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-kez-evans-defeated-grado-to-retain-the-icw-world-heavyweight-championship&quot;&gt;Main event: Kez Evans defeated Grado to retain the ICW World Heavyweight Championship.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After Evans missed on a Claymore attempt (while mocking Drew McIntyre), Grado hit him with a Death Valley driver for two; Grado then went for the Sweet Shin Music, but missed and hit referee Thomas Kearins. Then, Evans hit Grado with a low blow followed by the Kez Dispenser for a near fall after Sean McLaughlin ran in to make the count; this led to Evans punching the referee and then grabbing a steel chair before Grado booted him for two after Mark Dallas took over as a referee. Evans hit Grado with brass knuckles and coerced Dallas to perform the pin count before pinning the challenger for two, and then Grado paid homage to Road Dogg while fighting back until Evans incapacitated him with the Blood Clot Clutch for the win. Afterwards, Evans put Dallas in the Blood Clot Clutch until Jack Jester ran in and fought the champion. Then, “Jackie Polo” ran in and he and Evans beat down Jester until Sha Samuels ran in; the Kinky Party and Grado fought “Polo” out of the ring before triple teaming on Evans. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;nxt&quot;&gt;NXT&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, we head to Orlando, Florida in the United States for an episode of NXT.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Halloween Havoc is coming on October 22, and this time, it won’t be in the form of a special episode of NXT; it will be in the form of a “TakeOver” event (even though “TakeOver” hasn’t been revived yet for the brand’s premium live events per se).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A match was already made for Halloween Havoc this week; it will be a ladder match for the NXT North American Championship which was vacated this week. Kicking off this week’s episode, Shawn Michaels had Solo Sikoa—who won the title last week—relinquish the belt in order to have him focus on his run on SmackDown. (Sikoa, by the way, defended the title against Madcap Moss on SmackDown days after winning it on NXT.) As soon as the title was handed to Michaels, he announced that there would be a ladder match—involving five competitors—for the belt at Halloween Havoc. Carmelo Hayes was automatically inserted into the match despite being accused of attempting to “outsmart the system”, and some qualifying matches were made including one that took place this week. I was surprised that Sikoa would be stripped of the title, and honestly, I was pretty sure that he was going to kill two birds with one stone by competing on both NXT and SmackDown just like Raw superstar Dolph Ziggler did when he defeated Bron Breakker for the NXT Championship early this year. On the other hand, I think this is done to have him focus on being in the Bloodline with Roman Reigns, the Usos, Sami Zayn and Paul Heyman now that he’s on SmackDown.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just like the Progress chapter I reviewed and ICW Whit’s Occurrin’?!, this episode of NXT also had eight matches (I wonder if eight was the magic number for me this week…lol…); both the opener and closer were my favorite matches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The opener was part 2 of the best-of-three series between Axiom and Nathan Frazer. To me, it was as good as their first match, but even better. This match had great back and forth action between the two as well as high flying moments in and out of the ring, and in the end, it was Frazer that tied it up 1-1. I’m definitely looking forward to seeing what the two have in store for their third and final bout of that series.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main event match, that I also enjoyed as I noted, was for a shot at the NXT Championship between Tyler Bate and JD McDonagh. It’s not the first time that we’ve seen the two NXT UK alumni in action; remember their match at NXT UK TakeOver: Blackpool II in January of 2020? Long story short, it was as good as their Blackpool II match, even if we nowadays see McDonagh’s character showing a dark and disturbing side where everybody’s pain—including his own—is his pleasure. I was pretty sure we were going to see Breakker vs. Bate II at a later date (including the aforementioned Halloween Havoc), but McDonagh proved us wrong by picking up the win; this means that we’ll see Breakker vs. McDonagh II in the future…or are we?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the NXT results (including the reason why I said “or are we?”) from Orlando…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-nathan-frazer-defeated-axiom&quot;&gt;Match #1: Nathan Frazer defeated Axiom.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was match #2 in their best-of-three series, with Axiom coming into the match with the 1-0 lead. After Axiom was unable to make Frazer submit to the LeBell Lock (P.S.: RIP Gene LeBell whom we’ve lost last month), he climbed to the top rope until Frazer popped up and hit him with a superplex followed by an elevated corkscrew neckbreaker; Frazer then won with a phoenix splash. Both Frazer and Axiom are now tied 1-1. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-gigi-dolin--jacy-jayne-defeated-tatum-paxley--ivy-nile-in-almost-four-minutes&quot;&gt;Match #2: Gigi Dolin &amp;amp; Jacy Jayne defeated Tatum Paxley &amp;amp; Ivy Nile in almost four minutes.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ivy cleaned house towards the end until Gigi and Jacy came back and Gigi held Ivy for a big boot from Jacy for the win; Ivy is no longer undefeated on the NXT brand. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-3-the-dyad-w-joe-gacy-defeated-edris-enofé--malik-blade&quot;&gt;Match #3: The Dyad (w/ Joe Gacy) defeated Edris Enofé &amp;amp; Malik Blade.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This match was made after Enofé and Blade poked fun of the Schism for failing to have Cameron Grimes as a member of the team, leading to the two fighting the Dyad in the parking lot. Before the match started, the Schism talked about last week being the end of those that were “on the fence” on joining them, and that they brought it onto themselves without admitting that the road to peace and inclusivity can be scary; Gacy then accused Cameron Grimes of not joining them and facing the wrath of the Schism until Enofé and Blade ran in and fought Jagger Reid and Rip Fowler out of the ring. The Dyad won after hitting Enofé with an assisted Canadian destroyer followed by the Ticket To Mayhem. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-4-cora-jade-defeated-wendy-choo-in-four-minutes&quot;&gt;Match #4: Cora Jade defeated Wendy Choo in four minutes.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After Wendy hit Cora with a German suplex, Cora sent Wendy face first into the turnbuckles before winning with a double underhook DDT. After the match, Lash Legend ran in and kicked Wendy down. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-5-andre-chase--bodhi-hayward-w-thea-hail-defeated-carmelo-hayes--trick-williams-in-four-minutes&quot;&gt;Match #5: Andre Chase &amp;amp; Bodhi Hayward (w/ Thea Hail) defeated Carmelo Hayes &amp;amp; Trick Williams in four minutes.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before the match started, Hayes and Williams demanded they wanted those that played Solo Sikoa’s theme song, refereed Hayes vs. Sikoa, and the timekeeper fired, with Hayes still declaring himself “the A-champion.” Then, Chase U came into the ring, and Chase called it—regardless of how many times Hayes and Williams didn’t want to hear it—a “teachable moment” before fighting the two out of the ring. Chase cleaned house until Williams came back with a bicycle kick before knocking Hayward off the apron. Then, Hayes came in and went for a springboard maneuver until Chase countered with a rollup for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-6-von-wagner-w-mr-stone-defeated-sanga-in-almost-three-minutes&quot;&gt;Match #6: Von Wagner (w/ Mr. Stone) defeated Sanga in almost three minutes.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After Sanga fought Wagner out of the ring, Mr. Stone distracted Sanga, leading to Wagner sending him into a post and steel steps before deadlifting him and winning with a Death Valley bomb. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 0.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-7-oro-mensah-defeated-grayson-waller-to-qualify-for-the-nxt-north-american-championship-ladder-match-at-halloween-havoc&quot;&gt;Match #7: Oro Mensah defeated Grayson Waller to qualify for the NXT North American Championship ladder match at Halloween Havoc.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mensah is not a WWE newcomer; he’s actually NXT UK alum Oliver Carter. Plus, Mensah’s entrance had stanchions and velvet rope at the entryway, looking like the entrance to a nightclub. Near the end, Waller went for his through-the-ropes cutter finisher until he saw Apollo Crews—red eye and all—appear with bloody tear coming down his cheek. This led to Mensah hitting Waller with a tope before winning with a running heel kick in the corner. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-jd-mcdonagh-defeated-tyler-bate-to-become-the-1-contender-for-the-nxt-championship&quot;&gt;Main event: JD McDonagh defeated Tyler Bate to become the #1 contender for the NXT Championship.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bron Breakker, who brought Connor’s Cure patient Landon “The Conqueror” Chase to the arena, joined Vic Joseph and Wade Barrett on commentary. During the match, Bate fought McDonagh out of the ring before hitting him with a tope into the announce table; McDonagh ended up smiling as if he enjoyed being attacked afterwards. After blocking Bate’s Bop and Bang, McDonagh hit him with a Spanish fly until Bate hit him with the Bop and Bang while on his back. Then, towards the end, Bate went for the Tyler Driver ’97 off the top rope until McDonagh powered out of the attempt and hit him with a Spanish fly before winning with the Devlin Side (now renamed “Devil Inside”…and I don’t think it has anything to do with INXS). After the match, Breakker and McDonagh met face to face in the ring until all of the sudden, Ilja Dragunov—back from an ankle injury—came in and stood in the ring with the two! &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;nxt-lvl-up&quot;&gt;NXT: LVL UP&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Staying in Orlando, we wrap things up with NXT: LVL UP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-09-26/nxt_lvl_up.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;nxt_lvl_up&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This week’s episode was fairly better than last week’s episode match wise. There was one match—out of the three that were shown—that I thought was better than the rest; that match that I enjoyed was the main event bout between Andre Chase and hearing impaired up-and-comer Myles Borne. Even though Borne has yet to pick up a win after what was his seventh match this week, you could tell that he can still give rising stars such as Chase a run for their money in his matches. Not only did Borne do well, but so did Chase himself who ended up—like on this week’s episode of NXT—picking up the win.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the NXT: LVL UP results from Orlando…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-dante-chen-defeated-bryson-montana-with-a-hard-double-chop-to-the-chest&quot;&gt;Match #1: Dante Chen defeated Bryson Montana with a hard double chop to the chest.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My score: 1.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-indi-hartwell-defeated-valentina-feroz-in-four-and-a-half-minutes&quot;&gt;Match #2: Indi Hartwell defeated Valentina Feroz in four and a half minutes.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After Valentina made a comeback with a dropkick and a crossbody, she went for a wheelbarrow maneuver until Indi blocked it and won with a spinebuster. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-andre-chase-w-bodhi-hayward-and-thea-hail-defeated-myles-borne&quot;&gt;Main event: Andre Chase (w/ Bodhi Hayward and Thea Hail) defeated Myles Borne.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Borne worked on one of Chase’s arms briefly until Chase came back with a side Russian leg sweep, the Chase U stomps and a top rope crossbody for the win. Both men shook hands afterwards. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;next-time&quot;&gt;Next time…&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The currently usual three—ICW, NXT and NXT: LVL UP—and a belated recap or two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For my newsletters as well as any articles that are on the Wrestling With Johners website, the website is wrestlingwithjohners.com/articles&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For just my newsletters along on the WWJ website, it is wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/pro-darin/&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading! Feel free to comment! I’ll see you next time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Photos shown in the newsletter are from WWE, Progress and ICW.)&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>pro-darin</name></author><category term="articles" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">HEATH SLATER on BROCK LESNAR #shorts</title><link href="/rewind-recap-relive/videos/HEATH-SLATER-on-BROCK-LESNAR-shorts/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="HEATH SLATER on BROCK LESNAR #shorts" /><published>2022-09-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-09-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/rewind-recap-relive/videos/HEATH%20SLATER%20on%20BROCK%20LESNAR%20shorts</id><content type="html" xml:base="/rewind-recap-relive/videos/HEATH-SLATER-on-BROCK-LESNAR-shorts/"></content><author><name>rewind-recap-relive</name></author><category term="rewind-recap-relive" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">5 QUESTIONS! Featuring ThunderRosa</title><link href="/straight-talk-wrestling/videos/5-QUESTIONS-Featuring-ThunderRosa/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="5 QUESTIONS! Featuring ThunderRosa" /><published>2022-09-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-09-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/straight-talk-wrestling/videos/5%20QUESTIONS%20Featuring%20ThunderRosa</id><content type="html" xml:base="/straight-talk-wrestling/videos/5-QUESTIONS-Featuring-ThunderRosa/"></content><author><name>george-mckay</name></author><category term="straight-talk-wrestling" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Wanna know? @All Elite Wrestling #wrestler @Thunder Rosa answer? #aew #prowrestling</title><link href="/straight-talk-wrestling/videos/Wanna-know-All-Elite-Wrestling-wrestler-Thunder-Rosa-answer-aew-prowrestling/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Wanna know? @All Elite Wrestling #wrestler @Thunder Rosa answer? #aew #prowrestling" /><published>2022-09-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-09-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/straight-talk-wrestling/videos/Wanna%20know%20All%20Elite%20Wrestling%20%20wrestler%20Thunder%20Rosa%20answer%20aew%20prowrestling</id><content type="html" xml:base="/straight-talk-wrestling/videos/Wanna-know-All-Elite-Wrestling-wrestler-Thunder-Rosa-answer-aew-prowrestling/"></content><author><name>george-mckay</name></author><category term="straight-talk-wrestling" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>