<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-01-05T20:39:11+00:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Wrestling With Johners</title><subtitle>Pro Wrestling podcast with news, reviews and debate from WWE, NXT, NXT:UK, AEW, NJPW, Indy Wrestling and so much more. Listen to Wrestling With Johners on Apple Podcasts, Google Podcasts, Spotify, Podbean, Podcast Addict, Castbox, YouTube or wherever you get your podcasts.</subtitle><author><name>John Scott</name></author><entry><title type="html">Ep91 - NJPW Wrestle Kingdom 14 (Day 1 - 4th Jan 2020) with @KurtsAnglePod</title><link href="/podcasts/EP91/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep91 - NJPW Wrestle Kingdom 14 (Day 1 - 4th Jan 2020) with @KurtsAnglePod" /><published>2020-01-05T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP91</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP91/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep92 - NJPW Wrestle Kingdom 14 (Day 2 - 5th Jan 2020) with Griz</title><link href="/podcasts/EP92/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep92 - NJPW Wrestle Kingdom 14 (Day 2 - 5th Jan 2020) with Griz" /><published>2020-01-05T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP92</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP92/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">NXTUK Review - January 2nd, 2020</title><link href="/articles/NXTUK-Review-January-2nd-2020/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="NXTUK Review - January 2nd, 2020" /><published>2020-01-05T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/NXTUK%20Review%20January%202nd%202020</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/NXTUK-Review-January-2nd-2020/">&lt;p&gt;2 additional matches have been made for Takeover Blackpool 2:- Trent Seven vs. Eddie Dennis and Tyler Bate vs. Jordan Devlin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-05/trenteddienxtuk.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;trent eddie&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-05/tylerjordan.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;jordan tyler&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First match of 2020 - Dave Mastiff vs Kona Reeves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kona cut a promo before the match to get heat. This was an ok match. Kona hasn’t been too lucky since coming to NXT UK.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Winner of the match: Dave Mastiff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here comes Toni Storm. She calls out Piper Niven she asks Piper to step aside. Piper says no. They brawl and out comes Kay Lee Ray.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-05/PiperToni.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;piper toni&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kassius Ohno vs Ligero.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good match. I enjoyed this one. Kassius is a good heel. He is getting a push on NXT UK more than the normal NXT. Not many High flying moves in this match. Kassius Ohno cuts a promo after the match.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Winner of the match: Kassius Ohno.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ashton Smith and Oliver Carter vs The Outliers: Riddick Moss and Dorian Mack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good tag match. Ashton and Oliver have had no luck and no wins since coming to NXT UK. Hopefully the team of Riddick Moss &amp;amp; Dorian Mack are going to get a push. A very shocking end to the match.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Winner of the match: Ashton Smith and Oliver Carter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alexander Wolfe vs Ilja Dragunov in a No DQ Match.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-05/iljawolfe.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;ilja wolfe&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good main event. Many weapons involved. Great story telling in this one. The rest of imperium banned from ringside. Ilja went after Alexander before the bell. Brutal match. DDT and a suplex onto chairs. A chair uses on Ilja’s fingers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Winner of the match: Ilja Dragunov. Really good way to start off 2020.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t forget to go check and then like and subscribe to my YouTube channel the people’s WWE channel. IF YOU SMELL WHAT RICK THE ROCK IS COOKIN.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>ricky-j</name></author><summary type="html">2 additional matches have been made for Takeover Blackpool 2:- Trent Seven vs. Eddie Dennis and Tyler Bate vs. Jordan Devlin.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Epic Night #1 Wrestle Kingdom 14. Plus, The Main Event of Night #2 Set</title><link href="/news/wrestlekingdom-14-night-1/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Epic Night #1 Wrestle Kingdom 14. Plus, The Main Event of Night #2 Set" /><published>2020-01-04T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-04T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/news/wrestlekingdom%2014%20night%201</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/wrestlekingdom-14-night-1/">&lt;p&gt;After an epic night one of Wrestle Kingdom (4th Jan 2020) the main event of night two (5th Jan 2020) has been cemented. As newly crowned IWGP Intercontinental Champion Tetsuya Naito will face the reigning IWGP Heavyweight Champion, Kaszuskda Okada.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-04/OkadaNaito.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;okada naito set&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earlier in the evening Naito managed to regain the Intercontinental title after defeating Jay White, in a hard fought semi main event, inside of the sold out Tokyo Dome. While Okada battled for over 30+ minutes in an epic main event against Kota Ibushi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both Ibushi and Okada withstood a huge amount of offence against one-another, in what was the best match of the night, on a night of excellent matches, in what is already the best show of the year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Night two of Wrestle Kingdom 14 will not only feature the ‘Double Champ Dash’ between Okada vs. Naito. But will also feature Jon Moxley vs. Juice Robinson  for Moxley’s United States Championship, Chris Jericho vs. Hiroshi Takahashi, Zack Sabre Jr vs. SANADA for the British Heavyweight Championship, Jay White vs. Kota Ibushi,  and of course the final ever match of Jushin ‘Thunder’ Liger’s career.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html">After an epic night one of Wrestle Kingdom (4th Jan 2020) the main event of night two (5th Jan 2020) has been cemented. As newly crowned IWGP Intercontinental Champion Tetsuya Naito will face the reigning IWGP Heavyweight Champion, Kaszuskda Okada.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep90 - Interview with BIG F’N JOE (with Turnbuckle TV)</title><link href="/podcasts/EP90/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep90 - Interview with BIG F'N JOE (with Turnbuckle TV)" /><published>2020-01-03T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP90</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP90/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Brackets For 2020 Dusty Rhodes Tag Team Classic (NXT vs. NXT:UK)</title><link href="/news/Bracket-For-2020-Dusty-Rhodes-Tag-Team-Classic/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Brackets For 2020 Dusty Rhodes Tag Team Classic (NXT vs. NXT:UK)" /><published>2020-01-02T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/news/Bracket%20For%202020%20Dusty%20Rhodes%20Tag%20Team%20Classic</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/Bracket-For-2020-Dusty-Rhodes-Tag-Team-Classic/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-02/2020dustybracket.png&quot; alt=&quot;dusty tag classic brackets&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the eight teams for the tournament announced, the brackets for this year’s Dusty Rhodes Tag Team Classic has now been revealed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imperium (Marcel Barthel &amp;amp; Fabian Aichner) vs. The Forgotten Sons (Wesley Blake &amp;amp; Steve Cutler) and Matt Riddle &amp;amp; Pete Dunne vs. Mark Andrews &amp;amp; Flash Morgan Webster are the matches on the left side of the bracket.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The right side of the bracket has The Grizzled Young Veterans (Zack Gibson &amp;amp; James Drake) vs. Kushida and his partner (yet to be revealed) and The Undisputed Era (Kyle O’Reilly &amp;amp; Bobby Fish) vs. Gallus (Mark Coffey &amp;amp; Wolfgang).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;O’Reilly &amp;amp; Fish are the NXT Tag Team Champions, while Coffey &amp;amp; Wolfgang currently hold the NXT UK Tag Team titles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Dusty Classic features four teams from NXT (Undisputed Era, The Forgotten Sons, Riddle &amp;amp; Dunne, and Kushida’s team) and four teams from NXT UK (The Grizzled Young Veterans, Gallus, Imperium, and Andrews &amp;amp; Webster).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The schedule for the tournament hasn’t been announced.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">NXT and NXT UK to air on BT Sports</title><link href="/news/NXT-and-NXT-UK-to-air-on-BT-Sports/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="NXT and NXT UK to air on BT Sports" /><published>2020-01-01T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/news/NXT%20and%20NXT%20UK%20to%20air%20on%20BT%20Sports</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/NXT-and-NXT-UK-to-air-on-BT-Sports/">&lt;p&gt;BT Sport announced earlier this week that NXT and NXT UK will be joining their line-up of WWE programming. WWE’s deal with BT Sport will commence January 1st 2020.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like Raw and SmackDown, NXT will air live on BT Sport at the same time as it airs in the United States. The first show on BT will be this week’s taped episode of NXT, which begins at 1 a.m. local time on January 2nd for those in the UK and Ireland.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-01/nxtbt.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;NXT and NXTUK on BT Sports&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BT Sport wrote that “as well as airing all Raw, SmackDown and NXT shows live, BT Sport will also show primetime same day repeats. In addition, customers can catch up on all the overnight action whenever and wherever they like via the enhanced video player on the BT Sport app on mobile and BTSport.com.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BT Sport noted that full schedule details are to be announced for NXT UK. The show airs on the WWE Network on Thursdays.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a 30-year partnership, WWE closed out their run on Sky Sports with the Dec 30th edition of Raw.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html">BT Sport announced earlier this week that NXT and NXT UK will be joining their line-up of WWE programming. WWE’s deal with BT Sport will commence January 1st 2020.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Jushin Liger Will Retire With His Mask</title><link href="/news/Jushin-Liger-Will-Retire-With-His-Mask/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Jushin Liger Will Retire With His Mask" /><published>2019-12-31T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-12-31T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/news/Jushin%20Liger%20Will%20Retire%20With%20His%20Mask</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/Jushin-Liger-Will-Retire-With-His-Mask/">&lt;p&gt;The big wrestling event to kick off the year 2020 will be NJPW WrestleKingdom 14, which will feature the final two matches of Jushin Liger’s career. While you would think that the legend might unmask when he retires, that will not be the case.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an interview with Tokyo Sports Liger said that he will keep his mask even when his time in the ring is done. He said: “If you wear a mask even if you retire, it’s okay to take the name Liger.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Liger said that he can’t become a “Sugao”, which means “real face,” or “unmasked face” in his case.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jushin Liger made his debut with the mask in 1989.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the first night of WrestleKingdom, he will team with Tatsumi Fujinami, The Great Sasuke &amp;amp; Tiger Mask against Naoki Sano, Shinjiro Otani, Tatsuhito Takaiwa &amp;amp; Ryusuke Taguchi. On night two, he will team with Naoki Sano against Ryu Lee &amp;amp; Hiromu Takahashi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A retirement ceremony will be held at New Year Dash, on 6th January 2020.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2019-12-31/jushin liger.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;jushin liger&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html">The big wrestling event to kick off the year 2020 will be NJPW WrestleKingdom 14, which will feature the final two matches of Jushin Liger’s career. While you would think that the legend might unmask when he retires, that will not be the case.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">RAW Women’s Championship match announced for Royal Rumble 2020</title><link href="/news/RAW-Women-s-Championship-match-announced-for-Royal-Rumble-2020/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="RAW Women’s Championship match announced for Royal Rumble 2020" /><published>2019-12-31T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-12-31T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/news/RAW%20Women%E2%80%99s%20Championship%20match%20announced%20for%20Royal%20Rumble%202020</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/RAW-Women-s-Championship-match-announced-for-Royal-Rumble-2020/">&lt;p&gt;It was announced on the Dec 30th edition of RAW that Becky Lynch will face Asuka, at the Royal Rumble PPV from Houston, Texas on 26th Jan. With Becky’s RAW Women’s Championship on the line.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a backstage segment Becky told Charly Caruso that this was the match she wanted during recent contract negotiations. With Asuka being the only WWE Superstar on the women’s roster that she is yet to defeat. ‘The Man’ is looking for redemption after losing to Asuka at last year’s Royal Rumble, tapping out to the ‘Asuka-lock’.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lynch looks to continue her reign as the longest reigning RAW Women’s Champion, which started at WrestleMania 35. But don’t rule out the current Women’s Tag Team Champion Asuka, as she looks to become “Asuka two-belts” on 26th Jan 2020.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/TheMan?src=hash&amp;amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;#TheMan&lt;/a&gt; gets her wish.&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/BeckyLynchWWE?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;@BeckyLynchWWE&lt;/a&gt; WILL defend her &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/RAW?src=hash&amp;amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;#RAW&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/WomensTitle?src=hash&amp;amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;#WomensTitle&lt;/a&gt; against WWE Women&amp;#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/TagTeamChampion?src=hash&amp;amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;#TagTeamChampion&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/WWEAsuka?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;@WWEAsuka&lt;/a&gt; at &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/RoyalRumble?src=hash&amp;amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;#RoyalRumble&lt;/a&gt;! &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/H6j4oYN52G&quot;&gt;pic.twitter.com/H6j4oYN52G&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; WWE (@WWE) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/WWE/status/1211839784949342208?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;December 31, 2019&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;</content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html">It was announced on the Dec 30th edition of RAW that Becky Lynch will face Asuka, at the Royal Rumble PPV from Houston, Texas on 26th Jan. With Becky’s RAW Women’s Championship on the line.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">AEW - Just My Opinion!</title><link href="/articles/AEW-Just-My-Opinion/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="AEW - Just My Opinion!" /><published>2019-12-30T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-12-30T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/AEW%20Just%20My%20Opinion</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/AEW-Just-My-Opinion/">&lt;p&gt;This week I am focussing on AEW, a lot has been said and written about the new kids on the block over the last 12 months in FB groups, Pods, Vlogs and just about everywhere else you can imagine so I am just going to focus on my opinions and perceptions of what I have enjoyed or not and what I feel about All Elite Wrestling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To begin, I guess we start at the beginning… variety is the spice of life so when word of a new promotion came about I looked on it as a positive, the fact that the names associated with it were well known and popular in the industry, and looked like they would be getting some hefty financial backing I was certainly intrigued and hopeful that this would be good for wrestling on the whole.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What followed over the coming months actually turned me OFF the idea of AEW. We all know about keyboard warriors and how the IWC generally works but all this went into over drive in the build up to AEW – sign this guy, sign that guy, AEW will put Vince out of business etc etc. All this was way, WAY before a single episode of Dynamite had aired. It also came across in the shows too and felt a little desperate to grab attention and be controversial. But for the most part as things have progressed that seems to have stopped for the most part with only a few little references which have actually been quite amusing. like Jericho’s list and how he put down the crowd and corrected them that it’s NOT a list – although substituting it for the “Lexicon of Le Champion” didn’t actually mean what they were intending it to mean, but if you think about what we as fans are expected to accept in wrestling then I don’t really think anyone is too fussed by linguistics or grammar &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then there was the weekly argument for bragging rights over viewing figures, which became a much quieter argument once they levelled out!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall I think its excellent for wrestling on the whole to have competition, my opinion from the start is that it is hard to judge over a short period of time so I would be keen to see how things are going in 12 months – can AEW avoid the pitfalls that WWE periodically stumbles head first into? What changes will be seen in WWE to react to AEW? What individuals will step up to the plate for either company to strive for the next level?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Below, I am going to break down my thoughts into things I have seen as positives so far and areas that, in my opinion, need development going forwards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;positives&quot;&gt;Positives&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll start with the AEW Tag Division, growing up watching wrestling tag team teams were a big deal, teams stayed together for long periods of time with a large variety of gimmicks and styles until sometimes you’d get the break out singles star coming out of a team. More recently tag team matches have become increasingly more often used to give ring time/TV time to multiple singles wrestlers. Totally blame Teddy Long here playa!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its no surprise with The Young Bucks being key players in AEW that tag wrestling would get some attention and the teams signed from the start showed that there would be a big focus on this. There’s been a big focus on high flying tag matches, which obviously isn’t for everyone but several of the matches on Dynamite so far have been genuinely top drawer especially during the Tag Title tournament. Having proper teams who have been together for a long time and had matches previously has allowed the division to hit the ground running and most matches have been well put together to showcase the talent and variety of styles. It is also a breath of fresh air that AEW has steered clear of obvious booking decisions – like The Bucks losing early in the title tournament and SCU progressing without Christopher Daniels. It will be interesting to see how the division continues to develop from both talent and storyline perspectives. I’d expect to see Proud and Powerful take the titles in 2020 not only as they are a fantastic team but it would make sense for the Inner Circle to gain more gold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Promos, for the most part have been excellent week after week with Jericho obviously setting a pretty high bar which the likes of Cody, MJF and Scorpio Sky have really risen to. MJF in particular really shone in his back and forth with Le Champion after turning on Cody, the back and forth between the two was in equal parts amusing and intense while moving forward the narrative of the relationship between MJF and Cody.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The highlight for me though has been Cody Rhodes, the verbal sparring leading up to his title showdown with Jericho was brilliant, both with in ring promos and the taped vignettes. Cody has a great look with his expensive suits and how he represents the corporate side of the Brand but when he speaks in the ring, he portrays so much passion and respect for the business he commands attention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are a number of new names and faces appearing regularly in AEW who have impressed me, they may not be new to everyone but they are to me. Darby Allin and Joey Janela are both names I was aware of prior to watching Dynamite weekly and both have shown that they are more than simply gimmick wrestlers. Sammy Guevara in particular has grown on me rapidly, the opening Dynamite match vs Cody didn’t impress me much but how he has developed as a part of the Inner Circle he has gone up considerably in my estimation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jurassic Express as a unit are very new to me but both in ring and as a gimmick, they have been very impressive, Luchasaurus has a phenomenal look, hard hitting style and his brief bit of mic work facing off against Jericho was great and unexpected. Jungle Boy has impressed in his matches despite a losing record – he sells really well which is fortunate given the amount of time he spends on the receiving end but also has a good offensive move set. Marko Stunt is a phenomenon all of himself, he reminds me so much of Spike Dudley for obvious reasons. He always seems to be having fun despite being thrown around like a ragdoll!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, Orange Cassidy…. I absolutely love this gimmick, I probably shouldn’t but I do! I have spent far too much time recently watching match after match on YouTube and it just really works – obviously he is a really talented wrestler and athlete but his gimmick shows that he doesn’t need that to get over. From what I have seen in AEW he is being booked brilliantly and can’t wait to see what they do with him going forwards, but for now just being alongside the Best Friends with little involvements here and there is working really well for him as is evident by the pops he is getting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kenny Omega obviously isn’t a new face, but he is someone that I knew more by reputation than from seeing all that much of him, I have watched some NJPW over the last few years but never consistently. Early impressions in AEW for me were a bit mixed, I am not sure if he was deliberately being held back so it didn’t look like the execs were getting the rub from their positions, but in recent weeks the more I have seen of him I am starting to “get” the hype around him and would now say I am a fan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, I can’t talk about the positives of AEW without talking about Le Champion, Chris Jericho may be sporting a dad bod these days and the Judas Elbow is a People Elbow/Five knuckle shuffle type move in my opinion but I have always loved watching Jericho in the ring. Watching the way he moves around the ring, plays the crowd reacts and interacts with his opponents is always impressive and his mic work is consistently good and utilises it perfectly to go with the heel persona even down to how he pronounces Tony Schiavone’s name. Ignore the associated names and financial clout behind them AEW is still a fledgling company so to have Jericho involved and furthermore have him at the pinnacle of the Brand is vitally important.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;requires-development&quot;&gt;Requires development&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TV presentation – in my opinion from the PPVs so far and Dynamite there is a great deal of room for improvement in how AEW is presented technically, there have been a number of mistakes and gaffs so far which need to be ironed out – say what you want about Raw/Smackdown but the production values are sky high in comparison to AEW at this point. The highlight of this which will also lead onto my next point is the women’s Casino Battle Royale which I can only describe as a complete clusterf*** in terms of the presentation and commentary as well as the in-ring action. And remember when Tony Schiavone was off doing something else and they had some random stage hand on comms for a bit…. I don’t think anyone had any idea what was going on then!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before I start on the Women’s division, I have to say that improvements have been seen since I first started prepping this piece but there’s still a lot of scope to get better. The division is missing some top talent, a lot of what was making it to TV in the early weeks was a really low standard. I struggle to buy in to Rhio as champion – and I usually like an underdog – she seems far too timid and lacks in presence, on the flip side I think it would be equally bad had they put the title on Nyla Rose who I don’t feel has a great deal of in ring skill based on what I have seen so far. Hikaru Shida has really impressed me so far and Emi Sakura is great although arguably reaching the end of her career now – I recall seeing her about 10 years ago at an Indy show in Wolverhampton. The recent addition of Kris Statlander is a definite plus for AEWs women’s division though as she has looked very impressive in her matches so far, although would question her walking almost straight into the title picture&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Explaining the unknowns seems to have been a bit of an issue for AEW for example… “that’s the Butcher…. That’s the Blade…” but who are they? “It’s the Butcher and the Blade and the Bunny!” As a unit they are quite intriguing but the introduction was so random with zero build it didn’t make a whole heap of sense. Similarly, with Kris Statlander there seems to be zero build, and very little acknowledgement or explanation of her being “The Galaxy’s Greatest Alien”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And finally, Good Ol JR – it pains me to say it but I think his time is done, its almost like he has become a caricature of himself and speaks and shouts mostly nonsense throughout the broadcast. I quite like Excalibur and I can put up with Schiavone although I think they would be better off using new names on commentary who are more relevant and “in the know” for the modern product, I wouldn’t be averse to wheeling JR out for special matches or occasions but I’d prefer to hear a more modern voice alongside the in ring action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So that’s just my opinion on AEW so far, I remain open minded and hope to enjoy the ride over the coming months and see what changes in the business&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;name-drop&quot;&gt;Name Drop…&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With each article I will try to add in a relevant name drop for a wrestler I have met or experience I have had. Since we’re talking AEW I’ll throw back to meeting Trent Berreta at Kamikaze Pro’s “Project K” show. Trent had an amazing match against Pete Dunne, on a card which also included Eddie Dennis vs Tommaso Ciampa. Both matches were fantastic and it’s hard to pick between the two. Trent vs Pete was technically amazing and demonstrated great story telling throughout with some great spots and then was great meeting and chatting with fans at the end of the show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2019-12-30/Trent Barretta pic.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;trent baretta&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am on Twitter where I have a new profile – Matt Based Wrestling - just to focus on all things wrestling related, you can follow me at &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/mattbasedwres01&quot;&gt;@mattbasedwres01&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>matt-bayliss</name></author><summary type="html">This week I am focussing on AEW, a lot has been said and written about the new kids on the block over the last 12 months in FB groups, Pods, Vlogs and just about everywhere else you can imagine so I am just going to focus on my opinions and perceptions of what I have enjoyed or not and what I feel about All Elite Wrestling.</summary></entry></feed>