<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-11-27T08:19:01+00:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Wrestling With Johners</title><subtitle>Pro Wrestling podcast with news, reviews and debate from WWE, NXT, NXT:UK, AEW, NJPW, Indy Wrestling and so much more. Listen to Wrestling With Johners on Apple Podcasts, Google Podcasts, Spotify, Podbean, Podcast Addict, Castbox, YouTube or wherever you get your podcasts.</subtitle><author><name>John Scott</name></author><entry><title type="html">Issue 45 Shows of November 5-11, 2022</title><link href="/articles/Issue-45-Shows-of-November-5-11,-2022/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Issue 45 Shows of November 5-11, 2022" /><published>2022-11-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-11-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/Issue%2045%20Shows%20of%20November%205-11,%202022</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/Issue-45-Shows-of-November-5-11,-2022/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png&quot; alt=&quot;pro darin&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;pro-wrestling-noah-ariake-triumph--the-return--pro-wrestling-love-forever-3--triumph-&quot;&gt;Pro Wrestling Noah Ariake Triumph – The Return – Pro-Wrestling Love Forever 3 ~ Triumph ~&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though I was unable to finish up a Progress chapter (I’ll recap it in the next issue by the way), I’m still kicking things off with another Pro Wrestling Noah bonus.
Pro Wrestling Noah’s “The Return” (full name “Pro Wrestling Noah Ariake Triumph – The Return – Pro-Wrestling Love Forever 3 ~ Triumph ~”) took place on October 30 at the Ariake Arena in Tokyo, Japan; it was the same venue that hosted volleyball during the 2020 Summer Olympics and wheelchair basketball during the 2020 Summer Paralympics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-11-27/noah.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;noah&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ten matches—eleven if you count the pre-show match—took place that night; on the card—besides the one-on-one match that served as a pre-show bout—were three six-man tag team matches, two regular tag team matches, and five championship matches including one that was under martial arts rules.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There were three matches that I enjoyed when I checked out “The Return.” One was the tag team match between Dante Leon &amp;amp; ICW wrestler Jack Morris and Yo-Hey &amp;amp; Daiki Inaba, and there was very good tag team chemistry from all four competitors as well as fun “looking at the mirror” like moments by Leon and Yo-Hey whenever they clashed with one another.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another was the main event where Kaito Kiyomiya, for the first time, defended the GHC Heavyweight Championship against Kazuyuki Fujita; Fujita intimidated his opponent a handful of times during this match as well as tried to dissect him—as if he were in biology class minus a scalpel—until Kiyomiya came back regardless of how many times the challenger made it a one-sided affair.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My favorite match of this event involved the legendary Keiji Muto who is continuing his retirement tour. Here, Muto had his third match in his retirement tour as he was part of a six-man tag team bout, teaming with Yoshiki Inamura and Naomichi Marufuji and taking on New Japan wrestlers Tomoaki Honma, Togi Makabe and Hiroshi Tanahashi. All six competitors gave their all in this event, especially Muto and his teammates. He now has two matches remaining come next year; his first match of 2023 will be on New Year’s Day as he takes on WWE wrestler Shinsuke Nakamura!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good luck wishes go out to Muto on his ongoing retirement tour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the match results from Tokyo…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;pre-show-match-kai-fujimura-defeated-taishi-ozawa-with-a-missile-dropkick&quot;&gt;Pre-show match: Kai Fujimura defeated Taishi Ozawa with a missile dropkick.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My score: 3/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-hajime-ohara-shuji-kondo--manabu-soya-defeated-alejandro-xtreme-tiger--shuhei-taniguchi&quot;&gt;Match #1: Hajime Ohara, Shuji Kondo &amp;amp; Manabu Soya defeated Alejandro, Xtreme Tiger &amp;amp; Shuhei Taniguchi.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like Kondo and Soya, Ohara is also a member of Kongo. While everyone else fought at ringside, Kondo hit Alejandro with a snap powerslam followed by the King Kong Lariat for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-dante-leon--jack-morris-defeated-yo-hey--daiki-inaba&quot;&gt;Match #2: Dante Leon &amp;amp; Jack Morris defeated Yo-Hey &amp;amp; Daiki Inaba.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After Inaba hit Morris with the Fireball Bomb (blue thunder) before Morris came back with a Bryan Danielson knee, both Leon and Yo-Hey booted each other and then kipped up in stereo before Yo-Hey hit Leon with a missile until Morris broke up the pin. Then, Leon hit Yo-Hey with what looked like a reverse 450 cutter followed by a top rope corkscrew senton for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-3-yasutaka-yano-chris-ridgeway--yoshinari-ogawa-defeated-super-crazy-eita--nosawa-rongai-by-disqualification&quot;&gt;Match #3: Yasutaka Yano, Chris Ridgeway &amp;amp; Yoshinari Ogawa defeated Super Crazy, Eita &amp;amp; Nosawa Rongai by disqualification.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ECW original Super Crazy is—like Eita and Rongai—a member of Perros del Mal de Japon; the three gave fans Perros del Mal merchandise to the fans as they headed to the ring. The Stinger members and Yano went after Super Crazy, Eita and Rongai seconds before the bell rang, and all six fought at ringside until Super Crazy and Yano fought back in the ring; during the ringside melee, Ogawa and Eita fought at the ramp. A trashcan and lid came into play courtesy of the Perros del Mal members until their opponents took control of it; the well known saying “If you play with fire, you will get burned” would also come into play as Ogawa hit Eita with the lid, busting him open. Also, during the match, Ridgeway fought Eita at the Japanese broadcast table, putting him in the ankle lock while draped on the barricade. The match ended with Ridgeway holding Eita in an ankle lock and then a sleeper until Rongai hit him with a trashcan, giving Ridgeway, Yano and Ogawa the DQ in. Post-match, Ogawa put Eita in the trashcan and hit him with the lid. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.25/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-4-hijo-del-dr-wagner-jr--hideki-suzuki-defeated-masa-kitamiya--masato-tanaka&quot;&gt;Match #4: Hijo del Dr. Wagner Jr. &amp;amp; Hideki Suzuki defeated Masa Kitamiya &amp;amp; Masato Tanaka.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hijo del Dr. Wagner Jr. wore an orange and black outfit with a pumpkin mask…and yes, I felt like I wanted to say “It’s the great pumpkin, Charlie Brown!” (LOL!) Towards the end, Hijo del Dr. Wagner Jr. hit Kitamiya and Tanaka—who were fighting Suzuki at ringside—with a tope con giro, then Suzuki fought Kitamiya back in the ring and hit him with a spear for two and then put him in the Prison Lock (a seated cloverleaf) until Tanaka broke up the hold. Then, Hijo del Dr. Wagner Jr. hit Kitamiya with a delayed sit out powerbomb for two, followed by the Wagner Driver for three. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-5-seiki-yoshioka--atsushi-kotoge-defeated-hi69--tadasuke-to-retain-the-ghc-junior-heavyweight-tag-team-championship&quot;&gt;Match #5: Seiki Yoshioka &amp;amp; Atsushi Kotoge defeated Hi69 &amp;amp; Tadasuke to retain the GHC Junior Heavyweight Tag Team Championship.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Early in the match, Tadasuke wiped out Kotoge with a charging clothesline before he and Hi69 hit him with a double torture rack slam until Yoshioka broke up the pin; Kotoge had—to quote Frank Turner—a “long long road to recovery” at ringside while Yoshioka’s left leg was worked on. Near the end, the Kongo members hit Kotoge—who was finally able to get back in action a minute or so prior—with a dropkick/sidewalk slam combo before Hi69 hit him with a shining wizard for two, a leg lariat for two, and a Michinoku driver for two; Kotoge blocked Hi69’s top rope splash before he and Yoshioka hit him with a roundhouse kick/air raid crash combo for the win. Post-match, Kongo members Hajime Ohara and Shuji Kondo came in and attacked the champions until a masked wrestler ran in and fought the two and Hi69 &amp;amp; Tadasuke out of the ring; the masked wrestler turned out to be Haoh, whom Tadasuke claimed that he ejected, until Haoh—now going by the name Amakusa—vowed to go after him. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-6-ninja-mack-defeated-hayata-by-referees-decision-to-become-the-new-ghc-junior-heavyweight-champion&quot;&gt;Match #6: Ninja Mack defeated Hayata by referee’s decision to become the new GHC Junior Heavyweight Champion.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hayata took control of the match after kicking away Mack’s Ninja Special, causing him to crash into the barricade before he came back in at nine. The match ended with Mack hitting Hayata with a Ninja Special turned into a sunset flip powerbomb off the apron; Hayata ended up with a left arm injury, and the referee stopped the match and declared Mack the new champion. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.25/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-7-masakatsu-funaki-defeated-kazushi-sakuraba-in-three-minutes-in-a-martial-arts-rules-match-to-retain-the-ghc-national-championship&quot;&gt;Match #7: Masakatsu Funaki defeated Kazushi Sakuraba in three minutes in a martial arts rules match to retain the GHC National Championship.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The only way to win was by knockout, submission or TKO. Funaki won by knockout after incapacitating Sakuraba with a guillotine. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-8-satoshi-kojima--takashi-sugiura-defeated-katsuhiko-nakajima--kenoh-to-retain-the-ghc-tag-team-championship&quot;&gt;Match #8: Satoshi Kojima &amp;amp; Takashi Sugiura defeated Katsuhiko Nakajima &amp;amp; Kenoh to retain the GHC Tag Team Championship.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kojima accidentally booted Sugiura instead of Nakajima, giving the Kongo members the upper hand; Nakajima kicked away Kojima’s Western Lariat and hit him with an open palm strike and a brainbuster for two until Sugiura hit him with an Olympic slam before Kojima won with the Western Lariat. After the match, Funky Express came into the ring and praised Kojima and Sugiura for defeating the strongest and dangerous teams before challenging them for the belts; the champions—especially Kojima who was out of breath—accepted the challenge, then the champions shook hands instead of giving each other a finger shake. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-9-yoshiki-inamura-naomichi-marufuji--keiji-muto-defeated-tomoaki-honma-togi-makabe--hiroshi-tanahashi&quot;&gt;Match #9: Yoshiki Inamura, Naomichi Marufuji &amp;amp; Keiji Muto defeated Tomoaki Honma, Togi Makabe &amp;amp; Hiroshi Tanahashi.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Honma and Makabe are members of Great Bash Heel. Muto had pictures of his wrestling career before his entrance to the ring. During the match, Muto put Tanahashi in a Figure Four until Makabe broke up the hold and then blocked the shining wizard before nailing a grounded dragon screw leg whip and a sling blade; Muto and Marufuji then hit Tanahashi with a shining wizard/ripcord knee combo for two, and then Muto hit him with another shining wizard until—behind the referee’s back—Makabe knocked Muto off the top rope with his chain. Near the end, Honma ended up with a bloody chest after he and Marufuji exchanged chops until Tanahashi hit Marufuji with a sling blade and Honma hit him with the Kokeshi headbutt until Inamura broke up the pin; then, Honma went for a middle rope Kokeshi headbutt until Marufuji countered it with a bicycle kick before Muto and Marufuji hit him with—respectively—a shining wizard and a shiranui for the win. Post-match, Inamura and Makabe went at it at ringside until referees separated the two until all six competitors showed respect to each other. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-kaito-kiyomiya-defeated-kazuyuki-fujita-to-retain-the-ghc-heavyweight-championship&quot;&gt;Main event: Kaito Kiyomiya defeated Kazuyuki Fujita to retain the GHC Heavyweight Championship.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fujita came to the ring wearing a mask that looked similar to Wild Boar’s mask. Kiyomiya’s legs were worked on during the match. Towards the end, Kiyomiya came back and hit Fujita with a top rope cannonball at ringside until Fujita came back with the Beast Bomb and a Randy Orton punt; Fujita then went for another Beast Bomb until Kiyomiya blocked it before winning with a Frankensteiner. After the match, Fujita shoved the referee down while claiming that one of his shoulders was up (even though both shoulders were still down while Fujita tried to kick out per se). Then, Timothy Thatcher—with Hideki Suzuki in tow—came into the ring and (after Suzuki thanked the fans for coming) claimed that he was undefeated in Pro Wrestling Noah before challenging Kiyomiya for the belt; Kiyomiya nodded, accepting the challenge. As Thatcher left, Kiyomiya thanked the fans for coming. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;crown-jewel&quot;&gt;Crown Jewel&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that the bonus is out of the way, it’s time to head to Mrsool Park in Riyadh, Saudi Araba for Crown Jewel!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only did this mark the eighth WWE premium live event held in Saudi Arabia, but it also marked the second time that Crown Jewel took place at the venue, back when it was the King Saud University Stadium before it was sponsored by Mrsool; the first Crown Jewel that took place at that venue was this month in 2018.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the card for this year’s Crown Jewel were two one-on-one matches that involved heavy hitters (and would probably receive either the “Clash of the Titans” or “Alien vs. Predator” treatment), four championship matches including one that was in the form of a Last Woman Standing match, an Extreme Rules rematch that was in the form of a steel cage match (after all hell broke loose in a strap match last month), and a six-man tag team bout.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-11-27/crown jewel.png&quot; alt=&quot;crown jewel&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This also included an appearance from Bray Wyatt who came into the ring and said that even though he comes from a prestigious wrestling family, he didn’t like making a monster of himself after giving in by wearing a mask and believing that he would be untouchable; Wyatt said that this led to people loving the idea of him instead of Wyatt himself (as well as saying that he too didn’t love himself), and then—after saying that he didn’t like the person that he was in the past—vowed to rewrite the ending of his story. Suddenly, Uncle Howdy—whom we’ve seen on SmackDown in Wyatt’s appearances for weeks—appeared on the screen and said that Wyatt will go too far, and end up giving in to his inner demons if he doesn’t take the mask off. This is indeed an interesting storyline involving Wyatt and Uncle Howdy ever since he returned in Philadelphia last month, and I’m curious to see more of this story even if it means making another appearance at the upcoming Survivor Series—besides select episodes of SmackDown and/or Raw—later this month.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aside from the Bray Wyatt/Uncle Howdy storyline, this was indeed a very good Crown Jewel from start to finish; not a single match ended up being below average in my point of view. This of course included a match that I was leery about when I first heard it before it ended up being not only my favorite match of Crown Jewel but a great main event as well.
That match I’m talking about was the highly anticipated championship bout between Roman Reigns, who defended the Undisputed WWE Universal Championship, and Logan Paul. My first thought about it was that it was going to be a short-lived cakewalk for the champion Reigns besides the fact that this was also Paul’s third match. By the time that this main event occurred, I was proven wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though this was Paul’s third match as I just noted, his performance in this championship bout was as good—well, probably even better—than the performance he had in his two matches at WrestleMania and Summer Slam this year. Paul—who revealed that he was trained by Shawn Michaels days prior to Crown Jewel—surprised everyone that doubted that he would throw the champion off his game, even with moments that had me unglued to my seat when I watched it on Peacock that afternoon. Despite Reigns retaining the championship (as well as help for both competitors that occurred as the match was winding down), Paul definitely exceeded the expectations of those that were unsure about how he was going to perform at Crown Jewel. Will he surprise us again just like he did in his three matches? The answer as of now is this well-known saying…only time will tell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the match results from Riyadh…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-brock-lesnar-defeated-bobby-lashley&quot;&gt;Match #1: Brock Lesnar defeated Bobby Lashley.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lashley blindsided Lesnar at ringside sending him into the steel stairs, and then hit him with a spear before the match began; Lesnar ended up with a wounded left knee due the sneak attack. As soon as both wrestlers got into the ring, Lashley hit Lesnar with a spear, and then as soon as the two were at ringside, he speared the “Beast” again but through the barricade this time. The two then came back in where Lashley hit a fourth spear for a near fall, and then went for the Hurt Lock until Lesnar—bad leg and all—sent him to Suplex City before hitting the F5 for a near fall. After blocking spear and F5 attempts, Lashley locked in the Hurt Lock, and by the time the referee was dropping Lesnar’s arm for the third time, Lesnar powered up, ran up the turnbuckles, and—while in the hold—pinned Lashley for the win. Post-match, Lashley put Lesnar in the Hurt Lock before storming off. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-dakota-kai--iyo-sky-defeated-asuka--alexa-bliss-to-become-the-new-wwe-womens-tag-team-champions&quot;&gt;Match #2: Dakota Kai &amp;amp; Iyo Sky defeated Asuka &amp;amp; Alexa Bliss to become the new WWE Women’s Tag Team Champions.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This match was made after Asuka and Alexa defeated Dakota and Iyo for the belts on the Halloween episode of Raw which also served as the go-home episode before Crown Jewel. Before the match, Alexa was surprised to see the Bray Wyatt moth appearing on the screen while she and Asuka were interviewed by Byron Saxton backstage. During the match, Asuka climbed to the top rope until Iyo dropkicked her, causing her to dangle from the top rope before Dakota knocked her off; Asuka’s right knee was worked on afterwards. Towards the end, Dakota hit Asuka with a running corner-to-corner boot for a near fall, then Asuka came back and tagged in Alexa; Alexa attempted to hit Dakota with the Twisted Bliss until—after a distraction from Iyo—it was blocked. Asuka went after Iyo at ringside until the referee intervened; then, behind the referee’s back, Alexa went for Twisted Bliss again until Nikki Cross (you read correctly, she’s no longer “almost a superhero”) came from the crowd and shoved her off the top rope before hitting her with a rope-assisted neckbreaker, leading to Dakota pinning Alexa for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-3-drew-mcintyre-defeated-karrion-kross-w-scarlett-in-a-steel-cage-match&quot;&gt;Match #3: Drew McIntyre defeated Karrion Kross (w/ Scarlett) in a steel cage match.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scarlett wore spikes around her eyes, looking like Pinhead from “Hellraiser.” Seconds before the bell rang, McIntyre—as soon as he and Kross were inside—closed the cage door before the outside referee would do so. After yanking Kross off the top rope while in a tree of woe, McIntyre went for the Claymore until Kross countered it with a Bryan Danielson knee (that was compared to the Claymore by Michael Cole and Wade Barrett for some reason) for a near fall. McIntyre came back including getting a two count after a jackknife pin until Kross put him in the Kross Jacket; McIntyre got out of the hold and put his opponent in a sleeper until Kross got out of it with the Doomsday Saito. Kross went for the Kross Hammer until McIntyre dodged it and hit him with the Future Shock, then went for the Claymore until Scarlett distracted him, leading to Kross putting him in another Kross Jacket.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Near the end, Kross attempted to climb out after striking McIntyre with the Kross Hammer until McIntyre recovered and superplexed him off the top of the cage. McIntyre then attempted to walk out of the cage until Scarlett sprayed him—as well as the outside referee—with pepper spray; Kross attempted to leave until his blinded opponent dragged him away from the door while he had him in an ankle lock. McIntyre took down Kross with the Glasgow Kiss followed by the Claymore, then Scarlett locked the door until McIntyre decided to climb out of it; Scarlett pulled Kross to the door until McIntyre landed on the floor first and won. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-4-dominik-mysterio-finn-bálor--damian-priest-w-rhea-ripley-defeated-the-oc&quot;&gt;Match #4: Dominik Mysterio, Finn Bálor &amp;amp; Damian Priest (w/ Rhea Ripley) defeated the OC.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rhea mocked Beth Phoenix by having the same hairstyle as hers. In stereo, AJ Styles hit Bálor with a superplex while Priest hit Karl Anderson with an electric chair and Luke Gallows hit Mysterio with the same maneuver. Then, Styles attempted to hit Bálor with the Phenomenal Forearm until Rhea lifted him up in an electric chair position and dropped him face first into the apron; this led to Bálor hitting Styles with a shotgun dropkick followed by the Coup de Grace for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(NOTE: Two nights later on Raw, the OC added the returning Mia Yim to the team in order to solve the “Rhea Ripley problem.”)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-5-braun-strowman-defeated-omos-omos-made-the-majority-of-this-match-one-sided&quot;&gt;Match #5: Braun Strowman defeated Omos. Omos made the majority of this match one-sided.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Strowman went for the Strowman Express until Omos blocked it with a body block. Omos then went for a chokebomb until Strowman blocked it before being sent into the corner; Omos then attempted to splash him in the corner, but missed, leading to Strowman winning with a running powerslam. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-6-the-usos-defeated-butch--ridge-holland-to-retain-the-undisputed-wwe-tag-team-championship&quot;&gt;Match #6: The Usos defeated Butch &amp;amp; Ridge Holland to retain the Undisputed WWE Tag Team Championship.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jey Uso’s right arm and wrist were taped because—according to Michael Cole—he suffered a possible broken wrist while on WWE’s European tour. Holland paid homage to Sheamus during the match, hitting Jey with 10 Beats of the Bodhran (until Jimmy Uso stopped him at nine) as well as hitting him with White Noise. Towards the end, Butch and Holland threw Jimmy into the crowd, then hit Jey with a roundhouse kick/Northern Grit combo until Jimmy sprinted back in and broke up the pin; the match then ended with the Usos winning with—from the top rope—a 1D to Butch. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-7-bianca-belair-defeated-bayley-in-a-last-woman-standing-match-to-retain-the-raw-womens-championship&quot;&gt;Match #7: Bianca Belair defeated Bayley in a Last Woman Standing match to retain the Raw Women’s Championship.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A kendo stick (that almost went into the crowd earlier), steel chairs, a ladder, steel stairs, an equipment case at the entryway, a golf cart, and a table came into play in this bout. During the match, Bayley kicked the steps into Bianca and trapped her behind the steps including covering her with the ladder until Bianca popped out at seven; Bayley then beat down her trapped opponent with a kendo stick until Bianca recovered at eight. Bianca chased Bayley up the ramp with the stick until Bayley hit her with the Bayley-To-Bayley on the stage; then, as soon as the two recovered, Bayley shoved an equipment case into Bianca, causing the “EST” to fall in until Bianca got out of the case at seven.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After going back and forth with the case and Bayley wore down Bianca with an arm-trapped crossface until Bianca got up at seven, Bayley drove a golf cart on the stage until the two fought on the top of the cart; Bianca got down and drove the cart back to the ringside area with Bayley on the rooftop. Bayley grabbed Bianca by the ponytail until Bianca yanked her off the rooftop and onto the table before putting her through the table with a powerbomb until Bayley got up at nine. The two then got back inside where Bayley attempted to hit Bianca with the Rose Plant on an open chair until Bianca countered with the KOD on the chair (that Bayley tried to move out of the way); Bianca then trapped Bayley inside the ladder and propped it under the bottom turnbuckle where Bayley was unable to get out of it and get up at ten. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-roman-reigns-w-paul-heyman-defeated-logan-paul-to-retain-the-undisputed-wwe-universal-championship&quot;&gt;Main event: Roman Reigns (w/ Paul Heyman) defeated Logan Paul to retain the Undisputed WWE Universal Championship.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Logan was on an elevated podium that lowered him to the stage as he posed to the fans before making his way to the ring. During the match, Logan hit Reigns with his own Superman Punch followed by a top rope crossbody and a standing moonsault for two; he then went for Sweet Chin Music until Reigns caught him and hit him with a Rock Bottom for a near fall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Logan dodged a Superman Punch while hitting Reigns with a body shot, then hit him with a right hook (“One Lucky Punch” as he called it) and then another Superman Punch for a near fall. Logan then took apart the Arabic announce table, took the cell phone from his “Impaulsive” cohosts Mike Majlak and George Janko, and—while recording it all on the cell phone—hit Reigns with a frog splash through the table! Then, the Usos came and fought Majlak and Janko into the ring until Logan’s brother Jake Paul appeared and took down the Usos while the action returned to the ring where Logan hit Reigns with another frog splash—with no cell phone this time—for a near fall. Then, Solo Sikoa appeared and Jake attempted to fight him until referees and officials separated the two; the Usos closed in on Jake until Logan dove onto them before Logan came back in and was met with a Superman Punch and a spear that gave Reigns the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(NOTE: Logan Paul revealed on social media that he is currently inactive due to injury; in the middle of the match, he suffered a torn meniscus and MCL, and potentially tore his ACL as well.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;icw-fight-club&quot;&gt;ICW Fight Club&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s now time to go to the United Kingdom for ICW Fight Club. This time, it’s not taking place in the Asylum in Glasgow, Scotland; this week’s episode actually took place at the Ironworks in Inverness, Scotland. ICW was on the road prior to Fear &amp;amp; Loathing XIV, holding shows in Inverness as well as Newcastle, England. It also marked one of the final episodes of ICW Fight Club taking place at the Ironworks because the venue is expected to be demolished; it also held MMA events including one where Chris Bungard had his first ever Scottish Hit Squad MMA fight in the venue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We learned that a tag team championship match was made for Fear &amp;amp; Loathing XIV. “Jackie Polo”, while talking about teaming with Aaron Echo and taking on Sha Samuels &amp;amp; Chris Bungard in this week’s main event, said that he cut a deal by putting K.O.E. in a match at F&amp;amp;L for the ICW Tag Team Championship against the Glasgow Grindhouse. K.O.E has been building their momentum ever since becoming members of “Polo Promotions” as well as picking up a win over Casino Brutale as we saw last week, and if Adam and Marcus King keep doing so, it will indeed help them on their road to tag team gold come F&amp;amp;L.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-11-27/icw_fight_club.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;icw fight club&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Four matches took place on this week’s episode of Fight Club. Out of the four matches, I enjoyed one match that saw a rivalry briefly renewed, and it was back when Dylan Thorn was a member of the Manifesto; fast forward to this week’s episode, Thorn—no longer a member of the infamous group—took on rising star Levi. Thorn showed that he was doing more than just asking for forgiveness; he showed the up-and-comer what he’s capable of in this very good bout. Levi, who wasn’t ready to show respect to Thorn as soon as the match began, also had a very good showing in this match. In the end, it was Thorn that came out on top.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the match results from Inverness…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-luke-kyro-defeated-theo-doros&quot;&gt;Match #1: Luke Kyro defeated Theo Doros.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kyro’s back was worked on in this match. Kyro came back and hit Doros with a slingshot spear for two, then went for the Kyroscope until Doros blocked it before being hit with a Codebreaker for another two. Doros sent Kyro into the corner and hit him with a snap DDT for two, then—after changing his mind about hitting him with the Fall From Olympus—wanted to send a message to Daz Black by hitting Kyro with the Curbstomp; unfortunately, Doros missed, leading to Kyro winning with the Kyroscope. After the match, Kyro—backstage—said that he was hosting an episode of “Vibes” with Mark Dallas as his guest; Kyro is doing this interview to find out why he’s not on the road to Fear &amp;amp; Loathing XIV. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-kez-evans-defeated-the-outlaw-stevie-james-in-a-non-title-match&quot;&gt;Match #2: Kez Evans defeated “The Outlaw” Stevie James in a non-title match.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;James ambushed Evans seconds before the bell rang, then fought the champion out of the ring and hit him with a tope suicida. During the match, Evans went for the Blood Clot Clutch until James backed him into a corner before hitting him with a Saito suplex for two; he then went for a reverse brainbuster until Evans came back with a one-armed spinebuster for two followed by a Garvin stomp. Towards the end, Evans brandished brass knuckles from one of his boots until James hit him with two superkicks and an Impaler DDT for a near fall, then attempted to use the knuckles as a weapon until Evans rolled him up, grabbed the tights, and pinned him for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-3-dylan-thorn-defeated-levi&quot;&gt;Match #3: Dylan Thorn defeated Levi.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As soon as the match began, Levi refused to give Thorn a fist bump. Levi blocked the Crown of Thorns before taking him down and hitting him with a shining wizard for two, then Thorn came back and hit him with a top rope blockbuster for two; Thorn then offered a fist bump to Levi again until Levi responded by putting him in an arm-trapped crossface.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thorn fought back and missed on another Crown of Thorns attempt before hitting Levi with a black hole slam for two, then Levi hit him with a cutter for two, and went for a top rope maneuver, but missed, allowing Thorn to win with the Crown of Thorns. After the match, Levi shoved Thorn who was helping him up, but then gave him a fist bump and hug before raising his arm. Then, Thorn said that he was looking forward to fighting ADM at F&amp;amp;L XIV and talked about his accomplishments while ADM sat and did nothing. Moxie Malone appeared, and Thorn—who was waiting for the rest of the Manifesto to appear—wanted her to tell ADM that he was going to end the Manifesto; Moxie crotched him from behind and said that Thorn will end nothing and will instead prove how much of a failure he is while ADM ends up being the last man standing. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4.25/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-jackie-polo--aaron-echo-defeated-sha-samuels--chris-bungard&quot;&gt;Main event: “Jackie Polo” &amp;amp; Aaron Echo defeated Sha Samuels &amp;amp; Chris Bungard.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All four men brawled before the match began, with Samuels going after “Polo” while Bungard went after Echo; Samuels hit “Polo” with a steel chair before the two fought on the stage at the entryway while Bungard fought Echo in the crowd. Then, Samuels attempted to hit “Polo” with the polo mallet—as if he were Triple H with a sledgehammer—until Mark Dallas appeared and stopped the brawl; he wanted the tag team main event to take place, and if the four continued to brawl, their F&amp;amp;L matches would end up being cancelled. All four followed Dallas’ orders with Samuels bringing “Polo” into the ring to kick off the bout. Towards the end, Bungard had “Polo” in an ankle lock; Echo broke up the hold, and attempted to have “Polo” pin Bungard until Samuels stopped him from doing so. Then, Samuels tagged in and went after “Polo” while Bungard and Echo fought at ringside once again; behind the referee’s back, “Polo” hit Samuels with a low blow followed by the mallet for the win. As “Polo” celebrated after the match, Echo and Bungard fought to the back. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;nxt&quot;&gt;NXT&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We now head to Orlando, Florida in the United States for an episode of NXT.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We learned on “The Grayson Waller Effect”, with Bron Breakker and Von Wagner as the guests for that show, that a match for the NXT Championship has been set for next week’s episode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This occurred after Wagner ran in last week and took down Breakker, after Breakker and Wes Lee took on Pretty Deadly, who has been waiting for who is up next to fight him for the belt. During the segment, Wagner said that he didn’t come to NXT to be popular like Breakker and was only on that brand for the title, and his accomplice says that Wagner is more powerful and dangerous than the champion. Breakker said that he had the honor to be with NXT veterans such as Johnny Gargano and Tommaso Ciampa and was in the same spot as past champions such as Seth Rollins and Kevin Owens, then Wagner unnerved him by saying that he didn’t step foot into NXT by showing that he was the next generation of a pro wrestling family like Breakker is. I’m definitely looking forward to seeing this championship match between the dominant rising star Breakker and the hard-hitting powerhouse Wagner next week; this makes me wonder if Apollo Crews, who was mentioned by the champion, will be next to go after that belt at NXT Deadline once Breakker vs. Wagner is in the rearview.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of which, did anyone catch Wagner say “Pete Dunne” instead of “Butch” during that segment? This makes me wonder if Butch is going back to his previous ring name Pete Dunne soon in the WWE…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Out of the seven matches that took place on this episode, there were two matches that became my favorites; one match involved two NXT UK alumni, and the other was a rematch for the NXT Women’s Tag Team Championship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The match with NXT UK vibes was between JD McDonagh and Axiom, and yes, I guess you can say that it was a Jordan Devlin/A-Kid rivalry that was renewed for this week only. McDonagh portrays a great heel competitor with a dark side, even when it comes to making everybody’s—including his own—pain his pleasure. Not only that, but Axiom—the former A-Kid of course—is doing very well with not just his superhero character but also his fighting ability as we have seen on both NXT and NXT UK including his best of three matches with Nathan Frazer. The end of the match was similar to how McDonagh defeated Axiom on an episode of NXT UK last year—weeks before they clashed again in a 30-minute Iron Man match—with McDonagh making one of Axiom’s legs bend awkwardly (as well as McDonagh’s way).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other match that I enjoyed was the rematch for the NXT Women’s Tag Team Championship between Kayden Carter &amp;amp; Katana Chance and Nikkita Lyons &amp;amp; Zoey Stark. Even though it wasn’t as good as their first encounter with the gold on the line (especially with one or two of Katana’s maneuvers getting the “didn’t get all of it” treatment), it was still good enough to be one of my favorite matches of this week’s episode. I wasn’t sure if we were going to see Kayden and Katana retain the belts once again or Nikkita and Zoey finally winning the gold, and I also wasn’t sure if Zoey was going to control her emotions during the match (which she did); in the end, it was the primer, Kayden &amp;amp; Katana defeating Nikkita &amp;amp; Zoey once again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, and in case you’re wondering, Alba Fyre attacked Jacy Jayne as promised; it occurred as Jacy, while on the cell phone with Mandy Rose, was getting ready to drive out of the shopping mall parking lot. We would then learn that there will be a last woman standing match, between Alba and Mandy, for the NXT Women’s Championship next week.
Next week aside, here are this week’s NXT results from Orlando…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-joe-gacy-w-rip-fowler-jagger-reid-and-ava-raine-defeated-cameron-grimes&quot;&gt;Match #1: Joe Gacy (w/ Rip Fowler, Jagger Reid and Ava Raine) defeated Cameron Grimes.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This match was made because Schism was proving that they weren’t done with Grimes just yet. Also, Ava Raine—the daughter of Dwayne “The Rock” Johnson—was revealed to be a newer member of Schism a couple weeks ago after we have seen someone in a red hoodie with a yellow mask (that looks like a cross between the “Have A Nice Day” smiling face and the Blink-182 logo where it has the eyes looking like X’s) for weeks. Near the end, Grimes knocked Reid off the apron, then Fowler distracted him until Gacy accidentally crashed into him, leading to Grimes hitting his opponent with a poison rana. Then, Gacy got out of the ring as Grimes went for the Cave In until Grimes hit him and the Dyad with a tope suicida; then, behind the referee’s back, Ava knocked Grimes off the top rope, leading to Gacy winning with the Upside-Down World. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-elektra-lopez-defeated-sol-ruca-in-three-minutes&quot;&gt;Match #2: Elektra Lopez defeated Sol Ruca in three minutes.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Elektra won with a chokebomb. &lt;strong&gt;No score.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-3-charlie-dempsey-defeated-andre-chase-w-duke-hudson-and-thea-hail-in-almost-three-minutes&quot;&gt;Match #3: Charlie Dempsey defeated Andre Chase (w/ Duke Hudson and Thea Hail) in almost three minutes.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dempsey put Chase in the Regal Stretch, and Hudson attempted to push the bottom rope to Chase until the referee stopped him. Then, despite how close Chase was to the bottom rope, Hudson took Thea’s rally towel and threw it in the ring; the referee saw the towel and declared Dempsey the winner. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 0.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-4-stacks-w-tony-dangelo-defeated-hank-walker-in-three-and-a-half-minutes&quot;&gt;Match #4: Stacks (w/ Tony D’Angelo) defeated Hank Walker in three and a half minutes.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Walker fought Stacks in a corner until Stacks thumbed him in the eye and rolled him up for two before winning with a curbstomp-like knee drop. &lt;strong&gt;No score.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-5-jd-mcdonagh-defeated-axiom-by-referees-decision&quot;&gt;Match #5: JD McDonagh defeated Axiom by referee’s decision.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Axiom’s right knee was worked on after McDonagh kicked the steel stairs into his legs at ringside. Axiom countered McDonagh’s moonsault with a triangle choke, and McDonagh powered up until Axiom hit him with a hurricanrana for two. He was then unable to hit the Golden Ratio due to his knee, and McDonagh went for the Devil Inside until Axiom countered with a sleeper; McDonagh got out of the hold and put Axiom in a grapevine while bending his right knee until Axiom screamed in pain and ended up being unable to get back on his feet, leading to the referee stopping the match and giving McDonagh the win. After the match, McDonagh bragged about severe strains such as one he claimed to have given Axiom, then dared anyone to get on his level and test him like Ilja Dragunov and Apollo Crews. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-6-damon-kemp-defeated-brutus-creed-w-julius-creed-and-ivy-nile-by-disqualification-the-match-had-a-five-minute-time-limit&quot;&gt;Match #6: Damon Kemp defeated Brutus Creed (w/ Julius Creed and Ivy Nile) by disqualification; the match had a five-minute time limit.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brutus got out of the ring and fought Kemp into the ring before the match. Kemp brought in a steel chair until Brutus swatted it out of his hands; Brutus then took the chair and hit Kemp with it, giving Kemp the DQ win. Brutus gave Kemp one more chair shot afterwards, then he, Julius and Ivy noticed that Indus Sher was watching from the stage. &lt;strong&gt;No score.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-kayden-carter--katana-chance-defeated-nikkita-lyons--zoey-stark-to-retain-the-nxt-tag-team-championship&quot;&gt;Main event: Kayden Carter &amp;amp; Katana Chance defeated Nikkita Lyons &amp;amp; Zoey Stark to retain the NXT Tag Team Championship.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After Zoey hit Katana with a half-and-half suplex (ala Oney Lorcan) and a grounded jumping heel kick for two, she charged her opponent until missing and almost hitting Nikkita; Nikkita then moved Zoey out of the way to take the bullet in the form of a double superkick, then Katana hit Zoey with a tornado DDT before she and Kayden won with a neckbreaker/450 combo. After the match, Nikkita and Zoey handed the belts to Kayden and Katana until all of the sudden, Zoey refused to let go of the belt and hit Nikkita with it; Zoey then chased the champions out of the ring and beat down Nikkita some more while yelling at her. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;nxt-lvl-up&quot;&gt;NXT: LVL UP&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Staying in Orlando, we wrap things up with an episode of NXT: LVL UP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s nothing much to say about this episode with the exception that (even though NXT: LVL UP is often 30 minutes long) I was expecting more in both tag team bouts—that opened and closed the episode—as well as the second match. Other than that, it was an alright episode; plus, there’s always next week and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the NXT: LVL UP results from Orlando…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-tatum-paxley--ivy-nile-defeated-jakara-jackson--lash-legend&quot;&gt;Match #1: Tatum Paxley &amp;amp; Ivy Nile defeated Jakara Jackson &amp;amp; Lash Legend.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After Tatum hit Lash with a crossbody from the apron, Jakara rolled up Ivy twice for back-to-back two counts until Ivy made her submit to the DCL. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-javier-bernal-defeated-ikemen-jiro&quot;&gt;Match #2: Javier Bernal defeated Ikemen Jiro.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bernal swatted away a handshake as the match began. Jiro put Bernal in a Tarantula (ala Yoshihiro Tajiri), and then went for the Ikemen Slash, but missed and it allowed Bernal to roll him up, grab the tights and pin him for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-edris-enofé-malik-blade--odyssey-jones-defeated-bronco-nima-lucien-price--xyon-quinn&quot;&gt;Main event: Edris Enofé, Malik Blade &amp;amp; Odyssey Jones defeated Bronco Nima, Lucien Price &amp;amp; Xyon Quinn.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After Jones hit Price with a bodyslam, Blade hit Price with a frog splash—from on top of Jones’ shoulders—for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;next-time&quot;&gt;Next time…&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My usual three shows and—as promised—a belated Progress recap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For my newsletters as well as any articles that are on the Wrestling With Johners website, the website is wrestlingwithjohners.com/articles&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For just my newsletters on the WWJ website, it is wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/pro-darin/&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading! Feel free to comment! I’ll see you next time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Photos shown in the newsletter are from Pro Wrestling Noah, WWE and ICW.)&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>pro-darin</name></author><category term="articles" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Issue 46 Shows of November 12-18, 2022</title><link href="/articles/Issue-46-Shows-of-November-12-18,-2022/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Issue 46 Shows of November 12-18, 2022" /><published>2022-11-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-11-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/Issue%2046%20Shows%20of%20November%2012-18,%202022</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/Issue-46-Shows-of-November-12-18,-2022/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png&quot; alt=&quot;pro darin&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;progress-chapter-142-the-deadly-viper-tour--codename-california-mountain-snake&quot;&gt;Progress Chapter 142: The Deadly Viper Tour – Codename: California Mountain Snake&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As promised, I’m kicking things off with a belated Progress recap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 142nd chapter of Progress took place on September 25 at the O2 Academy in Birmingham, England in the United Kingdom; it was the third event that was part of the Deadly Viper Tour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-11-27/deadly viper tour.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;deadly viper tour&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nine matches were on the card that day with the last four being championship matches; not only did we see the champions in action, but we also saw competitors either visiting (such as those from other companies such as wXw and AEW) or returning to Progress—along with a long-awaited rivalry in the form of a tag team bout—as you’ll see shortly in the results.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the matches that didn’t see any belts on the line, my favorite would have to go to the one-on-one bout between Shigehiro Irie and Gene Munny. We have seen Irie compete in Europe (including wXw in events such as the Ambition and 16 Carat Gold tournaments) besides his home country of Japan and were introduced to what he’s capable of, and he even showed it in his match with Munny. Munny also had a good showing, introducing his opponent to his serious side besides having fun moments with Irie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for the championship matches, one of the four title matches became my favorite match of this chapter; it was the Progress Atlas Championship match between Luke Jacobs and Big Damo. Believe it or not, each Atlas Championship match has been scorching hot as of late ever since the belt was brought back early this year. Not only did it show Jacobs looking to continue his run while going through each competitor that gave him a run for his money chapter after chapter, but it also involved another storyline where Damo wanted to win more gold after losing the Progress World Championship to Spike Trivet three chapters prior. It was indeed a very good battle between the two, and in the end, it was the “Beast of Belfast” that walked away with the gold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the match results from Birmingham…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-millie-mckenzie-defeated-laura-di-matteo&quot;&gt;Match #1: Millie McKenzie defeated Laura di Matteo.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was Millie’s first Progress match in over a year. Laura put Millie in the Veni Vidi Vici until Millie rolled her up for two, then Millie hit her with a spear for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-peter-tihanyi-defeated-alexander-roth-tom-thelwell-and-hari-singh-in-a-fatal-four-way-natural-progression-series-qualifier&quot;&gt;Match #2: Peter Tihanyi defeated Alexander Roth, Tom Thelwell and Hari Singh in a fatal four-way Natural Progression Series qualifier.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Singh had a drummer performing at the entryway before he came into the ring. Before the match started, Thelwell called his opponents “Muppets” that don’t want to dance with the “Manchurian Stallion”, and then said that the city of Birmingham isn’t nice to look at; then, as soon as the bell rang, Tihanyi, Roth and Singh went after him. After Tihanyi took down Roth and Singh and then hit Thelwell with a tope con giro, the wXw wrestler hit Singh with a Meteora and then hit him and Roth with a 450 for the win in this quick four-way dance. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-3-aussie-open-defeated-danny-black--maverick-mayhew&quot;&gt;Match #3: Aussie Open defeated Danny Black &amp;amp; Maverick Mayhew.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mark Davis and Kyle Fletcher ambushed ½ of CPF seconds before the match began. Earlier, Black and Mayhew dove at Aussie Open until Davis and Fletcher caught them and ram them into each other before running around both sides of the ring and rammed them again. The team of Black and Mayhew made comebacks afterwards, including Black hitting Fletcher with an assisted cutter (after Mayhew threw Black in a crucifix powerbomb position) for two, until Aussie Open hit Black with the Cariolis (a.k.a. the Fidget Spinner) for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-4-shigehiro-irie-defeated-gene-munny&quot;&gt;Match #4: Shigehiro Irie defeated Gene Munny.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Irie kicked away an Ainsley Lariat earlier, and then—while Munny was seated on the apron—hit him with a spear followed by a top rope splash. Munny came back and missed on another Ainsley Lariat attempt, then the two clotheslined each other until Irie took back the upper hand; then, Munny hit Irie with the Ainsley Lariat until Irie won with the Bowman Lariat. Both wrestlers bowed to each other afterwards. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-5-cdk-defeated-lykos-gym-kid-lykos-ii-bullied-a-cameraman-while-entering-the-ring-before-the-match&quot;&gt;Match #5: CDK defeated Lykos Gym. Kid Lykos II bullied a cameraman while entering the ring before the match.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, Chris Brookes and Masa Takanashi came into the ring with the Asia Dream Tag Team Championship belts. Early in the match, both Brookes and Kid Lykos shook hands until Brookes blocked his opponent’s eye poke attempt. Later, CDK fought Kid Lykos at ringside, whipping him hard into the chairs before Brookes hit him with a back suplex onto the chairs. Near the end, KL2 hit Brookes with a moonsault at ringside, and then he and KL double teamed on Takanashi before KL hit Brookes with a tope suicida while KL2 hit the other “Calamari Drunken King” with a standing shooting star press for two; CDK made a comeback, then won after hitting KL2 with the Mantis Bomb (savate kick/piledriver combo). After the match, Brookes thanked the fans for giving him and Takanashi a warm welcome. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.25/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-6-big-damo-defeated-luke-jacobs-to-become-the-new-progress-atlas-champion&quot;&gt;Match #6: Big Damo defeated Luke Jacobs to become the new Progress Atlas Champion.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Early in the match, Jacobs fought Damo at ringside and then hit him with a crossbody into the chairs. Then, Jacobs hit Damo with a superplex for one followed by the Burning Lariat for a near fall, and then went for a coast-to-coast maneuver until Damo booted it away and then hit him with a pop up chokebomb and an elbow drop for two. After Damo hit Jacobs with the Divide for a near fall, he hit him with a boot, Wasteland and senton before missing with the Belfast Blitz; Jacobs fought back until Damo came back and hit him with the Belfast Blitz for a near fall. Jacobs came back with a headbutt and a powerbomb for two, then hit him with the Burning Lariat for another near fall; Damo hit Jacobs with his own Burning Lariat before winning with the Belfast Blitz. After the match, Lykos Gym appeared and attacked Jacobs until the returning Ethan Allen ran in and he and Jacobs fought the two out of the ring. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-7-the-sunshine-machine-defeated-violence-is-forever-to-retain-the-progress-tag-team-championship&quot;&gt;Match #7: The Sunshine Machine defeated Violence Is Forever to retain the Progress Tag Team Championship.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the match, Chuck Mambo hit Kevin Ku with the Reef Break (Meteora) for a near fall, then he and TK Cooper hit him with a Gory bomb/cutter combo until Ku and Dominic Garrini fought back and hit Cooper with a Claymore/back suplex combo for two. The Sunshine Machine then came back and won after hitting Garrini with the Designated Driver. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.25/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-8-kanji-defeated-lana-austin-w-skye-smitson-and-la-taylor-to-retain-the-progress-womens-championship&quot;&gt;Match #8: Kanji defeated Lana Austin (w/ Skye Smitson and L.A. Taylor) to retain the Progress Women’s Championship.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lana had ring announcer Simon Miller wear her sunglasses before the match began, then Kanji teamed up with a young fan named Penny who was busting the guts of the Lana Austin Experience (especially Lana), “LANA SUCKS” sign and all. Also, seconds before the bell rang, Kanji blindsided L.A., sending her into Lana. During the match, Lana seated Kanji at ringside and teased charging at her before shoving her down to the floor. Kanji fought back and fought away Skye and L.A. at times, then Lana hit Kanji with the Roaring Elbow (discus elbow) for a near fall until Kanji put her in a triangle choke; Skye put Lana’s foot on the bottom rope until the referee caught her and sent her to the back. Behind the referee’s back, L.A. hit Kanji from ringside, leading to Lana hitting her with a powerbomb for two; Lana then went for a Randy Orton DDT until Kanji countered with a rollup for the win. After the match, Skye and L.A. came back in the ring with steel chairs until Millie McKenzie ran in and evened the odds before the Lana Austin Experience left. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-spike-trivet-w-bullit-defeated-man-like-dereiss-to-retain-the-progress-world-championship&quot;&gt;Main event: Spike Trivet (w/ Bullit) defeated Man Like Dereiss to retain the Progress World Championship.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bullit is of course the “crewman” that helped Trivet in the last chapter and is now his bodyguard. Bullit went after Dereiss early in the match, including when Trivet pretended to suffer a leg injury after “tripping.” Also, after Trivet hit Dereiss with the Birthright for a near fall, Dereiss shoved Trivet off the top rope and climbed up until Bullit hit the post, causing Dereiss to lose his balance, leading to Trivet hitting him with a Codebreaker for two. Trivet and Dereiss then fought out of the ring, and Trivet hit him with a Gotch piledriver on the stage at the entryway until—with help from fans—Dereiss came back in at nine. Dereiss fought back and even fought away Bullit, then hit Trivet with the Four Fiddy until Bullit pulled the referee out of the ring, allowing Trivet to hit the challenger with a low blow and the Madame Guillotine for a near fall. Trivet then elbowed the referee while fighting Dereiss in the corner, and then Bullit attempted to hit Dereiss with the championship belt until Dereiss dodged it and took down the bodyguard before Trivet hit him with a low blow and the title. Then, after Trivet realized that the referee was unconscious, Dereiss came back and attempted to hit Trivet with another Four Fiddy but missed; Bullit came back in and hit Dereiss with a chokeslam before Trivet pinned him for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;icw-fight-club&quot;&gt;ICW Fight Club&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Staying in the United Kingdom, we now go to the Ironworks in Inverness, Scotland for an episode of ICW Fight Club.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Luke Kyro hosted another episode of “Vibes” this week, with ICW owner and founder Mark Dallas as his guest. Dallas, while talking about bringing ICW to Inverness, announced that there would be a six-man ladder match at Fear &amp;amp; Loathing XIV; the winner of this match would become the #1 contender for the ICW Zero-G Championship, and the contender would go on to fight for that belt at Square Go! in 2023. Then, Levi came into the ring and asked to be in that ladder match, ditto Thatcher Wright; Dallas then decided to name two of the six participants—Kyro and Levi—before saying “See you later” to Wright and leaving, leading to Wright attacking the two ladder match participants with his Margaret Thatcher book. During my first year of watching ICW, I enjoyed the ladder match that took place at last year’s F&amp;amp;L; I sure hope that this year’s F&amp;amp;L ladder match will be as good as last year’s.
By the way, unlike poor Luke Kyro, I know what a “PlayStation One” is (or PlayStation as we simply called it back in my day), as well as Ridge Racer even though my first Ridge Racer game (for the PlayStation of course) was “R4: Ridge Racer Type 4” per se.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-11-27/molly vs rhio.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;icw fight night&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Three matches took place this week, and my favorite match of the episode goes to the opening bout that involved ICW’s women’s division that has been—according to Billy Kirkwood (and probably the Velvet Underground as well)—“white hot” as of late. In the opening match, Rhio fought Molly Spartan while wanting to take part of the women’s championship match at F&amp;amp;L. It was a great battle from start to finish that also included the action spilling out of the ring and into the audience (as well as the balcony). In the end, it was Molly who won and kept Rhio out of attempting to enter the women’s championship match. Molly has been on a roll even after winning the ICW Women’s Championship as she continues to build her momentum heading into F&amp;amp;L. Rhio has been showing what she’s capable of as well, and despite not entering that match at F&amp;amp;L, I still see her as championship material; I would definitely love to see her win championship belts in the near future even if it means near the end of 2022 or already stepping foot into 2023.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the match results from Inverness…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-molly-spartan-defeated-rhio-in-a-non-title-match-if-rhio-won-she-would-be-added-to-the-icw-womens-championship-match-at-fear--loathing-xiv&quot;&gt;Match #1: Molly Spartan defeated Rhio in a non-title match; if Rhio won, she would be added to the ICW Women’s Championship match at Fear &amp;amp; Loathing XIV.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After Rhio hit Molly with a tope suicida, Molly hit her with a back suplex onto the barricade, leading to the two fighting in the crowd; Rhio and Molly fought upstairs to the balcony and both attempted to throw each other out before heading back downstairs where Molly was whipped into the chairs and—heading back to the ringside area—Rhio was whipped into the stairs next to the stage. As soon as the two came back into the ring, Rhio worked on Molly’s left ankle. Molly fought back and hit Rhio—who was seated—with a crossbody from behind for two; Rhio came back with a rolling heel kick for two, and then—near the end—climbed to the top rope until Molly powerbombed her off before winning with a spear. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-craig-anthony--leyton-buzzard-defeated-ian-skinner--charlie-vyce&quot;&gt;Match #2: Craig Anthony &amp;amp; Leyton Buzzard defeated Ian Skinner &amp;amp; Charlie Vyce.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Skinner and Vyce are probably becoming a babyface tag team because they high fived a few fans while heading to the ring. Anthony and Buzzard tried not to focus on their championship match at F&amp;amp;L, and they argued at ringside early in the match until Skinner hit Buzzard with a tope suicida. Towards the end, after Anthony accidentally hit Buzzard with a superkick instead of Skinner, Thatcher Wright appeared until Buzzard shooed him away. Skinner and Vyce got the upper hand, and Skinner put Buzzard in an octopus until Buzzard powered out of it and put him in a Scorpion Death Lock; Anthony took down Vyce while Skinner—after shoving the Margaret Thatcher book away after Wright slid it to him—grabbed the ropes to break the hold. Then, Luke Kyro and Levi appeared and fought Wright to the back while Anthony powered out of Skinner’s octopus and hit him with a moonsault before Buzzard hit Skinner with the X Marks the Spot for the win. Both Anthony and Buzzard shook hands afterwards. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-bt-gunn-defeated-jack-jester&quot;&gt;Main event: BT Gunn defeated Jack Jester.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As soon as the match began, Jester brandished his large corkscrew and attempted to fight Gunn with it until Gunn fought back and disposed of the corkscrew. A kendo stick, a table, and a steel chair came into play as well (as did a fan’s chair which Gunn got rid of afterwards). Jester whipped Gunn hard into the barricade, causing a section of it to collapse until Gunn fought back early in the match. Then, after Jester hit Gunn with a Death Valley Driver through the table in a corner for two, the two fought out of the ring and into the crowd; Jester whipped Gunn into the exit doors until Gunn closed one of the doors on him, busting Jester open. Near the end, after Jester hit Gunn with the Last Laugh leg drop (apron leg drop) for a near fall, Gunn came back and hit Jester with a superkick which didn’t faze his opponent; Jester went after Gunn until Gunn hit him with a roundhouse kick for the win. After the match, Gunn took Jester’s corkscrew and attacked him with it until referees, Scott Reed and Mark Dallas separated the two; then, as Gunn was leaving, Jester—after saying that he’s no stranger to bleeding and getting scars everywhere—challenged him to a King of Insanity match at Fear &amp;amp; Loathing XIV. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;nxt&quot;&gt;NXT&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We now head to Orlando, Florida in the United States for an episode of NXT.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NXT Deadline is taking place on December 10, and there is a new type of match that Shawn Michaels announced that will take place; this type of match, the Iron Survivor Challenge, will be for both the men and women on NXT’s roster.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The rules for the Iron Survivor Challenge were then announced by Shawn Michaels. Five wrestlers compete in this match that will last for 25 minutes, with two beginning the bout; another wrestler comes in every five minutes until all five wrestlers are in the ring. The goal is to have the most falls—by pinfall, submission, or disqualification—at the end of 25 minutes; one fall equals one point, and one wrestler that is pinned, submitted, or disqualified will be in the penalty box for 90 seconds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the men, the winner of this match will become the #1 contender for the NXT Championship; for the women, the winner of this match will become the #1 contender for the NXT Women’s Championship. Despite looking forward to seeing if any championship matches will take place at Deadline, the idea of this match—the Iron Survivor Challenge—definitely caught my attention; I actually like the concept of this match since it looks like a cross between the Gauntlet Eliminator (or Progress’ Thunderbastard)—but with eliminations replaced with penalties—and the Iron Man match, and I’m pretty sure that the fans looking forward to Deadline come next month are chomping into bit after waiting to see it in person (and not just seeing how good it looks on paper) just like I am.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Putting aside the idea of jumping to December as if this were H.G. Wells’ “The Time Machine” or if I was Emmett “Doc” Brown and his time traveling DeLorean from the “Back To the Future” franchise, there were six matches that took place this week; three of them were indeed very good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One match was the opening bout between Bron Breakker and Von Wagner for the NXT Championship; this championship pitted—respectively—power against strength, and regardless of how many times Wagner attempted to overpower (pun intended) the champion as well as have his insurance policy in the form of Mr. Stone, it was Breakker that came out on top. It was indeed a great hard-hitting battle between the two that kicked off this week’s episode, and I’m pretty sure that Wagner isn’t done with his road to gold—with or without anybody in tow—in the WWE after seeing a good performance like this; as for Breakker, he is doing a great job on his second championship reign as usual.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another match was the closer, which was a Last Woman Standing match between Mandy Rose and Alba Fyre. Mandy flew solo after Alba attacked her Toxic Attraction colleagues Gigi Dolin and Jacy Jayne in the past two weeks, and it looked like that she was backed against the wall in the form of defending the NXT Women’s Championship against the former Kay Lee Ray in that bout. In the end, Mandy retained the belt courtesy of an NXT UK alum that’s now part of the white-and-gold roster. I expected Mandy to retain the title in this match in some shape and form (such as the return of Sonya Deville), and not in the form of someone who is now Alba’s rival. I also like Alba showing a more dangerous side in a match that’s not a run-in-the-mill one-on-one match but a match with a no-DQ stipulation such as the Last Woman Standing match.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-11-27/nxt.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;nxt&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The third match was my favorite match of the episode, and it was a one-on-one match between JD McDonagh and Apollo Crews. This match was made after the two wanted Bron Breakker’s attention while learning that Breakker was looking for another competitor to go after him for the NXT Championship. Not only did we see McDonagh attempting to pick apart his opponent—sinister side and all—just like he did with his past NXT UK rivals Ilja Dragunov and Axiom in the past weeks, but Crews continuing his run in the white-and-gold brand on one high note after another. In the end, it was the NXT veteran Crews who emerged as the winner. I’m not going to lie, but I’m glad to have predicted that Crews would become the next challenger from Breakker; I have no idea if it’s taking place on either a future episode of NXT or NXT Deadline, but we’ll have to wait and see.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that I’m done being self-centered and tooting my own horn, let’s take a look at the NXT results from Orlando…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-bron-breakker-defeated-von-wagner-w-mr-stone-to-retain-the-nxt-championship&quot;&gt;Match #1: Bron Breakker defeated Von Wagner (w/ Mr. Stone) to retain the NXT Championship.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As soon as the match began, Wagner threw Mr. Stone into Breakker as a distraction. He would work on Breakker’s left arm later on. After Wagner hit Breakker with a chokeslam on the bottom portion of the steel stairs for two, Breakker came back and went for a spear until Wagner caught him and hit him with a Death Valley Bomb for a near fall. Wagner then took his frustration out on Mr. Stone who tried to calm him down, and then attempted to hit Breakker—who was unable to lift him due to his left arm being worked on—with another Death Valley Bomb until Breakker blocked it and won with a spear. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4.25/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-indus-sher-defeated-george-cannon--jake-fingado-in-two-and-a-half-minutes&quot;&gt;Match #2: Indus Sher defeated George Cannon &amp;amp; Jake Fingado in two and a half minutes.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fingado, best known as Ariel Dominguez in the indies as well as select AEW appearances, made his second NXT appearance; his first was back in late 2020 where he worked as “Joey Pistachio” in a match against Cameron Grimes that lasted for seven seconds. Keeping the long story short, the reunited team of Veer Mahaan and Sanga won after hitting Fingado with a sidewalk slam/middle rope elbow drop combo. After the match, Indus Sher said that they respect the Creed Brothers as do the fans, but don’t appreciate the disrespect they receive; they then vowed to destroy the Creed Brothers just like they destroy anyone that disrespects them. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 0.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-3-apollo-crews-defeated-jd-mcdonagh&quot;&gt;Match #3: Apollo Crews defeated JD McDonagh.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the match, McDonagh attempted to boot Crews from the apron until Crews caught him and hit him with a sidewalk slam on the announce table. McDonagh came back including putting him in a sleeper, and then went for the Devil Inside until Crews kneed him away; Crews then blocked the Devil Inside attempt again and went for a powerbomb until McDonagh rolled him up for two. McDonagh continued to mount his comeback, and then went for a moonsault, but missed; this allowed Crews to win with a pop up uranage. After the match, Bron Breakker appeared at the entryway and looked at Crews. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-4-the-dyad-w-joe-gacy-and-ava-raine-defeated-josh-briggs--brooks-jensen-w-fallon-henley-in-four-minutes&quot;&gt;Match #4: The Dyad (w/ Joe Gacy and Ava Raine) defeated Josh Briggs &amp;amp; Brooks Jensen (w/ Fallon Henley) in four minutes.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the match, Jensen went after Rip Fowler and Jagger Reid at ringside until Ava blocked Jensen’s path, leading to Fowler hitting him with a tope suicida. Towards the end, Kiana James appeared and went after Fallon until Fallon slapped her into Jensen; Briggs saw this awkward moment occur until the Dyad hit him with a double Codebreaker for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-5-indi-hartwell-defeated-tatum-paxley-w-ivy-nile-in-almost-four-minutes&quot;&gt;Match #5: Indi Hartwell defeated Tatum Paxley (w/ Ivy Nile) in almost four minutes.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After Tatum hit Indi with a standing moonsault, Indi ripped off her mask and stomped her before throwing the mask to Ivy and then hitting Tatum with a blindsiding forearm for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-mandy-rose-defeated-alba-fyre-in-a-last-woman-standing-match-to-retain-the-nxt-womens-championship&quot;&gt;Main event: Mandy Rose defeated Alba Fyre in a Last Woman Standing match to retain the NXT Women’s Championship.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A steel chair, a metal rod from a toolbox, a trashcan and a ladder came into play in this match. Alba worked on Mandy’s right knee early in the match after blocking the Kiss By the Rose attempt with a steel chair and then used the rod as part of a half crab. Mandy came back and fought at ringside with a ladder until Alba got up at eight and slammed Mandy onto a trashcan; Mandy got up at nine, and the two fought close to the crowd until she shoved Alba off the top of a barricade and face first onto the steel stairs before Alba got up at eighth. Alba hit Mandy with a superkick and then hit her with the Fyre Bomb on the apron, then placed her on the announce table and climbed up the ladder. All of the sudden, Isla Dawn appeared on the ladder and spat a smoky mist in Alba’s face before shoving her off and through the table; Mandy recovered at nine while Alba was unable to get up at ten. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;nxt-lvl-up&quot;&gt;NXT: LVL UP&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Staying in Orlando, we wrap things up with an episode of NXT: LVL UP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Again, I expected more like on the last episode, even though I saw that two matches were slightly better than the other. Not only did we see a fair showing from Thea Hail and Dante Chen, but also from up and comers Dani Palmer and Oba Femi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No worries, I’m not giving up on watching the show; I always keep my fingers crossed when it comes to see more action as well as what the wrestlers have in store.
Okay, now that I’m done being “Saturday Night Live” character Debbie Downer, let’s take a look at the NXT: LVL UP results from Orlando…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-thea-hail-w-andre-chase-and-duke-hudson-defeated-dani-palmer-in-almost-five-minutes&quot;&gt;Match #1: Thea Hail (w/ Andre Chase and Duke Hudson) defeated Dani Palmer in almost five minutes.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was Dani’s debut; she shook Chase and Hudson’s hands as soon as the match began, and then shook Thea’s hand later on. Thea won with a neckbreaker-like faceplant. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-dante-chen-defeated-oba-femi&quot;&gt;Match #2: Dante Chen defeated Oba Femi.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was Femi’s debut. After Chen chopped Femi down for two, he won with a running double chop. My score: 1.5/5
Main event: Stacks defeated Oro Mensah. Tony D’Angelo joined Sudu Shah and Byron Saxton—who appears to be turning heel (even though he’s a babyface backstage interviewer on Raw per se)—on commentary. Mensah’s left arm was worked on. Near the end, D’Angelo distracted Mensah, and then—behind the referee’s back—hit him with his crutch, leading to Stacks winning with a curbstomp-like knee drop. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;next-time&quot;&gt;Next time…&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once again, my usual three shows and a belated Progress recap or two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For my newsletters as well as any articles that are on the Wrestling With Johners website, the website is wrestlingwithjohners.com/articles&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For just my newsletters on the WWJ website, it is wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/pro-darin/&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading! Feel free to comment! I’ll see you next time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, have a Happy Thanksgiving!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Photos shown in the newsletter are from WWE, Progress and ICW.)&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>pro-darin</name></author><category term="articles" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Samy Zayn Wins War Games for the Bloodline | WWE Survivor Series War Games 2022 #shorts</title><link href="/rope-break/videos/Samy-Zayn-Wins-War-Games-for-the-Bloodline-WWE-Survivor-Series-War-Games-2022-shorts/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Samy Zayn Wins War Games for the Bloodline | WWE Survivor Series War Games 2022 #shorts" /><published>2022-11-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-11-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/rope-break/videos/Samy%20Zayn%20Wins%20War%20Games%20for%20the%20Bloodline%20%20WWE%20Survivor%20Series%20War%20Games%202022%20%20shorts</id><content type="html" xml:base="/rope-break/videos/Samy-Zayn-Wins-War-Games-for-the-Bloodline-WWE-Survivor-Series-War-Games-2022-shorts/"></content><author><name>rope-break</name></author><category term="rope-break" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Samy Zayn Wins War Games for the Bloodline | WWE Survivor Series War Games 2022</title><link href="/rope-break/videos/Samy-Zayn-Wins-War-Games-for-the-Bloodline-WWE-Survivor-Series-War-Games-2022/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Samy Zayn Wins War Games for the Bloodline | WWE Survivor Series War Games 2022" /><published>2022-11-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-11-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/rope-break/videos/Samy%20Zayn%20Wins%20War%20Games%20for%20the%20Bloodline%20%20WWE%20Survivor%20Series%20War%20Games%202022</id><content type="html" xml:base="/rope-break/videos/Samy-Zayn-Wins-War-Games-for-the-Bloodline-WWE-Survivor-Series-War-Games-2022/"></content><author><name>rope-break</name></author><category term="rope-break" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Survivor Series Picks 2022</title><link href="/bob-culture/Survivor-Series-Picks-2022/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Survivor Series Picks 2022" /><published>2022-11-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-11-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/bob-culture/Survivor%20Series%20Picks%202022</id><content type="html" xml:base="/bob-culture/Survivor-Series-Picks-2022/"></content><author><name>bob-culture</name></author><category term="bob-culture" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Survivor Series Picks 2022</title><link href="/bob-culture/videos/Survivor-Series-Picks-2022/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Survivor Series Picks 2022" /><published>2022-11-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-11-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/bob-culture/videos/Survivor%20Series%20Picks%202022</id><content type="html" xml:base="/bob-culture/videos/Survivor-Series-Picks-2022/"></content><author><name>bob-culture</name></author><category term="bob-culture" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Great Solo Performances in Survivor Series History</title><link href="/articles/Great-Solo-Performances-in-Survivor-Series-History/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Great Solo Performances in Survivor Series History" /><published>2022-11-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-11-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/Great%20Solo%20Performances%20in%20Survivor%20Series%20History</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/Great-Solo-Performances-in-Survivor-Series-History/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;great-solo-performances-in-survivor-series-history&quot;&gt;Great Solo Performances in Survivor Series History&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Survivor Series is one of the longest-standing traditions in WWE history. Every November team warfare enters our homes and the results have, usually, been great. The team dynamic is one that WWE doesn’t explore often and we are given some interesting pairings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Survivor Series has always been more about the team game than anything. The importance of working together is always highlighted going into the show but that doesn’t mean a solo performance can’t shine above.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There have been a few times throughout the history of the Survivor Series when a man/woman rises above the rest. There have been times when a wrestler puts on such a great performance that they rise above the rest and become stars. Below we will take a look at some of these instances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-undertaker-1990&quot;&gt;The Undertaker (1990)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Million Dollar Man promised the world that he had a huge surprise for the Survivor Series. He delivered in that aspect when he announced The Undertaker as his final teammate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The audience was aghast when the Deadman made his way through the curtain. His appearance and demeanor were terrifying and unlike anything we had seen before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When he reached the ring, The Undertaker proceeded to carve through his opponents. He eliminated Koko B.Ware and Dusty Rhodes with ease and proved to be too much of a match for others. Only when he got himself counted out did he leave the match. It was an amazing debut and a performance that set the tone for The Undertaker for the next 30 years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;dolph-ziggler-2014&quot;&gt;Dolph Ziggler (2014)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Showoff has always been one of the best workers in WWE. His skill set matched with his amazing selling ability has kept him relevant in the company over the years. This ability made him one of the most over wrestlers on the roster in 2014. A year when his star-making performance had him on top of the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main event of Survivor Series in 2014 had some high stakes attached to it. The loser of the contest, whether it be the Authority or Cena’s partners, would be fired.  It was a great way to add some much need suspense to the match, which was heightened when Cena was eliminated early on in the match. This left Ziggler alone against the three remaining members of Team Authority.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These odds seemed to be insurmountable but Ziggler pulled himself together and put in the performance of a lifetime. He disposed of Kane and Luke Harper on his way to getting the pinfall over Seth Rollins. It was an astonishing finish and one that will go down as a masterful performance by Ziggler.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;roman-reigns-2013&quot;&gt;Roman Reigns (2013)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before the hatred spilled out of every corner of the arena, Roman was a popular member of the Shield. It was still known that he had the company’s backing and was the one from the group poised for bigger things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We got to see this backing start to form when we hit Survivor Series 2013. The heel team of The Shield and Real Americans took on Cody Rhodes, Goldust, and The Usos. It was a great opener to the PPV and it showcased a lot of the younger talent on the roster, namely Roman Reigns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reigns were already earmarked for greatness, but it was here we saw this firsthand. Reigns plowed his way through 4 out of the 5 members of the opposing team. It was a dominance not rarely seen and established him as a force to be reckoned with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;keith-lee-2019&quot;&gt;Keith Lee (2019)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2019 the brand warfare that was Survivor Series was taken to a new level. The PPV had always included Raw v Smackdown, but this was the first year that NXT was added to the event. This made for an interesting dynamic involving three teams for every match. It also allowed Keith Lee to burst onto the scene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lee had been great in NXT, but it was time he took his talents to the main roster. He looked like a beast during this match. His size and athleticism astounded the crowd and impressed all who were watching. This was the first time he was exposed to a national audience and he didn’t disappoint.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lee was eventually eliminated by Roman Reigns, but their few-minute showdown showed Lee was destined for greater things. He hung with Reigns and had the world believing that he might go over The Big Dog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;randy-orton-2004&quot;&gt;Randy Orton (2004)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Randy Orton is the most prolific performer in the history of the Survivor Series. He has been the surviving competitor so often that an entire list can be made of his triumphs. With that being said his 2004 performance was one of his best.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was one of the few times that Orton was a babyface in his early career. He had been, recently, booted from Evolution, and banded together with Benoit, Jericho and Maven to take on HHH’s group at the Survivor Series.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Orton was fantastic during the match.  His, and Hunter’s team, went toe to toe for most of the match until nearing the end. After Jericho had been eliminated Orton was left to fend off both Edge and Triple H. For anyone else, this would have been a death sentence but The Viper was able to summon his courage and cut through both men, en route to winning the match. It was an all-time great performance from Randy Orton.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>dan-sinasac</name></author><category term="articles" /><summary type="html">Great Solo Performances in Survivor Series History The Survivor Series is one of the longest-standing traditions in WWE history. Every November team warfare enters our homes and the results have, usually, been great. The team dynamic is one that WWE doesn’t explore often and we are given some interesting pairings.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Survivor Series Championship Matches</title><link href="/articles/Survivor-Series-Championship-Matches/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Survivor Series Championship Matches" /><published>2022-11-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-11-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/Survivor%20Series%20Championship%20Matches</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/Survivor-Series-Championship-Matches/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;survivor-series-championship-matches&quot;&gt;Survivor Series Championship Matches&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The American Thanksgiving tradition of the Survivor Series has been a staple of WWE programming for decades. Compiling teams of 4/5 wrestlers, teams go to war with each other to establish their dominance over the company. It was a great idea and one that has continued to this day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The concept of the Survivor Series has generally remained the same. The importance of team warfare is always the driving force behind the PPV, but that doesn’t mean the show was a one-trick pony.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Survivor Series has been the site of some fantastic championship matches. Matches that have stolen the show and presented us with a well-rounded night of wrestling. Let’s take a look at some of these great matches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;bret-hart-v-shawn-michaels-wwe-championship-survivor-series-1992&quot;&gt;Bret Hart v Shawn Michaels (WWE Championship; Survivor Series 1992)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5 years before their controversial championship match, HBK and Bret Hart engaged in an underrated Survivor Series classic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hart and Michaels were still young in their singles careers, but that didn’t stop them from putting on a clinic. Their technical skill meshed well together and they put on a fresh match. Gone were the lumbering main events of old and in their place a younger, faster more exciting product was presented.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This match was merely a precursor to their later feud, but it still was an outstanding addition to the Survivor Series.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;triple-h-v-rvd-v-hbk-v-kane-v-booker-t-v-chris-jericho-elimination-chamber-match-for-the-world-heavyweight-championship-survivor-series-2002&quot;&gt;Triple H v RVD v HBK v Kane v Booker T v Chris Jericho (Elimination Chamber Match for the World Heavyweight Championship; Survivor Series 2002)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Elimination Chamber was perfect for the Survivor Series. The concept of survival was heavily attached to the contest and with the A-List lineup, it was a near guarantee that it was going to be awesome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The match didn’t fail to deliver on its promise. It was violent and innovative. It was unlike anyone in WWE had seen and it provided new visuals and spots. Specifically, RVD pulling off the frog splash from the top of the pod was a sight to see.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was also the best way to have HBK win the title. Seeing him overcome Triple H on way to winning the match was the perfect ending to HBK’s return story arc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;trish-stratus-v-victoria-street-fight-for-the-wwe-womens-championship-survivor-series-2002&quot;&gt;Trish Stratus v Victoria (Street Fight for the WWE Women’s Championship; Survivor Series 2002)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This match was a pioneer for the Women’s Revolution. Long before Becky Lynch, Sasha Banks, and Charlotte were putting on great gimmick matches, we had this great hardcore match. At the time women’s matches were subjugated to bra’ and panties stipulations. It was an insult and a move that made women’s wrestling hard to take seriously. This match changed all that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Victoria and Trish flourished under the hardcore stip.  They were creative with the spots and the level of violence surprised many. It showed that women’s wrestling was just as viable as men’s and should be taken seriously.  A great job by both women on that night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;bret-hart-v-diesel--wwe-championship-match-survivor-series-1995&quot;&gt;Bret Hart v Diesel ( WWE Championship Match; Survivor Series 1995)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The year-long reign of Diesel was not exactly a success. His match quality was sub-par and the ratings were low. Luckily, he was able to turn in a great WWE Championship match on his way out of the main event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He and Bret put on the perfect David v Goliath story. Bret spent his time trying to wrestle the big man down while Diesel relied on his brute strength. These styles meshed very well and helped to tell a compelling story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The match was made even better by the great finish. Bret surprised Big Daddy Cool with a small package, winning the championship. This enraged the big man and he proceeded to give Bret a brutal post-match beatdown. It added another layer to the match and was a great way to turn Diesel heel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;bret-hart-v-shawn-michales--wwe-championship-survivor-series-1997&quot;&gt;Bret Hart v Shawn Michales ( WWE Championship; Survivor Series 1997)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was the most infamous match in Survivor Series, or WWE as a whole, history. The story surrounding the match and its finish has been well documented so there is no need to rehash it here. What isn’t talked about as much is the fact that both men put on one hell of a wrestling match.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It gets lost in the shuffle, but Bret and Shawn were fantastic on that night. Their talents were on full display. The technical skill was there but the intensity behind it was turned up to 11. Their real-life, and kayfabe hatred, was woven into the match beautifully and added that extra something to the contest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-miz-v-sami-zayn-intercontinental-championship-survivor-series-2016&quot;&gt;The Miz v Sami Zayn (Intercontinental Championship; Survivor Series 2016)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Miz and Sami Zayn were two of the WWE mid-cards best heading into this night. They were on separate brands but that didn’t stop them from putting on a great 15-minute match.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Miz is your prototypical WWE wrestler. His style is more methodical than most and doesn’t involve the eye-dropping moves of others, but that isn’t a detriment. This work rate matched perfectly with the plucky underdog of Sami Zayn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was the classic ground the faster wrestler style of match. Boring to some sure, but when you have world-class talents pulling it off it becomes engaging television. Couple that with a heel-heat-inducing finish for The Miz and you have a great IC title match.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;batista-v-the-undertaker--hell-in-a-cell-for-the-world-heavyweight-championship-survivor-series-2007&quot;&gt;Batista v The Undertaker ( Hell In A Cell for the World Heavyweight Championship; Survivor Series 2007)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The feud between Batista and The Undertaker was one of the best in 2007. Both hosses lock horns at Wrestlemania and other various shows throughout the year. Each match got better as they grew comfortable with one another, leading to their vicious contest at the Survivor Series.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was the perfect ending point for their feud. Both men used every weapon imaginable as they tore each other apart. It was the best way to tell a Hell in a Cell match and these were the best men to tell it. They had the history and physicality necessary to put on a great contest inside the cell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ending, with Edge costing The Undertaker the match, was a bit overbooked but it can be forgiven considering the 20 minutes that preceded it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;cm-punk-v-alberto-del-rio--wwe-championship-match-survivor-series-2011&quot;&gt;CM Punk v Alberto Del Rio ( WWE Championship Match; Survivor Series 2011)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Summer of Punk was leading to this match. CM had built himself into a megastar and his quest to finally become, the undisputed, WWE Champion culminated at Survivor Series in 2011.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Del Rio was a bit of a sacrificial lamb for this match but that doesn’t mean he was useless. His submission style of working matched well with Punk.  It allowed for both men to put on a more grounded, submission style of match. The realism with which they pulled this off was great and helped to give us a big match feel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It also didn’t hurt to have Howard Finkel come out to announce Punk’s entrance. It was a great throwback and the perfect way to start the match.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;john-cena-v-triple-h-v-shawn-michaels-triple-threat-match-for-the-wwe-championship-survivor-series-2009&quot;&gt;John Cena v Triple H v Shawn Michaels (Triple Threat Match for the WWE Championship; Survivor Series 2009)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes a match needs little build-up to garner any excitement. This was one of these matches. Triple H, HBK, and Cena had already built a long and storied history among one another and they were all main-event players. Add to that the fact that D-X was a tag team, and you have one drama-filled match.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes, matches only need to be fun, and that’s what this was. It started with HBK superkicking HHH at the match’s onset. It was a great way to set the tone for the rest of the match. There were no friends as all three men did their best to put the other one away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The end was never in doubt. Cena was going to walk away the champ but that doesn’t mean it wasn’t a highly entertaining championship match.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;mizdow-v-the-usos-v-goldust--stardust-v-los-matadores-fatal-4-way-match-for-the-wwe-tag-team-championships-survivor-series-2014&quot;&gt;Mizdow v The Uso’s v Goldust &amp;amp; Stardust v Los Matadores (Fatal 4-Way Match for the WWE Tag Team Championships; Survivor Series 2014)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why WWE couldn’t ever figure out how to use Damien Sandow properly is beyond any of us. At this point in time he was one of the most over figures on the roster. Which made this match so damn entertaining.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All four teams were great in their own right. They put on a great opener in 2014. They were given plenty of time and the fast-paced nature of the match had everyone eating out of the performers hand. It was a great showing from all 8 men.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All being said, this was Sandow’s night. The crowd ate up everything he did and the eruption was deafening when he got the pin for his team. This alone makes this a match worth watching.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>dan-sinasac</name></author><category term="articles" /><summary type="html">Survivor Series Championship Matches</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">WWE Goldberg Security</title><link href="/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/WWE-Goldberg-Security/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="WWE Goldberg Security" /><published>2022-11-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-11-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/WWE%20Goldberg%20Security</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/WWE-Goldberg-Security/"></content><author><name>jofo-in-the-ring</name></author><category term="jofo-in-the-ring" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ecuador 1 Paises Bajos 1 | FIFA Copa del Mundo Qatar 2022 | Resumen y Analisis</title><link href="/rope-break/videos/Ecuador-1-Paises-Bajos-1-FIFA-Copa-del-Mundo-Qatar-2022-Resumen-y-Analisis/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ecuador 1 Paises Bajos 1 | FIFA Copa del Mundo Qatar 2022 | Resumen y Analisis" /><published>2022-11-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-11-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/rope-break/videos/Ecuador%201%20Paises%20Bajos%201%20%20FIFA%20Copa%20del%20Mundo%20Qatar%202022%20%20Resumen%20y%20Analisis</id><content type="html" xml:base="/rope-break/videos/Ecuador-1-Paises-Bajos-1-FIFA-Copa-del-Mundo-Qatar-2022-Resumen-y-Analisis/"></content><author><name>rope-break</name></author><category term="rope-break" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>