<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-01-09T09:53:30+00:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Wrestling With Johners</title><subtitle>Pro Wrestling podcast with news, reviews and debate from WWE, NXT, NXT:UK, AEW, NJPW, Indy Wrestling and so much more. Listen to Wrestling With Johners on Apple Podcasts, Google Podcasts, Spotify, Podbean, Podcast Addict, Castbox, YouTube or wherever you get your podcasts.</subtitle><author><name>John Scott</name></author><entry><title type="html">The Time Splitters (Alex Shelley &amp;amp; Kushida) to reunite in NXT</title><link href="/news/Alex-Shelly-to-team-with-Kushida-in-NXT/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Time Splitters (Alex Shelley &amp; Kushida) to reunite in NXT " /><published>2020-01-09T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-09T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/news/Alex%20Shelly%20to%20team%20with%20Kushida%20in%20NXT</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/Alex-Shelly-to-team-with-Kushida-in-NXT/">&lt;p&gt;The Time Splitters are reuniting in NXT for the 2020 Dusty Rhodes Tag Team Classic!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mauro Ranallo announced during last night’s show that Alex Shelley will team with Kushida next week against The Grizzled Young Veterans in the first round of the tag team tournament.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-09/shelley.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;alex shelly and kushida&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Time Splitters were an active team from 2012-2015 and last competed together in 2016.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alex Shelley is most famously known for his time in TNA/Impact Wrestling as one half of the Motor City Machine Guns with Chris Sabin. He recently guest coached at the WWE Performance Centre, leading many to speculate he’d team with Kushida in the tourney, but Shelley attempted to downplay this last night on Twitter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Everybody seems to think Kushi needs me,” he wrote. “Kushi and I, and The Bucks, and Forever Hooligans, and ReDragon, helped change [NJPW]’s jr. tag division. But really, he’s going to be awesome with any partner.”&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html">The Time Splitters are reuniting in NXT for the 2020 Dusty Rhodes Tag Team Classic!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Mercedes Martinez signs with WWE</title><link href="/news/Mercadez-Martinez/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mercedes Martinez signs with WWE" /><published>2020-01-08T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-08T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/news/Mercadez%20Martinez</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/Mercadez-Martinez/">&lt;p&gt;It is being reported that popular Indy wrestler and current IWS Champion Mercedes Martinez has signed with WWE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;39 year old Martinez has performed inside of a WWE ring in the past. Including, appearances in the Mae Young Classic and on NXT TV.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-08/martinez.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;mercedes martinez&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Martinez was also a surprise entrant in AEW’s women’s pre-show Casino Battle Royal, at their ALL OUT PPV in August 2019.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is expected that Mercedes Martinez will report to the Performance Centre in Orlando within the next month, and that her IWS championship will be vacated and put up for grabs in a tournament at their next big show in February.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html">It is being reported that popular Indy wrestler and current IWS Champion Mercedes Martinez has signed with WWE.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">WWE Champion Brock Lesnar to enter the Royal Rumble 2020 at #1</title><link href="/news/WWE-Champion-Brock-Lesnar-to-enter-the-Royal-Rumble/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="WWE Champion Brock Lesnar to enter the Royal Rumble 2020 at #1" /><published>2020-01-07T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/news/WWE%20Champion%20Brock%20Lesnar%20to%20enter%20the%20Royal%20Rumble</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/WWE-Champion-Brock-Lesnar-to-enter-the-Royal-Rumble/">&lt;p&gt;The advocate for current WWE Champion Brock Lesnar, Paul Heyman announced on last night’s RAW (6th Jan 20) that ‘The Beast’ will be a participant in this year’s Royal Rumble match.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-07/lesnar.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;brock lesnar on raw&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a particularly unusual situation for any WWE or Universal Champion to be a part of the Rumble match itself. As the winner of the Rumble match would usually go on to face either the WWE or Universal Champion at ‘The Showcase of the Immortals’ WrestleMania.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This huge announcement became even more unprecedented with Heyman declaring in front of the live crowd on RAW, that Lesnar will not only be in the Royal Rumble match, but Brock will also be the No.1 entrant in the Rumble match. And will have to face and over-come 29 other men.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/MRVZe7JBd10&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite Lesnar being in the Royal Rumble match, this does not mean that his WWE Championship will be on the line. However, it does mean that if Brock does out last every other man in the match, he will no doubt be able to choose his own opponent at WrestleMania 36, on 5th April 2020.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Royal Rumble takes place on 26th January 2020 from Houston, Texas.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html">The advocate for current WWE Champion Brock Lesnar, Paul Heyman announced on last night’s RAW (6th Jan 20) that ‘The Beast’ will be a participant in this year’s Royal Rumble match.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep91 - NJPW Wrestle Kingdom 14 (Day 1 - 4th Jan 2020) with @KurtsAnglePod</title><link href="/podcasts/EP91/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep91 - NJPW Wrestle Kingdom 14 (Day 1 - 4th Jan 2020) with @KurtsAnglePod" /><published>2020-01-05T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP91</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP91/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep92 - NJPW Wrestle Kingdom 14 (Day 2 - 5th Jan 2020) with Griz</title><link href="/podcasts/EP92/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep92 - NJPW Wrestle Kingdom 14 (Day 2 - 5th Jan 2020) with Griz" /><published>2020-01-05T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP92</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP92/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">NXT:UK Review - January 2nd, 2020</title><link href="/articles/NXTUK-Review-January-2nd-2020/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="NXT:UK Review - January 2nd, 2020" /><published>2020-01-05T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/NXTUK%20Review%20January%202nd%202020</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/NXTUK-Review-January-2nd-2020/">&lt;p&gt;2 additional matches have been made for Takeover Blackpool 2. Trent Seven vs. Eddie Dennis and Tyler Bate vs. Jordan Devlin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-05/trenteddienxtuk.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;trent eddie&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-05/tylerjordan.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;jordan tyler&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First match of 2020 - Dave Mastiff vs Kona Reeves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kona cut a promo before the match to get heat. This was an ok match. Kona hasn’t been too lucky since coming to NXT UK.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Winner of the match: Dave Mastiff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here comes Toni Storm. She calls out Piper Niven she asks Piper to step aside. Piper says no. They brawl and out comes Kay Lee Ray.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-05/PiperToni.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;piper toni&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kassius Ohno vs Ligero.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good match. I enjoyed this one. Kassius is a good heel. He is getting a push on NXT UK more than the normal NXT. Not many High flying moves in this match. Kassius Ohno cuts a promo after the match.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Winner of the match: Kassius Ohno.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ashton Smith and Oliver Carter vs The Outliers: Riddick Moss and Dorian Mack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good tag match. Ashton and Oliver have had no luck and no wins since coming to NXT UK. Hopefully the team of Riddick Moss &amp;amp; Dorian Mack are going to get a push. A very shocking end to the match.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Winner of the match: Ashton Smith and Oliver Carter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alexander Wolfe vs Ilja Dragunov in a No DQ Match.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-05/iljawolfe.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;ilja wolfe&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good main event. Many weapons involved. Great story telling in this one. The rest of imperium banned from ringside. Ilja went after Alexander before the bell. Brutal match. DDT and a suplex onto chairs. A chair uses on Ilja’s fingers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Winner of the match: Ilja Dragunov. Really good way to start off 2020.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t forget to go check and then like and subscribe to my YouTube channel the people’s WWE channel. IF YOU SMELL WHAT RICK THE ROCK IS COOKIN.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>ricky-j</name></author><summary type="html">2 additional matches have been made for Takeover Blackpool 2. Trent Seven vs. Eddie Dennis and Tyler Bate vs. Jordan Devlin.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Epic Night #1 Wrestle Kingdom 14. Plus, The Main Event of Night #2 Set</title><link href="/news/wrestlekingdom-14-night-1/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Epic Night #1 Wrestle Kingdom 14. Plus, The Main Event of Night #2 Set" /><published>2020-01-04T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-04T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/news/wrestlekingdom%2014%20night%201</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/wrestlekingdom-14-night-1/">&lt;p&gt;After an epic night one of Wrestle Kingdom (4th Jan 2020) the main event of night two (5th Jan 2020) has been cemented. As newly crowned IWGP Intercontinental Champion Tetsuya Naito will face the reigning IWGP Heavyweight Champion, Kaszuskda Okada.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-04/OkadaNaito.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;okada naito set&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earlier in the evening Naito managed to regain the Intercontinental title after defeating Jay White, in a hard fought semi main event, inside of the sold out Tokyo Dome. While Okada battled for over 30+ minutes in an epic main event against Kota Ibushi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both Ibushi and Okada withstood a huge amount of offence against one-another, in what was the best match of the night, on a night of excellent matches, in what is already the best show of the year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Night two of Wrestle Kingdom 14 will not only feature the ‘Double Champ Dash’ between Okada vs. Naito. But will also feature Jon Moxley vs. Juice Robinson  for Moxley’s United States Championship, Chris Jericho vs. Hiroshi Takahashi, Zack Sabre Jr vs. SANADA for the British Heavyweight Championship, Jay White vs. Kota Ibushi,  and of course the final ever match of Jushin ‘Thunder’ Liger’s career.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html">After an epic night one of Wrestle Kingdom (4th Jan 2020) the main event of night two (5th Jan 2020) has been cemented. As newly crowned IWGP Intercontinental Champion Tetsuya Naito will face the reigning IWGP Heavyweight Champion, Kaszuskda Okada.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep90 - Interview with BIG F’N JOE (with Turnbuckle TV)</title><link href="/podcasts/EP90/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep90 - Interview with BIG F'N JOE (with Turnbuckle TV)" /><published>2020-01-03T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP90</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP90/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Brackets For 2020 Dusty Rhodes Tag Team Classic (NXT vs. NXT:UK)</title><link href="/news/Bracket-For-2020-Dusty-Rhodes-Tag-Team-Classic/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Brackets For 2020 Dusty Rhodes Tag Team Classic (NXT vs. NXT:UK)" /><published>2020-01-02T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/news/Bracket%20For%202020%20Dusty%20Rhodes%20Tag%20Team%20Classic</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/Bracket-For-2020-Dusty-Rhodes-Tag-Team-Classic/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-02/2020dustybracket.png&quot; alt=&quot;dusty tag classic brackets&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the eight teams for the tournament announced, the brackets for this year’s Dusty Rhodes Tag Team Classic has now been revealed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imperium (Marcel Barthel &amp;amp; Fabian Aichner) vs. The Forgotten Sons (Wesley Blake &amp;amp; Steve Cutler) and Matt Riddle &amp;amp; Pete Dunne vs. Mark Andrews &amp;amp; Flash Morgan Webster are the matches on the left side of the bracket.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The right side of the bracket has The Grizzled Young Veterans (Zack Gibson &amp;amp; James Drake) vs. Kushida and his partner (yet to be revealed) and The Undisputed Era (Kyle O’Reilly &amp;amp; Bobby Fish) vs. Gallus (Mark Coffey &amp;amp; Wolfgang).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;O’Reilly &amp;amp; Fish are the NXT Tag Team Champions, while Coffey &amp;amp; Wolfgang currently hold the NXT UK Tag Team titles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Dusty Classic features four teams from NXT (Undisputed Era, The Forgotten Sons, Riddle &amp;amp; Dunne, and Kushida’s team) and four teams from NXT UK (The Grizzled Young Veterans, Gallus, Imperium, and Andrews &amp;amp; Webster).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The schedule for the tournament hasn’t been announced.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">NXT and NXT UK to air on BT Sports</title><link href="/news/NXT-and-NXT-UK-to-air-on-BT-Sports/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="NXT and NXT UK to air on BT Sports" /><published>2020-01-01T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/news/NXT%20and%20NXT%20UK%20to%20air%20on%20BT%20Sports</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/NXT-and-NXT-UK-to-air-on-BT-Sports/">&lt;p&gt;BT Sport announced earlier this week that NXT and NXT UK will be joining their line-up of WWE programming. WWE’s deal with BT Sport will commence January 1st 2020.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like Raw and SmackDown, NXT will air live on BT Sport at the same time as it airs in the United States. The first show on BT will be this week’s taped episode of NXT, which begins at 1 a.m. local time on January 2nd for those in the UK and Ireland.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-01/nxtbt.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;NXT and NXTUK on BT Sports&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BT Sport wrote that “as well as airing all Raw, SmackDown and NXT shows live, BT Sport will also show primetime same day repeats. In addition, customers can catch up on all the overnight action whenever and wherever they like via the enhanced video player on the BT Sport app on mobile and BTSport.com.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BT Sport noted that full schedule details are to be announced for NXT UK. The show airs on the WWE Network on Thursdays.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a 30-year partnership, WWE closed out their run on Sky Sports with the Dec 30th edition of Raw.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html">BT Sport announced earlier this week that NXT and NXT UK will be joining their line-up of WWE programming. WWE’s deal with BT Sport will commence January 1st 2020.</summary></entry></feed>