<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-01-25T19:41:43+00:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Wrestling With Johners</title><subtitle>Pro Wrestling podcast with news, reviews and debate from WWE, NXT, NXT:UK, AEW, NJPW, Indy Wrestling and so much more. Listen to Wrestling With Johners on Apple Podcasts, Google Podcasts, Spotify, Podbean, Podcast Addict, Castbox, YouTube or wherever you get your podcasts.</subtitle><author><name>John Scott</name></author><entry><title type="html">WrestleMania Card Still Wide Open</title><link href="/news/WrestleMania-Card-Wide-Open/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="WrestleMania Card Still Wide Open" /><published>2020-01-20T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/news/WrestleMania%20Card%20Wide%20Open</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/WrestleMania-Card-Wide-Open/">&lt;p&gt;It is being reported from sources within WWE that WrestleMania 36 is still “wide open in many regards.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-20/wrestlemania 36 logo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;wm36logo&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At this point in previous years, there would be run-sheets or tentative WrestleMania lineups around, though those have been made more secretive in recent years. According to Sean Ross Sapp from Fightful.com, no one he’s spoken to has seen a run sheet or anything related to WrestleMania 36 yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There have even been a couple of people at the WWE Performance Center who have been told to “be ready” in case a WrestleMania spot is there for them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-20/keith lee.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;keith lee&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This could be seen as a massive positive and a welcome change, as compared to previous years. One wrestler spoken to said that it leads them to think WWE will go with who is hot for certain spots, instead of trying to make certain talents hot to fit the roles they’ve already decided for them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-20/adam cole.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;adam cole&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WrestleMania 36 is more than 2 months away, but there is already speculation regarding potential match-ups and whether NXT talent could be a part of the “Showcase of the Immortals” on April 5th in Tampa, Florida.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html">It is being reported from sources within WWE that WrestleMania 36 is still “wide open in many regards.”</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">‘The Man’ and CM Punk on this week’s WWE Backstage</title><link href="/news/Becky-and-CM-Punk-on-WWE-Backstage/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="'The Man' and CM Punk on this week's WWE Backstage" /><published>2020-01-19T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-19T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/news/Becky%20and%20CM%20Punk%20on%20WWE%20Backstage</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/Becky-and-CM-Punk-on-WWE-Backstage/">&lt;p&gt;Current WWE RAW Women’s Champion Becky Lynch has been announced as the guest for Tuesday’s episode of WWE Backstage on FS1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-19/becky.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;becky lynch&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The show will also feature CM Punk’s third appearance as an analyst.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The combination of Becky Lynch and CM Punk should help to boost viewing figures for WWE Backstage. Which has struggled to maintain a strong viewing audience since the show began in October 2019.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-19/CM-Punk-2019.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;cm punk&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And with The Royal Rumble PPV just around the corner it will be interesting to hear Punk’s thought’s on the line-up and the build, to one of the most popular WWE Pay-Per-Views of the year.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html">Current WWE RAW Women’s Champion Becky Lynch has been announced as the guest for Tuesday’s episode of WWE Backstage on FS1.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">NXT:UK Review - January 16th, 2020</title><link href="/articles/NXT-Review-16th-January-2020/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="NXT:UK Review - January 16th, 2020" /><published>2020-01-17T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-17T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/NXT%20Review%2016th%20January%202020</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/NXT-Review-16th-January-2020/">&lt;p&gt;We are coming off the heels off NXT:UK Takeover Blackpool 2. Only 2 matches on this week’s episode on the WWE Network. 
First match is…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-17/ballroom.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;empress ballroom&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-kid-vs-joseph-connors&quot;&gt;A-Kid vs. Joseph Connors&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-17/conners.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;conners&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These matches were taped before takeover Blackpool 2. This was a good match. I do think Connors should have been on the main Takeover card. It’s cool we got a taping before Takeover. A-kid seems to have turned into a jobber. Connors with the win in this match.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-17/a-kid.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;a-kid&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WINNER OF THE MATCH: Joseph Connors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;kassius-ohno-vs-dave-mastiff&quot;&gt;Kassius Ohno vs. Dave Mastiff&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-17/ohno.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;ohno&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another good match here. Hard hitting as expected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-17/mastiff.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;mastiff&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is another match I enjoyed but I do think the wrong person won, on this occasion. I thought Ohno was being pushed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-17/mastiff2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;mastiff&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WINNER OF THE MATCH: Dave Mastiff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was a good episode of NXT:UK.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t forget to go and check out my YouTube channel - The people’s WWE channel. If you smell what rick the rock is cookin’&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>ricky-j</name></author><summary type="html">We are coming off the heels off NXT:UK Takeover Blackpool 2. Only 2 matches on this week’s episode on the WWE Network. First match is…</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">NXT:UK TakeOver Blackpool II Review - 12th Jan 2020</title><link href="/articles/nxtuk-takeover-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="NXT:UK TakeOver Blackpool II Review - 12th Jan 2020" /><published>2020-01-17T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-17T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/nxtuk%20takeover%20review</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/nxtuk-takeover-review/">&lt;p&gt;Well here we go! We are live and time to make review history. First match is…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;trent-seven-vs-eddie-dennis&quot;&gt;Trent Seven vs. Eddie Dennis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Very, very good match to start things out. The crowd are absolutely hot. Hard hitting action. Eddie threw Trent over the top rope for the high spot.  By the way I have a great view of the ring. I did enjoy this match. My prediction came true.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Winner of the match Eddie Dennis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;kay-lee-ray-vs-piper-niven-vs-toni-storm-in-a-triple-threat-match-for-the-nxt-uk-womens-title&quot;&gt;Kay Lee Ray vs Piper Niven vs Toni Storm in a triple threat match for the NXT UK women’s title.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What a match. Just incredible! All 3 women left it all in the ring. High spots and high flying action. The crowd were super-hot. I’m lost for words. Toni hit her  finisher and was so close to winning the title but it didn’t happen. So many pin fall attempts, by all 3 women. The title did not change hands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-17/toni piper ray.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;storm ray niven&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Winner of the match and still NXT UK Women’s champion: Kay Lee&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tyler-bate-vs-jordan-devlin&quot;&gt;Tyler Bate vs Jordan Devlin&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wow, wow, wow! What an incredible match. We get an “Are you watching Vince McMahon chant. Another great match. During this match I discovered the commentators are on the balcony above me. I got the prediction wrong for this one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-17/tylerbate.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;tyler &amp;amp; jordan&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Winner of the match: Tyler Bate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;gallus-vs-imperium-vs-mark-andrewsflash-morgan-vs-the-grizzled-young-veterans-in-a-fatal-four-way-ladder-match-for-the-nxt-uk-tag-team-titles&quot;&gt;Gallus vs. Imperium vs. Mark Andrews/Flash Morgan vs. The Grizzled Young Veterans in a fatal four way ladder match for the NXT UK tag team titles.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-17/gallus.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;tag titles&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet another incredible match. All tag teams in the hunt for the titles. High flying action. Tag Gold on the line. A really hot crowd. This is wrestling! The titles didn’t change hands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Winner of the match and still NXT UK tag team champions, Gallus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Review time for the main event&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;walter-vs-joe-coffey-for-the-wwe-uk-title&quot;&gt;Walter vs. Joe Coffey for the WWE UK title.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-17/referee bump.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;referee&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wow, just wow! What a match. What a main event. Hard hitting powerful action. I thought this was never going to end. Both men with big moves. The referee got knocked down during the match by Walter, so in comes Alexander Wolfe to help him. Here comes Ilja Dragunov to take out Wolfe, the match continues and didn’t end there. This was breath taking. I’m so happy I got to witness it live.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-17/imperium.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;walter&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The finish came out of nowhere. A sleeper hold. Yes a sleeper bold from Walter. But wait a minute they are here. It’s the Undisputed Era bay-bay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They destroy Imperium. Winner of the match and still WWE UK Champion, Walter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-17/undisputed.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;adam cole bay bay&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What a show and I give it 10 out of 10. I did get to meet the ring announcer, Andy Shepard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t forget to go and check out my channel the people’s WWE channel. If you smell what Rick the Rock is cookin!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>ricky-j</name></author><summary type="html">Well here we go! We are live and time to make review history. First match is…</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep95 - MAVERICK BLADE Interview (Independent Wrestling Elite UK)</title><link href="/podcasts/interviews/EP95/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep95 - MAVERICK BLADE Interview (Independent Wrestling Elite UK)" /><published>2020-01-16T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/interviews/EP95</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/interviews/EP95/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Comedy In Wrestling!</title><link href="/articles/Comedy-in-Wrestling/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Comedy In Wrestling!" /><published>2020-01-13T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/Comedy%20in%20Wrestling</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/Comedy-in-Wrestling/">&lt;p&gt;It’s important not to shy away from the big topics, so this time around I am focussing on…. Is there a place for comedy in wrestling?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I featured Orange Cassidy in my first piece and how much I have been taken in by the gimmick so far so it got me to thinking more about comedy in wrestling, in addition to this I am currently working my way through a hell of a lot of Chikara on Amazon Prime – there are about TEN seasons of content for FREE if you are a Prime Member (for the record this article is not sponsored by Amazon Prime and other streaming services are available….)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I think of comedy in wrestling I am looking at the more overt use of characters, gimmicks and spots, more so than being funny in promos and put downs – for example The Rock and John Cena are probably two of the best all time on the mic and could be hilarious at times but I would never consider them as comedic wrestlers so to that end I am ignoring the ‘cheap pop’ sort of comedy, which also means reluctantly I am not including Mick Foley, one of my all-time wrestling heroes and incredibly funny guy, in this piece.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Obviously in the Indies there is more scope for comedy and there is more opportunity to be a bit more silly and go all out with wild gimmicks and humour. To look at British Wrestling the like of Grado, Sebastian Radclaw and Mad Man Manson quickly spring to mind. Manson is someone that I saw loads of on DVD and YouTube before having the opportunity to see him live and meet him a couple of times and he really didn’t disappoint, and the fact that so many people would go along with it sums up how much fun wrestling can be. One of my personal Manson highlights occurred at a Pro Wrestling Kingdom show where he competed with another one of my favourite comedic wrestlers, Sebastian Radclaw in an “11 Stages of Hell” match which included thumb wrestling, a staring contest and playing noughts and crosses on the referees back. It was completely silly and stupid and yet at the same time completely engaging and entertaining!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grado tends to split opinions a little more as many would argue that his wrestling ability falls far short of how over his character was, but ultimately getting over is every wrestlers goal and Grado has done very well with what he does. Similarly, someone like Joey Ryan really polarises opinion, he has a tonne of talent but has really bought into his gimmick which doesn’t really work with a lot of people. In the earlier days the sleazy character worked but as the boundaries have been pushed it seems to have pushed a lot of people away – possibly it’s the typical wrestling thing of over using certain moves so they lose shock value and just become a bit tedious. Although arguably what I saw of him predominantly teaming with Candice LeRae in PWG I really enjoyed and felt that he was a good worker.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nick Dinsmore, who is likely better known to most as Eugene, Eric Bischof’s nephew in WWE is another name that springs to mind on this subject. When he arrived in WWE he was portrayed as being quite simple and copying famous moves etc to be honest the character seemed to get over really well with fans but I recall at the time thinking that there’s definitely a limit on how far the character can go and ultimately it would be incredibly difficult to repackage the character down the line … as Robert Downey Jr said as Kirk Lazarus in “Tropic Thunder” “…everyone knows you never go full retard.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Attack! Pro Wrestling is a promotion which I have followed for a long time and have been fortunate to get to a number shows in Birmingham, Bristol and even at the legendary Cathays in Cardiff. Attack is unique in that they have utilised arguably the best roster available from the UK but made their shows uniquely entertaining and fun with themed shows and top talent dressing up and becoming different characters from movies and computer games. I’d say that my visit to Cardiff for the Press Start 2 show a few years ago remains one of my favourite wrestling shows I have ever attended – just a few highlights from card include Pete Dunne, Damian Dunne, Chris Brookes and Ryan Smile in a fatal 4 way as Streetfighter and Mortal Kombat characters, Mark Andrews as Ash Ketchum against Tyler Bate as the Pokémon Machoke where he was painted silver head to toe not to mention the Hunters going head to head in the main event as Mario and Luigi! If you haven’t seen it, I highly recommend finding the DVD or heading over to their page on Vimeo. I am also fairly certain that Attack is the birthplace of No Fun Dunne which is one of the best gimmicks around at present in my opinion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Often the crowd can contribute to comedy in wrestling, it can be simply buying in to gimmicks and silly matches – let’s face it going into slow motion during a match doesn’t really go over if the crowd aren’t willing to suspend their disbelief! Or if you watch NXTUK the crowd really get into it resulting in some interesting songs and chants for different wrestlers, or chanting for VAR as they were at Takeover Blackpool II – which is topical but very unique to the UK/European audience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The flipside to that is that, at times, those in attendance forget that in reality they are just spectators and try to take over themselves and become a part of the show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The likes of Kris Travis and Martin Kirby deserve a mention in the discussion of comedic wrestling, individually they are both highly entertaining and when together as Project Ego they seemed to blend being a well-oiled, effective tag team perfectly with being very funny and entertaining - both in the ring and interacting with the crowd.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I mentioned above, I have been watching rather a lot of Chikara of late, and similar to Attack they have some amazing talent on their shows but manage to make it good fun and get a lot of interaction with their audience. Some of the characters are wacky but generally well developed including The Colony, I like the fact that each member of the Colony is different and has a different role and style. There are lots of outlandish characters and the variety works really well over a succession of shows, I can’t wait to watch more. Based on what I have seen so far, I would certainly recommend that if you haven’t seen Chikara yet it is worth checking them out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, in summary I definitely see a place for comedy in wrestling but as with a lot of things it does run a fine line and can go somewhat wrong if not done well. I think the major promotions do quite well with bringing comedy into promos and skits without making it too silly – in my last piece I mentioned some of the promo work in AEW in particular with Le Champion which I think works really well. WWE unfortunately often create “funny” moments unintentionally and some angles become laughable for all the wrong reasons…. cough cough…. Lana and Lashley….&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Name Drop… There are quite a few to choose from on this topic but I’ll go with Seb Radclaw. I was fortunate enough to see him in action numerous times including being selected to join him in the ring to learn the Gremlin dance at a Pro Wrestling Kingdom show, I even got chance to have a lengthy sit down chat with him at a Kamikaze Pro event in order to write a piece on him (which can be found here:  http://bit.ly/36eQAaU )&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-13/matt2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;matt2&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-13/matt1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;iron&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am on Twitter where I have a new profile – Matt Based Wrestling - just to focus on all things wrestling related, you can follow me at &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/mattbasedwres01&quot;&gt;@mattbasedwres01&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>matt-bayliss</name></author><summary type="html">It’s important not to shy away from the big topics, so this time around I am focussing on…. Is there a place for comedy in wrestling?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Things to leave in the 2010’s…</title><link href="/articles/Things-to-leave-in-the-2010s/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Things to leave in the 2010's… " /><published>2020-01-13T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/Things%20to%20leave%20in%20the%202010s</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/Things-to-leave-in-the-2010s/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;things-to-leave-in-the-2010s&quot;&gt;Things to leave in the 2010’s…&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-13/tyler.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;tyler&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happy New Year! Welcome to the return of the roaring 20’s, a surge in individuals’ positivity, changes in their attitude and the creation of resolutions and frequent reminders of them at every turn… well, for a few weeks anyway! Mine are temporarily on hold, thanks to illness and lack of sleeping caused by coughing fits. Despite attempting to change my outlook to be more positive,  I have used the first days of 2020 to reflect on the last decade of wrestling, its events / topics / sources of irritation [delete as appropriate] and attempted to compile a list of things that should really be left in the 2010s – you know, out with the old and in with the new (and all that).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;1promotions-seemingly-ignoring-fans&quot;&gt;1.Promotions Seemingly Ignoring Fans.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-13/sir.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;sir&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By promotions… We can all think of one and it’s easy to use them as the ‘scapegoat’ for this particular trait. To support this, let me take you back to Pittsburgh on January 26th, 2014. This is a significant date for a few reasons, namely it being the date and location of the 27th Royal Rumble PPV and the beginning of the famed Road to Wrestlemania. Little did us fans know it, but this was the last time we would see a certain CM Punk in a wrestling match for WWE, Daniel Bryan was overlooked, and the wrong man won the Royal Rumble (Sorry Dave, as much as I love you la, you didn’t deserve it! But props for you putting over D-Bry at ‘Mania). The crowd was annoyed from the minute it was clear who would be winning the Royal Rumble. Normally, when wrestling fans get annoyed, it seemingly dies down after a week or so. This was not the case, and fans were loudly expressing it on any platform possible – social media, at shows, on wrestling forums. You name it, people made it clear they were not happy. There is a saying that “The customer is King” and whilst this saying was coined way before the invention of computers, let alone the internet, WWE missed the memo on this one. Ultimately, fans got what they wanted at Wrestlemania 30 and the sight of D-Bry holding the titles up high at the close of the show is one of the moments that made us fans feel warm and fuzzy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But we shouldn’t be surprised - WWE has got form for seemingly ignoring the wishes of their fans - there have been several occasions both prior to [such as their burial of the original Nexus stable in 2010; their refusal to turn John Cena Heel in 2012; Dolph Zillgers’ treatment after his 2012 Money In The Bank win] and since the 2014 Royal Rumble where WWE have simply ignored the fans. From the constant ignoring of overlooking of talent like Cesaro, Bray Wyatt, Shinskue Nakamura and countless others, to the way Roman Reigns was seemingly forced down our throat as the next guy – with shameless tactics like muting crowds and cheers being deployed. Most recently, fans called for Liv Morgan to return as Sister Abigail alongside Bray Wyatt, given her recent return… it’s clear that lessons have not been learned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;2repetition-repetition-and-a-little-more-repetition&quot;&gt;2.Repetition. Repetition… and a little more Repetition.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This one comes in many forms. One of the most obvious is the continued seemingly reliance on ‘authority figures’ and a talents’ struggle against them. Whilst it does provide a ‘feel good moment’ when the authority figure has been outsmarted / triumphed over, if promotions are going to run with this, it needs to be something special. Either by delivering something we’ve not seen before or making it so believable fans actively avoid seeking out the next twist and turn in the story via the internet – the show alone becomes must see. Yes, the internet and social media can be used to support and develop storylines, but it can also undermine them. In the age of social media, instant access to content and a wider level of fan communication, it is harder for promotions to ‘blur the lines’ between reality and storyline. This also applies to the famed “7 year rule” [where storylines are recycled every 7 years]. There is an argument that this should really be forgotten or at least be modified to stand out from other previous angles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-13/cole.png&quot; alt=&quot;cole&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The same could be said for certain moves and sequences. I understand that there are only so many wrestling moves in existence, so this is partly inevitable and tolerable. But things like the continued use of phrases like “…That’s the hardest part of the ring!” when describing a move that has been completed using the outside of the ring (for example an x-plex or buckle bomb). Whilst I understand that this is partly used to create drama on behalf of the commentator [and is often directed at them by someone in production], for some reason it irritates me. Fans do not need to be reminded of this every single time it is used and every time it is replayed / recapped. In fact, the use of the outside of the ring itself is, in my opinion, becoming overused. Think of the use of chair shots, blading and, of course, sledge hammers during the Attitude and Ruthless Aggression eras – they were a certainty at some point, especially during a PPV, and now, it seems that the use of the outer edge of the ring has now become the certainty. For me, when used little and often, the moves have a dramatic impact and I have no doubt that they hurt. However, at the rate they are currently being used, I worry that the moves will become the equivalent of chair shots, meaning that the risks wrestlers take to perform this move is essentially worthless and borderline reckless. I also hate to mention it [mainly because I adore Mauro Ronallo on commentary], but “Tope Suicida” is slowly getting onto the above list, especially when used by anyone else other than Mauro. Don’t ask me why, but its just not the same and gets cringeworthy after a while. Whilst I’m here, I’m also going to add “The Big Dog” to the above list – irrespective of who it’s said by. I don’t know if this because of how Roman Reigns has been treated by the promotion or simply because I don’t think the moniker suits him – but it is irritating to say the least. For me, it ruins the overall product and does not have the desired effect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;3flaunting--belittling-real-life-romances&quot;&gt;3.Flaunting / Belittling Real Life Romances.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh boy… this could make me sound like a crank [a crazy / jealous person] and, for the sake of clarity, any of the individuals / couples mentioned here I truly wish well. But… just because two talents are together off screen does not mean to say they should be forced to be seen together on screen or have their relationship flaunted at the fans, especially when it makes no sense in terms of storylines to do so or there is very little build up to their onscreen relationship and it seems ‘forced’. Especially if there is very little pay off or their relationship is seemingly ignored / never discussed again after a few weeks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-13/lana.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;lana&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Case and point – Becky Lynch and Seth Rollins. From a storyline perspective it didn’t make sense to shoehorn their relationship into the storylines. Why? The Man character doesn’t need to be associated with anyone; does what she wants to do, when she wants to do it; looks out for number one. Whilst Seth Rollins has proven that he doesn’t need anyone to support him – be it heel or face. Rollins has the ‘it factors’ to make it on his own. These are the traits that have made their characters so refreshing and entertaining. Especially Becky Lynch, who is a talented performer and conducts herself like one, making the fans take note. For me, the acknowledgement of her relationship with Seth Rollins by WWE in terms of storyline is a jarring reminder of the person behind The Man, and it’s unnecessary. It also reminds me that the person behind the Beast Slayer is capable of thinking of someone other than himself (given that he’s currently a heel). Maybe its just me, but every time I see Becky Lynch now, I automatically think about her relationship with Seth Rollins and not the reason why she’s on screen – usually to prove that she is one of the best wrestlers in the division. It’s the same with Rollins. Also, the fact that there is merchandise that profits from their relationship makes me somewhat uncomfortable. I don’t know why, but I can’t be the only one who cringes at the merchandise?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is also worth noting that there are plenty of couples in promotions that are dating / engaged / married, and you’re not reminded of this every time you see them. For example, Adam Cole and Britt Baker, Sarah Logan and Erik Rowe, Bianca Belair and Montez Ford, Alistair Black and Zelina Vega, Jack Gallagher and Alexis Rose, Nikki Cross and Killian Dain are either dating, engaged or married – but this is never mentioned by their respective promotions. Granted, if you look hard enough, there are some subtle nods to certain relationships – for example, Montez Ford sports Bianca Belairs’ lips on his attire and via a tattoo, which is a fantastic nod to their lives away from the squared circle, and gives fans like ourselves something different to discuss etc. By not explicitly discussing their relationships it allows the fans to continue to see the individual talent as just that – individuals and not the spouse of who they are dating.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-13/chyna.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;chyna&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whilst it is important to take the time to remember that wrestling consumes the life of a wrestler – as a fan, I pretty much think about it constantly, but imagine the level of obsession it would grow to, should I dedicate my body to it. It makes sense for wrestlers to date other wrestlers or those involved in the industry in some way, shape or form, especially as they understand the sacrifices needed to be successful. Although, it can become problematic, especially if two talents are together IRL, and they share aspects of their lives together outside the ring. Look at Lana and Rusev. Whilst WWE initially did their best to separate the respective characters of Lana and Rusev back in 2015, until Lana announced their real-life engagement via social media, essentially forcing WWEs hand and putting the pair back together onscreen. Since then WWE has made no secret of the pair’s relationship, featuring it within storylines on both Raw, SmackDown! and the likes of Total Divas [from what I’m told via people and an internet search]. Yet, in 2019 we saw the ‘breakdown’ their marriage, with Lana seemingly running off with Bobby Lashley. My issue with it…? It is uncomfortable viewing to say the least. One could argue that it is trash TV at its finest [and it is directed by Paul Heyman, a man known for outrageous storylines and controversy], but for me, it seemingly belittles the real-life relationship that Lana and Rusev have – especially as the stakes are get more and more ridiculous – from restraining orders, matches that never happen, awkward ‘proposals’, a ruined wedding and a fake pregnancy [the most irritating part IMO]. All of this is somewhat tolerable, given that we’re discussing Wrestling. Yet, I can’t help but question how the individuals behind Lana, Rusev and Lashley truly feel about what they’re being asked to portray? How does the person behind Lashley and his spouse feel [if they exist, as google seemingly shows nothing but Lana]? Are all parties truly happy with it? It would be interesting to see if any of them have refused aspects of this storyline. I know I would have refused most things asked of them. I remember Eddie Gurrereo discussing his ‘relationship’ with Chyna – and I never noticed this until it was pointed out, he never, ever kissed Chyna on the lips. Ever. That is a testament to his marriage with Vickie. So, my question is why couldn’t this logic be applied here? By all means, split the onscreen characters of Lana and Rusev, with her ‘moving on’, but being respectful at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;4foreign-heels&quot;&gt;4.Foreign Heels.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s 2019; this angle ages b a d l y. It should have stopped in the 2000’s. Enough said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-13/iron.png&quot; alt=&quot;iron&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seriously though, if this is going to be done, it needs to be handled with extreme caution and care, to ensure that motives of said heel(s) are legitimate, yet inoffensive, and have more to them than just ‘I grew up in a different country to you all so I hate you’ as this is honestly what it feels like. Take note from NJPW who seemingly overlook the temptation to do this (from what I’ve seen anyway). Wrestlers from other parts of the world offer promotions a chance to make history in some way, shape or form. Use that as the motives and not just the nationality / current affairs to influence this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;5lacklustre-returns&quot;&gt;5.Lacklustre Returns.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-13/meh.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;meh&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll refrain from discussing Batista’s 2014 return in detail – this my attempt to remain somewhat neutral and apply restraint. But, let’s be honest, every one of his returns during the 2010s could have been handled better (though, I was saying Boo-Tista!). The same could be said for Sting’s return in 2014, both of Goldberg’s returns in 2016 – 17 and 2018 – 2019 respectively, the Hardy Boyz return in 2017… I could go on, and I’m sure there are ones I’ve missed (and I’m sure you’ll let me know). All of these have specific reasons for their lacklustre returns – from poor booking to a failure to instil a sense of nostalgia. Whatever the reason behind it, after the initial excitement (even if it was for a fleeting moment) dissipated, the fans were usually left with a sense of “why?”, which was often left unanswered or creative seemingly forgot about the performer after a few weeks or months, leaving them in creative limbo for what feels like forever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, be still my beating heart in 2016 when I first saw the image of A J Styles and Shawn Michaels on a Royal Rumble poster floating around the internet. Immediately, I forgot about the botched returns of others. I forgot about the potential implications of the return. This was the match I needed to see, one I didn’t realise I needed in my life and one that I could happily have seen Michaels come out of retirement for. It allowed myself to dream of what I would see. How it would play out. Whilst it wouldn’t make sense to have Michaels win, the idea of seeing him against someone the calibre of Styles was exciting – it could have been what WWE needed at the time. When it was shot down… I respected the decision and the reasons behind it. However, Crown Jewel 2018 happened and frankly, my heart sank when I saw it. We all know the reasons behind what went wrong in the match and the criticisms us fans shared. The fact remains, despite Michaels’ protests that Crown Jewel was a “…glorified house show…” and “…done as a favour…”, this was Michaels last match. Such a big deal was made of the fact that he was coming out of retirement for this adds more salt into the wound. Given the choice over what ‘last match’ I wanted to see Shawn Michaels have, what we got, wasn’t something to end such an accomplished career on. And, between you and me, I hope this fact bugs him just enough to make him have this one, last match, against AJ… Or, at the risk of further contradiction… maybe against Adam Cole or… dare I say it… Tyler Bate? Allow me to dream on this one…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;6part-time-champions&quot;&gt;6.Part Time Champions.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some returns in the 2010s that can be deemed successful for a variety of reasons – The Rock in 2011, Brock Lesnar in 2012 and Goldberg in 2016 (and believe me, we’ll discuss them at length at some point). For the sake of keeping the word count down, and to maintain your interest, these returns are associated with being part time champions. That is, having some incarnation of a World Title, yet sporadically appearing on TV with title defences being scarce. Granted, The Rock only had his title for just over 2 months, so maybe some leeway should be applied. However, by having those who are on part time contracts hold the top titles, the damage done to the prestige and history of the respective title must be considered. Not to mention the message it sends to full time, fan favourites in the locker room. For me and others, if the top Title is on someone who isn’t contracted to appear regularly and as a result, is not defended on every PPV event surely makes the belt redundant? Why should fans like us be excited to see a title that both management and the champion themselves seemingly doesn’t care about? If I ask you to cast your mind back to the mid 2000s, although top title belts were on the same person for a long period of time (in certain circumstances anyway), the belt was seen on TV every week and the audience was reminded of who had it. When feuds were had over it, both parties made it clear that they wanted the title – at any cost.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-13/brock.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;brock&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Such a big deal was made of Brock Lesnars’ 504-day run with the Universal title, irrespective of the memes about missing title belts and general fan upset at hardly seeing the title, let alone the champion. Although very young in its existence, the WWE UK Championship was defended more times during Pete Dunne’s 685-day run [21] than Brock Lesnar defended the Universal Title in his 504-day run [8]. At the time of his reign, Pete Dunne was also wrestling in other promotions and proudly carrying his title with him wherever he went, irrespective of him defending it, meaning that the title was still seen, and fans were still talking about the champion positively. When the title was defended, there was such an emphasis on the importance of its defence and implications to the NXT UK Roster. Yet, we are expected to believe the same for Lesnars’ Universal title run, despite it never being as hyped in the same manner. There was attempts to do so for sure, but it never felt as important.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;7pay-per-views-for-days&quot;&gt;7.Pay Per Views for Days…&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is one that I am sure will not stay, but I can dream. Back in the day of Channel 4 showing WWF PPVs, I could get a good 4 hours of sleep BEFORE the show and a good 3 hours of sleep AFTER the show before heading to school and functioning normally. This is an impossible task now – not because I’m older, but because of the amount of content surrounding a PPV – the pre-show, the PPV itself and some form of interview / documentary / pod cast that will follow. Shows like Wrestlemania, if you include the pre-show is close to 7 hours long. Now, don’t get me wrong, I love wrestling, as I’m sure you do… but 7 hours? Especially in a week that has the Hall of Fame Ceremony (usually around 5 hours, if you include the pre-show), NXT Takeover (usually around 4 hours, pre show included), 3 hours of RAW, 2 Hours of SmackDown! and 1 Hour of NXT. That makes it 22+ hours of wrestling in 5 days. Not to mention the events that happen in and around Wrestlemania Weekend if you’re lucky enough to be there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-13/wwf-forever.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;wwf forever&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The point I’m trying to make is that with the lengths of time being extended for seemingly every PPV, it feels like wrestlers are not challenged to go out give their absolute best in such a short amount of time. Sometimes matches surpass 20 minutes, which is great if the match is engaging – but how long is too long? Having been at NXT UK: Takeovers / Tournaments / Tapings, once I’m in my seat, I don’t leave it. Not for a drink, food or a comfort break (unless desperate). Why? Because I want to take in every single second of the experience possible. I don’t want to miss a thing. And whilst it is doable for me, for others, its simply not. Whilst fans now have the luxury of being able to view PPVs via an On-Demand style platform, meaning we can pause, rewind and revisit PPVs as we please, if you are someone who likes to keep up to date with events (and not have spoilers from social media), you are forced to keep going or turn the internet off on your devises to maintain your spoiler free experience. There is a slight glimmer of hope though, with NJPW splitting Wrestlekingdom 14 over 2 nights. Maybe this could pave the way for other major PPVs to follow – for example, WWE could split PPVs over 3 nights – Raw, Smackdown and NXT to have their nights respectively, reducing the length of the shows per night?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As per usual, I’m sure I’ve missed things off this list! My only hope is that some of these will be left in the last decade. So, the question is, what would you like to see left in the 2010s?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>lexi-helms</name></author><summary type="html">Things to leave in the 2010’s…</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep94 - NXTUK TakeOver Blackpool 2 Review (with Matt Bayliss)</title><link href="/podcasts/EP94/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep94 - NXTUK TakeOver Blackpool 2 Review (with Matt Bayliss)" /><published>2020-01-12T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP94</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP94/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep93 – Brock #1 In Rumble | NXTUK TakeOver Preview | AEW &amp;amp; NXT (with @fowl_original)</title><link href="/podcasts/EP93/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep93 – Brock #1 In Rumble | NXTUK TakeOver Preview | AEW &amp; NXT (with @fowl_original)" /><published>2020-01-11T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP93</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP93/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Time Splitters (Alex Shelley &amp;amp; Kushida) to reunite in NXT</title><link href="/news/Alex-Shelly-to-team-with-Kushida-in-NXT/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Time Splitters (Alex Shelley &amp; Kushida) to reunite in NXT " /><published>2020-01-09T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-09T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/news/Alex%20Shelly%20to%20team%20with%20Kushida%20in%20NXT</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/Alex-Shelly-to-team-with-Kushida-in-NXT/">&lt;p&gt;The Time Splitters are reuniting in NXT for the 2020 Dusty Rhodes Tag Team Classic!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mauro Ranallo announced during last night’s show that Alex Shelley will team with Kushida next week against The Grizzled Young Veterans in the first round of the tag team tournament.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-09/shelley.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;alex shelly and kushida&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Time Splitters were an active team from 2012-2015 and last competed together in 2016.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alex Shelley is most famously known for his time in TNA/Impact Wrestling as one half of the Motor City Machine Guns with Chris Sabin. He recently guest coached at the WWE Performance Centre, leading many to speculate he’d team with Kushida in the tourney, but Shelley attempted to downplay this last night on Twitter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Everybody seems to think Kushi needs me,” he wrote. “Kushi and I, and The Bucks, and Forever Hooligans, and ReDragon, helped change [NJPW]’s jr. tag division. But really, he’s going to be awesome with any partner.”&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html">The Time Splitters are reuniting in NXT for the 2020 Dusty Rhodes Tag Team Classic!</summary></entry></feed>