<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-12-27T15:54:33+00:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Wrestling With Johners</title><subtitle>Pro Wrestling podcast with news, reviews and debate from WWE, NXT, NXT:UK, AEW, NJPW, Indy Wrestling and so much more. Listen to Wrestling With Johners on Apple Podcasts, Google Podcasts, Spotify, Podbean, Podcast Addict, Castbox, YouTube or wherever you get your podcasts.</subtitle><author><name>John Scott</name></author><entry><title type="html">Bray Wyatt first match back in WWE AT MSG #shorts #wweraw #braywyatt</title><link href="/da-call-up/videos/2022/12/27/Bray-Wyatt-first-match-back-in-WWE-AT-MSG-shorts-wweraw-braywyatt/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bray Wyatt first match back in WWE AT MSG #shorts #wweraw #braywyatt" /><published>2022-12-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-12-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/da-call-up/videos/2022/12/27/Bray%20Wyatt%20first%20match%20back%20in%20WWE%20AT%20MSG%20shorts%20wweraw%20braywyatt</id><content type="html" xml:base="/da-call-up/videos/2022/12/27/Bray-Wyatt-first-match-back-in-WWE-AT-MSG-shorts-wweraw-braywyatt/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name>da-call-up</name></author><category term="da-call-up" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">MONDAY NIGHT RAW LIVE STREAM 12-26-22- Special end of year Show</title><link href="/da-call-up/videos/2022/12/27/MONDAY-NIGHT-RAW-LIVE-STREAM-122622-Special-end-of-year-Show/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="MONDAY NIGHT RAW LIVE STREAM 12-26-22- Special end of year Show" /><published>2022-12-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-12-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/da-call-up/videos/2022/12/27/MONDAY%20NIGHT%20RAW%20LIVE%20STREAM%20122622%20%20Special%20end%20of%20year%20Show</id><content type="html" xml:base="/da-call-up/videos/2022/12/27/MONDAY-NIGHT-RAW-LIVE-STREAM-122622-Special-end-of-year-Show/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name>da-call-up</name></author><category term="da-call-up" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">My 1st Wrestling Training session vs My Lastest</title><link href="/my-britwres-journey/videos/2022/12/27/My-1st-Wrestling-Training-session-vs-My-Lastest/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My 1st Wrestling Training session vs My Lastest" /><published>2022-12-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-12-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/my-britwres-journey/videos/2022/12/27/My%201st%20Wrestling%20Training%20session%20vs%20My%20Lastest</id><content type="html" xml:base="/my-britwres-journey/videos/2022/12/27/My-1st-Wrestling-Training-session-vs-My-Lastest/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name>my-britwres-journey</name></author><category term="my-britwres-journey" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Issue 48 Shows of November 26-December 2, 2022</title><link href="/articles/2022/12/27/Issue-48-Shows-of-November-26-December-2,-2022/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Issue 48 Shows of November 26-December 2, 2022" /><published>2022-12-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-12-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/2022/12/27/Issue%2048%20Shows%20of%20November%2026-December%202,%202022</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/2022/12/27/Issue-48-Shows-of-November-26-December-2,-2022/"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png" alt="pro darin" class="restrict-width" /></p>

<h1 id="progress-chapter-143-the-deadly-viper-tour--codename-sidewinder">Progress Chapter 143: The Deadly Viper Tour – Codename: Sidewinder</h1>

<p>We’re kicking things off with a belated Progress recap. Plus, even though a sidewinder is a type of snake, I—for some reason—think of “Rogue Trip: Vacation 2012” (a comedic parody of the “Twisted Metal” franchise) where one of the vehicles is named Sidewinder.</p>

<p>Videogame nostalgia aside, the 143rd chapter of Progress took place on October 9, 2022 at the O2 Arena in Manchester, England in the United Kingdom; it also served as the fourth part of the Deadly Viper Tour. Nine matches were on the card including two quarterfinal round matches that were part of the Natural Progression Series tournament, a match that featured a returning Progress wrestler that competed in NXT UK in the past, and a brand-new match—known as Super Mob Smash 12—that looked like a cross between a fatal four-way tag match and a trios match mainly because all four teams consisted of three wrestlers each.</p>

<p>The aforementioned Super Mob Smash 12 was indeed a fun bout to watch, even with high flying and “blink and you’ll miss it” moments coming from all twelve competitors that were in this match along with some comedic moments. Yes, it was hard to keep an eye on who was going after whom at times, but it still fun while it lasted.</p>

<p>Not only did I enjoy this match, but there were also two others after ranking them from fair to very good; one was the opening match between Millie McKenzie—whom we saw return one chapter ago—and Alexxis Falcon. Millie, even though I’m two chapters in, appears to be on the roll as of late ever since returning to Progress; Alexxis—a fan favorite as well as my favorite—on the other hand still gives her opponents a run for their money, even in matches where there is no gold on the line.</p>

<p>The other match that I enjoyed became my favorite of this chapter, and it served as part of the quarterfinal round of the Natural Progression Series tournament; in this match were two wrestlers that are not related despite having the same last name, and they were Liam and Leon Slater. Both wrestlers—or Slaters if you will—fought tooth and nail while being aware that advancing to the next round was on the line, and in the end, it was Leon who picked up his career first Progress win. Leon has shown us that he has more in store in his pro wrestling career even in Progress; he definitely has a bright future in that sport for sure.</p>

<p>Here are the match results from Manchester…</p>

<h2 id="match-1-millie-mckenzie-defeated-alexxis-falcon">Match #1: Millie McKenzie defeated Alexxis Falcon.</h2>
<p>Beating poor Olie Spring to the punch, I do remember Millie and Alexxis competing in their last one-on-one match; the last time they did so was in 2021 in the Theatre Peckham in London, England. After Millie blocked the Falcon’s Fury, she hit Alexxis with an uppercut and a cutter for two before Alexxis came back with a Twist of Fate for two, a snapmare neckbreaker for two, and the Falcon’s Fury for a near fall. Then, Millie hit her with a basement dropkick followed by a spear for the win. Both wrestlers shook hands afterwards before Alexxis raised Millie’s arm. <strong>My score: 4/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="match-2-elijah-defeated-tom-dawkins">Match #2: Elijah defeated Tom Dawkins.</h2>
<p>This was Dawkins’ first match without his Cara Noir alter ego; he felt reluctant coming into the ring and competing as a plain vanilla wrestler. Spike Trivet, with Bullit, appeared at the entryway and told Dawkins to take off his Cara Noir t-shirt; he would then stop Dawkins from attempting any of his Cara Noir maneuvers such as the Swan Woo.</p>

<p>After Elijah hit Dawkins with the Graveyard Smash for a near fall, Dawkins hit him with a powerbomb for two and went for a package driver until Trivet stopped him again; Dawkins instead put Elijah in a cross armbreaker and gave the “sovereign lord” the “number one salute” until Elijah fought out of the hold and won with the Danger Buster. Afterwards, Trivet coerced Dawkins to leave while Elijah stood in the ring and saw the lights go out with his music video and theme song going awry, SMPTE color bars, numeric code and all; Elijah looked confused afterwards as soon as the lights went back on. <strong>My score: 2/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="match-3-tate-mayfairs-defeated-sam-bailey-in-the-quarterfinal-round-of-the-natural-progression-series-tournament">Match #3: Tate Mayfairs defeated Sam Bailey in the quarterfinal round of the Natural Progression Series tournament.</h2>
<p>This was Manchester native Bailey’s debut. Before the match started, Simon Miller was trying not to laugh while introducing Mayfairs until Mayfairs called him a “stupid idiot” and then called Manchester a “b-town”; Miller looked flustered and took off his Progress jacket before announcing Bailey’s intro. During the match, Mayfairs beat down Bailey and—after saying “Tate-ness is greatness”—performed a Spinaroonie until Bailey booted him and hit him with a blockbuster for two; Bailey then attempted to dropkick Mayfairs in the corner, but missed and ended up getting tangled on the top rope, allowing Mayfairs to hit him with a coast-to-coast double axe handle for two. Near the end, Mayfairs grabbed brass knuckles from under the ring, and Bailey went after him until almost hitting referee LK; Bailey then rolled up Mayfairs—who grabbed one of the turnbuckle covers—for two and, when LK went to fix the cover, Mayfairs hit him with the knuckles before incapacitating him with a sleeper/bodyscissors combo for the win. <strong>My score: 2.5/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="match-4-nina-samuels-defeated-taonga">Match #4: Nina Samuels defeated Taonga.</h2>
<p>The last time Nina was in Progress was in chapter 94 where she lost in the last round of the Revelations of Divine Love tournament to Impact wrestler Jordynne Grace in 2019. After Nina blocked the I’m Prettier, Taonga hit Nina with an armbreaker and a running knee for two, then Nina pretended to be unconscious before rolling her up for two; then, Nina blocked the I’m Prettier again and grabbed Taonga by the hair before hitting her with a roundhouse kick and winning with the Starstruck (ushigoroshi).</p>

<p>After the match, Nina said that Progress needed “more Nina” and poked fun of the fans for not having high standards, then had a crewman give her a “Nina Samuels Award”—a small pink trophy—and declared herself the winner of that award; Alexxis Falcon appeared and called the award a “shit little trophy”, then said that she and the rest of the women built the division while Nina was away, and then vowed to take the award and shove it up Nina’s ass. <strong>My score: 2.5/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="match-5-kid-lykos-w-kid-lykos-ii-defeated-luke-jacobs-w-ethan-allen">Match #5: Kid Lykos (w/ Kid Lykos II) defeated Luke Jacobs (w/ Ethan Allen).</h2>
<p>Allen his healing from his injuries for the rest of the year. During the match, after KL hit Jacobs with a Casanova kick and a Swanton for a near fall, Jacobs fought back and then knocked KL2 off the apron; he then fought both members of Lykos Gym at ringside, and then hit KL2 and KL with half-and-half suplexes into the chairs in the audience. The end of the match saw Jacobs hit KL with a top rope splash for two until KL surprised him with a small package for the win. <strong>My score: 2.75/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="match-6-leon-slater-defeated-liam-slater-in-the-quarterfinal-round-of-the-natural-progression-series-tournament">Match #6: Leon Slater defeated Liam Slater in the quarterfinal round of the Natural Progression Series tournament.</h2>
<p>Both shook hands and hugged as soon as the bell rang. During the match, Leon went for a tope con giro until Liam ran back to the ring; Liam then hit Leon with a chop block and then worked on his opponent’s right knee. Leon came back and then won with a 450 splash. Both men hugged afterwards, and Liam raised Leon’s arm; then, Leon—due to his knee being worked on—was helped to the back by a crewman. <strong>My score: 4.25/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="match-7-maverick-mayhew-omari--mike-bird-defeated-joe-lando-callum-newman--danny-black-and-vaughn-vertigo-keinen-krishna--tu-byt-and-gene-munny--the-sunshine-machine-in-super-mob-smash-12">Match #7: Maverick Mayhew, Omari &amp; Mike Bird defeated Joe Lando, Callum Newman &amp; Danny Black and Vaughn Vertigo, Keinen Krishna &amp; Tu Byt and Gene Munny &amp; the Sunshine Machine in Super Mob Smash 12.</h2>
<p>The teams of three were selected by the fans, two wrestlers started the match and would tag anyone they want, and the winner of the match would get a championship opportunity of his choosing. Mayhew jokingly wanted to team with the rest of CPF until Mayhew was sent to the back because he wasn’t teaming with the three. Also, this was Tu Byt’s debut; he represented North West Strong. Plus, Munny did a Big E-like intro for the Sunshine Machine; as soon as Chuck Mambo and TK Cooper appeared, it was beachball mania as there were beachballs bouncing from the entryway to the rest of the venue.</p>

<p>Moments in this match included Mayhew wanting to fight with the rest of CPF; Munny hitting one of his opponents with the Ainsley Lariat until the rest (all ten of course!) broke up the pin; Munny and Mayhew walking on the top rope like a tightrope while clinging onto Omari and Cooper respectively—while those in the ring were fighting—and then diving onto the rest of their opponents before Omari and Vertigo had dives of their own (Cooper went for a tope suicida, but it was blocked from ringside); Krishna putting the Sunshine Machine in a double crossface while Tu Byt had one of the SM members in an ankle lock; Cooper hitting Krishna with a tope suicida and then Munny hitting him—on the chairs in the audience—with a Cactus Jack elbow drop from the apron; Bird having ¾ of CPF in holds (Lando in an Indian death lock, Black in an abdominal stretch, and Newman in an armbar) until Mayhew rained on his parade by stopping him from putting his CPF colleagues in those holds before Mayhew ended up being used as a weapon by Bird and Krishna; Omari, Mayhew and Newman hitting their opponents with shooting star presses including one at ringside; Munny hitting Black and Newman with a double James Blunt Force Trauma; and Mambo and Black with assisted dives—from Cooper and Newman respectively—to their opponents at ringside. The match ended Bird cleaning house and then hitting Vertigo with a middle rope piledriver for the win. After the match, Bird said that Mayhew and Omari deserve a shot at the Progress Tag Team Championship while he’s going after Spike Trivet for the Progress World Championship. <strong>My score: 3.75/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="match-8-rhio-defeated-skye-smitson-w-lana-austin-and-la-taylor">Match #8: Rhio defeated Skye Smitson (w/ Lana Austin and L.A. Taylor).</h2>
<p>Kanji was scheduled to fight in this match until it was revealed that she was absent due to illness. Before the match started, Lana said that Kanji was scared of fighting her, then performed “Lana-oke” in the ring—singing songs from “Grease” and “Frozen”—until Rhio came into the ring; Rhio said that she knew which member of the Lana Austin Experience she was going to face since Skye was the only member wearing wrestling gear. After Skye hit Rhio with the Smitson Effect for a near fall followed by a fisherman’s buster for two, Lana grabbed Rhio for Skye until Rhio dodged and made Skye knock Lana off the apron; this led to Rhio winning with a package piledriver. After the match, L.A. attacked Rhio, then Millie ran in and hit Skye with a spear until L.A. slammed her. Then, while the Lana Austin Experience was leaving, Taonga appeared and wanted to team with the three until the three had no interest in celebrating with her. <strong>My score: 2.5/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="main-event-dan-moloney-defeated-spike-trivet-w-bullit-in-a-non-title-match">Main event: Dan Moloney defeated Spike Trivet (w/ Bullit) in a non-title match.</h2>
<p>Before the match started, Trivet said that Manchester was “like Sheffield but more [f-bombed] in the head”, then said that Moloney didn’t deserve this match because of how many times he lost—especially to Trivet—and that people like Moloney work for people like him. Moloney went for the Drilla early on until Trivet got to the apron where Moloney knocked him off, and Bullit caught Trivet as if he jumped out of a burning building. Then, at ringside, Moloney had Trivet seated and—after placing a fan’s sign on his chest—chopped him off; he then had a fan hold Trivet down so he could hit his opponent with a running punt. Later on, Trivet hit Moloney with the Swan Woo dropkicks followed by a Rude Awakening, then went for a package piledriver until Moloney hit him with a Last Ride (ala the Undertaker) for two. Near the end, Bullit—behind the referee’s back—hit Moloney with a low blow and tripped him on the apron, leading to Trivet hitting his opponent with a middle rope Codebreaker for two; Moloney then pretended to be tripped by Bullit, leading to the referee and ring crew sending Trivet’s bodyguard to the back. Afterwards, Moloney won after hitting Trivet with the Drilla. Post-match, Moloney—while sitting and then standing on top of Trivet—called out Bullit who then stared at him while helping Trivet to the back. <strong>My score: 3/5</strong></p>

<h1 id="survivor-series-wargames">Survivor Series WarGames</h1>

<p>It’s now time to head to the TD Garden in Boston, Massachusetts in the United States. Cue “War Games” by Black Sabbath as well as “Parasite” by Ozzy Osbourne featuring Zakk Wylde because it’s time to take a look back at Survivor Series…(in a William Regal voice)…WAR GAMES!!!</p>

<p>(Interesting to note, “War Games” by Black Sabbath was also the official theme song of NXT TakeOver: WarGames in 2020.)</p>

<p>It was the first time that WWE’s main roster—Raw and SmackDown—held WarGames matches; one was for the women, and the other was for the men. It was also the third time in Survivor Series history that there weren’t any traditional Survivor Series matches that were part of the pay-per-view/premium live event; 1998 only focused on a tournament that was for the then-vacant WWE Championship (back when WWE was still a “Federation”), and 2002 only focused on the then-brand-new Elimination Chamber.</p>

<p>With the exception of the SmackDown Women’s Championship match that turned out to be a cakewalk for Ronda Rousey as I figured (regardless of how much hell Shotzi gave to both her and Shayna Baszler), the rest of the matches were very good. Out of the five matches that took place that night, both WarGames matches and the one-on-one bout between Finn Bálor and AJ Styles were my favorites.</p>

<p>This wasn’t the first time that Finn Bálor and AJ Styles fought in a one-on-one match. Back in October of 2017 at TLC, Bálor was scheduled to face Bray Wyatt as both “The Demon” and “Sister Abigail” respectively until Wyatt was replaced with AJ Styles because Wyatt had medical issues; both Styles and “The Demon” clashed in the ring, and it ended with Bálor winning the bout. Fast forward to November of 2022 where Styles is back together with the OC and Bálor is with the Judgment Day. To me, it was as good as their first one-on-one match from five years ago; this time, the outcome was much different as Styles would be the victor in this bout.</p>

<p>Onto the WarGames matches, they were as good as the last WarGames matches that I’ve seen back when it was only exclusive for the NXT roster; seeing both Raw and SmackDown superstars compete in this type of match this year was definitely worth the wait. Not only did we see the wrestlers that had WarGames experience in the past (Bianca Belair, Rhea Ripley, Dakota Kai, Iyo Sky, Kevin Owens and Butch) collaborate with those that had their first taste of being a WarGames participant, but also all twenty competitors giving their all inside two rings surrounded by one cage. I can assure you that Dusty Rhodes was smiling from the heavens as soon as he saw those WarGames bouts.</p>

<p>For the women, the storyline heading into this match was Damage CTRL running roughshod on Raw’s women’s roster—as well as SmackDown’s women’s roster in their select appearances—including targeting Bianca Belair for the Raw Women’s Championship after Bayley lost to her a couple times for that belt; other storylines included Mia Yim solving the OC’s “Rhea Ripley problem” as well as the return of someone Bayley attacked two days after Summer Slam. For the men, the storyline heading into this match was whether or not Sami Zayn would be trusted—in the eyes of Jey Uso—as the “honorary Uce” in the Bloodline even after seeing him encounter his best friend Kevin Owens less than 24 hours prior to this event; another storyline was the ongoing rivalry between the Bloodline and the Brawling Brutes stemming back to when the Usos and Solo Sikoa injured one of Sheamus’ arms.</p>

<p>In my honest opinion, both the women and men kicked ass in those matches from how they competed both with and without weapons to focusing on the storylines that came into play. Will next year’s WarGames matches be as good as those as well as the past WarGames matches that we’ve seen in the WWE? I sure hope so. Besides, seeing NXT’s WarGames matches as well as similar ones such as—most recently—ICW’s Super Smokin’ Thunderbowl at Barred II prior to seeing Raw and SmackDown’s WarGames matches have indeed paid off.</p>

<p>Here are the match results from Boston…</p>

<h2 id="match-1-becky-lynch-alexa-bliss-asuka-michin-mia-yim--bianca-belair-defeated-rhea-ripley-nikki-cross--damage-ctrl-in-wargames">Match #1: Becky Lynch, Alexa Bliss, Asuka, “Michin” Mia Yim &amp; Bianca Belair defeated Rhea Ripley, Nikki Cross &amp; Damage CTRL in WarGames.</h2>
<p>NXT’s Alicia Taylor was the ring announcer for this match. Bianca and Dakota Kai started off the match, followed by—in order—Iyo Sky, Asuka, Nikki (with kendo sticks, trashcan lids, handcuffs, and her own jacket), Alexa, Bayley (with two ladders and a table), Mia (with three trashcans), Rhea and finally Becky. Highlights included Nikki diving from the top of the cage and onto Bianca and Asuka who were fighting Dakota and Iyo; Bianca, Mia, Alexa and Asuka moving in stereo—ala the Cars—with superplexes to Bayley, Dakota, Nikki and Iyo respectively (Asuka’s superplex was actually a German superplex); Asuka spitting blue mist in Rhea’s face; Iyo hitting Bianca and Mia with a moonsault from the top of the cage; and Nikki attempting to handcuff Alexa to the cage until Alexa cuffed herself to the “twisted sister.” The match ended with Bianca hitting Bayley with the KOD into the steel mesh while Becky hit Dakota and Iyo with a diving leg drop from the top of the cage and through the table for the win. <strong>My score: 4/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="match-2-aj-styles-w-luke-gallows-and-karl-anderson-defeated-finn-bálor-w-dominik-mysterio-and-damian-priest">Match #2: AJ Styles (w/ Luke Gallows and Karl Anderson) defeated Finn Bálor (w/ Dominik Mysterio and Damian Priest).</h2>
<p>Bálor wore an all-black mask to the ring, and Styles wore a gas mask that’s part of the OC’s logo. Styles worked on Bálor’s left leg early in the match. During the bout, Priest distracted the referee which allowed Mysterio to trip Styles on the apron; this led to Gallows and Anderson fighting the Judgment Day members at ringside and into the crowd, with Styles throwing Mysterio into the crowd as the managers fought away from the ringside area. Both Styles and Bálor traded signature maneuvers as well as stole signature maneuvers later on; Bálor was unable to hit the Styles Clash (which was countered with a Calf Crusher attempt) but was able to hit Styles with an ushigoroshi (one of Styles’ signatures), and Styles hit him with a moonsault into a neckbreaker/elbow drop combo (one of Bálor’s signatures). After Bálor got out of the Calf Crusher by bouncing Styles’ head off the mat like a basketball, Styles came back and won with the Phenomenal Forearm. <strong>My score: 4/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="match-3-ronda-rousey-w-shayna-baszler-defeated-shotzi-to-retain-the-smackdown-womens-championship">Match #3: Ronda Rousey (w/ Shayna Baszler) defeated Shotzi to retain the SmackDown Women’s Championship.</h2>
<p>Shotzi wore KISS-inspired gear. During the match, Shotzi—after hitting Ronda with a botched tornado DDT on the apron—bounced off of her opponent and hit Shayna with Sliced Bread, then threw the two into the audience and hit them with a crossbody from the barricade, causing them to collapse into three fans seated at ringside. Ronda came back and hit Shotzi with Piper’s Pit before making her submit to an armbar. <strong>My score: 2/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="match-4-austin-theory-defeated-bobby-lashley-and-seth-freakin-rollins-to-become-the-new-wwe-united-states-champion">Match #4: Austin Theory defeated Bobby Lashley and Seth “Freakin’” Rollins to become the new WWE United States Champion.</h2>
<p>Even though Theory’s theme song was still playing, his entrance video was replaced with an advertisement for Beyblade Burst QuadDrive for some reason. As soon as the bell rang, Lashley clotheslined Theory out of the ring, as did Rollins ten seconds or so later. Lashley fought Theory at the timekeeper’s area until Rollins hit him with a flying knee from the apron before Theory fought back and attacked the two with steel stairs. Later on, Rollins hit Lashley with a tope suicida, Theory with the same maneuver, and Lashley with it again before throwing Theory into the same area as Lashley and hitting the two with a tope con giro. Towards the end, Theory attempted to hit Rollins with a Pedigree (one of Rollins’ signatures), and Rollins attempted to hit Theory with the A-Town Down (Theory’s finisher) until Lashley put the two in a double Hurt Lock; Rollins fought out of the hold and took down the two, then used Theory as a springboard and stomped Lashley. Then, after Lashley was sent into a corner (and ended up with some cuts on his face afterwards), Rollins hit Theory with a superplex and went for a Falcon Arrow until Lashley hit him with a spear on the way down, leading to Theory pinning Rollins for the win. <strong>My score: 3.75/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="main-event-the-bloodline-w-paul-heyman-defeated-kevin-owens-drew-mcintyre--the-brawling-brutes-in-wargames">Main event: The Bloodline (w/ Paul Heyman) defeated Kevin Owens, Drew McIntyre &amp; the Brawling Brutes in WarGames.</h2>
<p>Heyman had a boot on his left leg as he came with the Bloodline. Butch and Jey Uso started off the match, followed by—in order—Ridge Holland, Sami Zayn (after Roman Reigns told Jimmy Uso to wait), McIntyre, Jimmy Uso (with three tables), Owens (with steel chairs), Solo Sikoa, Sheamus and finally Roman Reigns. Highlights from this match included Butch working on Jey’s right hand; Zayn and Jey arguing (even with Jimmy intervening at one point); and Owens, McIntyre and the Brawling Brutes giving all five of their opponents more than 50 “Beats of the Bodhran.” Near the end, Zayn stopped the referee from performing the three count while Owens pinned Reigns, then Jimmy attempted to hit Owens with a superkick until Owens blocked it before Zayn—who had Reigns watch—hit him with a low blow followed by the Helluva Kick; then, Jimmy hit Owens with a top rope splash for the win. After the match, Reigns and Zayn hugged, then the hatchet was buried as Jey gave Zayn a hug before all five members of the Bloodline celebrated together. <strong>My score: 4/5</strong></p>

<h1 id="icw-fight-club">ICW Fight Club</h1>

<p>Returning to the United Kingdom, we head to the Northumbria University Students Union in Newcastle Upon Tyne, England for an episode of ICW Fight Club.</p>

<p>Four matches, that were buildups to Fear &amp; Loathing XIV, took place on this week’s episode. Out of the four matches that took place, my favorite would go to the opening bout between Leyton Buzzard and Ian Skinner. Like is tag team partner Charlie Vyce in last week’s episode, Skinner also had a strong showing as a singles competitor—and, like Vyce, he’s no stranger to fighting in singles action—this week. Plus, like Craig Anthony when he took on the aforementioned Vyce on last week’s episode, Buzzard also had a good warmup heading into F&amp;L in his bout. Seeing both Buzzard and Anthony pick up wins was a great way to build their momentums heading into that event, and this match was indeed a good way to kick off this week’s episode besides a great back-and-forth bout.</p>

<p>Here are the match results from Newcastle Upon Tyne…</p>

<h2 id="match-1-leyton-buzzard-defeated-ian-skinner-w-charlie-vyce">Match #1: Leyton Buzzard defeated Ian Skinner (w/ Charlie Vyce).</h2>
<p>Skinner made a Lykos Gym mistake during the match as he shouted out “Brainbuster!” before Buzzard countered the brainbuster with a suplex for two. Near the end, Skinner gave Buzzard joint manipulation until Buzzard came back with a superkick and the Buzzkiller before putting him in a Scorpion Death Lock; Skinner grabbed the bottom rope for the break until Buzzard hit him with a second Buzzkiller followed by the X Marks the Spot for the win. <strong>My score: 3.75/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="match-2-thatcher-wright-defeated-levi-if-wright-won-he-would-be-inserted-into-the-ladder-matchfor-a-future-shot-at-the-icw-zero-g-championshipat-fear--loathing-xiv">Match #2: Thatcher Wright defeated Levi; if Wright won, he would be inserted into the ladder match—for a future shot at the ICW Zero-G Championship—at Fear &amp; Loathing XIV.</h2>
<p>Before the match started, Wright wanted the fans to thank Margaret Thatcher for what she did for their hometown; the fans booed and chanted “[F-bomb] the Tories” instead. He then blindsided his opponent seconds before the bell rang. During the match, Wright was reading from his Margaret Thatcher book while kicking and stomping Levi down until Levi—after Thatcher handed the book to the referee—fought back. Towards the end, Charlie Vyce and Ian Skinner appeared, and Skinner slid the book to Thatcher who then struck Levi with it before pinning him for the win. <strong>My score: 1.5/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="match-3-kasey-defeated-martin-macalistair-in-almost-three-minutes">Match #3: Kasey defeated Martin MacAlistair in almost three minutes.</h2>
<p>Kasey was originally scheduled to compete against Lizzy Evo, but she was absent; Kasey mocked her for not being in attendance, then challenged anyone—including the medic and merchandise seller—to fight her. MacAlistair—who was 0-26 heading into the match according to Simon Cassidy (thus making it feel like I’m watching AEW with the win-loss record being mentioned)—answered the challenge, and Kasey fought him; he was afraid to hit her during the match, and this gave Kasey the upper hand from start to finish as well as win with Off With Her Head. Afterwards, Kasey sent a message to Molly Spartan by taking off the She Wolves t-shirt and stomping it in the middle of the ring. <strong>No score.</strong></p>

<h2 id="main-event-jack-jester-defeated-rory-coyle-in-an-insane-rules-match">Main event: Jack Jester defeated Rory Coyle in an Insane Rules match.</h2>
<p>Coyle came with a bag of weapons as well as a video camera; inside the bag were a kendo stick, two sets of jumper cables, videotapes and a VCR. Both Coyle and Jester took turns using the camera while fighting including having a fan hold the camera for the two, and Jester taking a page out of Logan Paul’s playbook by fighting and filming at the same time. After Jester hit Coyle with the VCR and then slammed him onto the tapes, he struck Coyle with an exploding cassette—with red dust flying everywhere—for the win. After the match, BT Gunn appeared and Jester dared him to get in the ring. Gunn came in, but then got out after it looked like the two were getting ready to fight. Then, Sha Samuels came and threw Gunn back in the ring, and then he and Jester fought Gunn out of the ring before celebrating. <strong>My score: 2.5/5</strong></p>

<h1 id="nxt">NXT</h1>

<p>Returning to the United States, we head to Orlando, Florida for an episode of NXT.</p>

<p>The male and female participants for the two Iron Survivor Challenge matches at NXT Deadline were made this week, courtesy of a panel consisting of WWE Hall of Famers Shawn Michaels, Road Dogg, Sean Waltman, Alundra Blayze and Molly Holly; four were announced for the men’s match, and four were announced for the women’s match.</p>

<p>The four male wrestlers for their Iron Survivor Challenge match will be Carmelo Hayes, JD McDonagh, Grayson Waller and Joe Gacy, and the fifth competitor will be the winner of a wildcard triple threat match (taking place next week); the three attempting to qualify for this match are Von Wagner, Axiom and Andre Chase.</p>

<p>As for the women’s Iron Survivor Challenge match, the four female wrestlers will be Zoey Stark, Cora Jade, Roxanne Perez, Kiana James and—like the men’s match—the winner of a wildcard triple threat match (also taking place next week); the three attempting to qualify for this match are Wendy Choo, Fallon Henley and Indi Hartwell.
I don’t have any predictions for either Iron Survivor Challenge match yet, but I do like the choices that were made for those two bouts. I’m glad to see Hayes, McDonagh, Waller and Gacy in this match mainly because of how much they accomplished especially during the short-lived multicolored “2.0” era—especially Hayes who won gold on NXT, ditto McDonagh during his time on NXT UK—and I believe that we’ll see Axiom qualify for this match next week.</p>

<p>As for the women, I agree with who was selected to be in this match, especially Kiana who appears to be getting a push as of late even before her rivalry with Fallon Henley. Speaking of Fallon, I’m torn on seeing either her or Indi qualifying for that match next week; part of me would like to see the Kiana/Fallon rivalry take part of the Iron Survivor Challenge at Deadline, but the other part of me sees Indi getting a push while focusing on her character where she’s proving the new additions to the women’s roster—the hard way—what she’s capable of.</p>

<p>Eight matches took place this week, and there were three matches that I enjoyed. One was the opening match between Roxanne Perez and Indi Hartwell; both women had a strong showing in this match and proving that they deserve to be making names for themselves in Deadline, even though we didn’t see Indi take part of the qualifying match yet per se.</p>

<p>Another match that I liked was between Javier Bernal and Axiom. Axiom has been on a roll ever since he jumped to NXT before his tenure as A-Kid came to a close, and Bernal also had a good showing not just in competition but also on building his cocky heel character.</p>

<p>Lastly, I also enjoyed the match between JD McDonagh and Julius Creed. It was another good bout that McDonagh competed in, even with his sinister heel character coming into play; the same goes for Julius who continues to have a good showing in singles competition and has proved it even before his ambulance match with Damon Kemp at Halloween Havoc occurred.
Here are the NXT results from Orlando…</p>

<h2 id="match-1-roxanne-perez-defeated-indi-hartwell">Match #1: Roxanne Perez defeated Indi Hartwell.</h2>
<p>As soon as the match began, Roxanne offered a handshake until Indi slapped her hand away. After Indi booted Roxanne down, Roxanne kicked her away and then—after clubbing her in the back to help herself jump over her opponent—won with the Pop Rox. My score: 3.5/5</p>

<h2 id="match-2-dijak-defeated-dante-chen-in-almost-four-minutes">Match #2: Dijak defeated Dante Chen in almost four minutes.</h2>
<p>Chen had a bloody mouth during the match. Dijak wore down Chen with a sleeper, then won with the Feast Your Eyes. After the match, Dijak said that what he did was “an example of hard justice”, then vowed to eviscerate anyone that gets in his way—calling out Wes Lee, Chen, Apollo Crews and Bron Breakker—and bring them to his “justice.” My score: 1/5
Match #3: Grayson Waller defeated Duke Hudson (w/ Andre Chase and Thea Hail). Earlier, both Waller and Hudson were grabbing each other by the hair until Chase told Hudson to stop cheating. Near the end, Hudson attempted to boot Waller, but missed and almost hit Thea; after Hudson calmed Thea down, he came back in the ring where Waller won with a through-the-ropes cutter. <strong>My score: 1/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="match-4-kiana-james-defeated-fallon-henley-w-josh-briggs-and-brooks-jensen">Match #4: Kiana James defeated Fallon Henley (w/ Josh Briggs and Brooks Jensen).</h2>
<p>Fallon’s left arm was worked on. After Fallon fought back, she chased Kiana until Kiana threw her purse at her before sending her shoulder first into a corner and winning with the 401k. <strong>My score: 2.5/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="match-5-axiom-defeated-javier-bernal">Match #5: Axiom defeated Javier Bernal.</h2>
<p>This match was made after Bernal was announcing who he wanted to fight, even with a long list of enemies that also included Elon Musk. Axiom wore a green and gold outfit that was a tribute to Jason David Frank, an actor best known as Tommy in the “Power Rangers” franchise whom we lost recently. Axiom’s right leg was worked on. After Bernal dodged the Golden Ratio and hit Axiom with a DDT for two, he climbed to the top rope until Axiom hit him with a superplex and the Golden Ratio for the win. <strong>My score: 3.5/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="match-6-julius-creed-w-brutus-creed-defeated-jd-mcdonagh-by-disqualification">Match #6: Julius Creed (w/ Brutus Creed) defeated JD McDonagh by disqualification.</h2>
<p>Indus Sher appeared during the match. After McDonagh hit Julius with an Asai moonsault, he attempted to work on one of his legs (like he has to Axiom) until Julius powered him away; McDonagh then grabbed a steel chair and attempted to hit Julius with it until Sanga shoved Julius out of the way—giving Julius the DQ win—and took the bullet. After the match, Veer Mahaan and Sanga approached the Creed Brothers (as well as Ivy Nile who checked on Julius). <strong>My score: 3.5/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="match-7-von-wagner-w-mr-stone-defeated-malik-blade-in-almost-three-minutes">Match #7: Von Wagner (w/ Mr. Stone) defeated Malik Blade in almost three minutes.</h2>
<p>This match was made after Wagner refused to hang out with Blade and Edris Enofé and attacked them, and then tore what was the last sweater vest Blade’s father wore before his passing. After Blade—who brought that torn sweater vest to the ring—surprised Wagner with a bodyslam, he went for a frog splash, but it was blocked; this led to Wagner winning with a Death Valley Bomb. Afterwards, Enofé ran in to stop Wagner from continuing to attack Blade; Enofé was beaten down by Wagner until Odyssey Jones ran in and fought him out of the ring. <strong>My score: 1/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="main-event-toxic-attraction-defeated-nikkita-lyons-kayden-carter--katana-chance">Main event: Toxic Attraction defeated Nikkita Lyons, Kayden Carter &amp; Katana Chance.</h2>
<p>This was supposed to be the fifth match of the episode until Zoey Stark attacked Nikkita at the entryway; Nikkita ended up competing with a bandaged right knee afterwards. Towards the end, Nikkita hit Jacy Jayne with a leg split leg drop until Gigi Dolin broke up the pin. Then, Mandy Rose—who hit Katana with the Kiss By the Rose at ringside—distracted Nikkita from the apron, and Nikkita attempted to kick her off but collapsed due to the injured knee; this allowed Gigi and Jacy to win with a leg sweep/heel kick combo. After the match, Zoey appeared on the stage and taunted Nikkita. <strong>My score: 2/5</strong></p>

<h1 id="nxt-lvl-up">NXT: LVL UP</h1>

<p>Staying in Orlando, we wrap things up with an episode of NXT: LVL UP.</p>

<p>Both the opener and closer were my favorite matches of this episode. The opener was Oro Mensah taking on Myles Borne, and the two gave us a great way to kick off this week’s episode; Borne is still giving his opponents a good run for their money (as well as looking for his next win), and Mensah continues to give his opponents a strong showing just like he did on NXT UK as well as his select NXT appearances when he was renamed from “Oliver Carter” to “Oro Mensah.”</p>

<p>The closer was Thea Hail taking on Sol Ruca, and those two wrestlers definitely gave us a good way to end this episode on a high note; Sol continues to be impressive in her fighting ability even while attempting to close in on another win, and the same goes for Thea even with her own high-octane energy coming into play.</p>

<p>Here are the NXT: LVL UP results from Orlando…</p>

<h2 id="match-1-oro-mensah-defeated-myles-borne">Match #1: Oro Mensah defeated Myles Borne.</h2>
<p>After Borne picked up a two after a sleeper into a northern lights suplex, Mensah came back and won with a running heel kick. Both men hugged afterwards. <strong>My score: 3/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="match-2-stacks-w-tony-dangelo-defeated-tavion-heights-in-four-minutes">Match #2: Stacks (w/ Tony D’Angelo) defeated Tavion Heights in four minutes.</h2>
<p>This was Heights’ debut. Stacks won with a Curbstomp-like knee drop. <strong>My score: 1.5/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="main-event-thea-hail-w-andre-chase-and-duke-hudson-defeated-sol-ruca">Main event: Thea Hail (w/ Andre Chase and Duke Hudson) defeated Sol Ruca.</h2>
<p>After Thea fought out of Sol’s surfboard and fought back including hitting her with a senton for two, Sol went for a rollup until Thea countered with a rollup of her own for the win. Post-match, Chase U showed respect to Sol. <strong>My score: 3/5</strong></p>

<h1 id="next-time">Next time…</h1>

<p>The usual three and a belated Progress recap or two. Oh, and yes, I have a handful of wXw events to go through once I get chapters 144 and 145 out of the way…unless I’m jinxing myself for some reason…</p>

<p>For my newsletters as well as any articles that are on the Wrestling With Johners website, the website is wrestlingwithjohners.com/articles</p>

<p>For just my newsletters on the WWJ website, it is wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/pro-darin/</p>

<p>Thanks for reading! Feel free to comment! I’ll see you next time!</p>

<p>(Photos shown in the newsletter are from WWE, Progress and ICW.)</p>]]></content><author><name>pro-darin</name></author><category term="articles" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Issue 49 Shows of December 3-9, 2022</title><link href="/articles/2022/12/27/Issue-49-Shows-of-December-3-9,-2022/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Issue 49 Shows of December 3-9, 2022" /><published>2022-12-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-12-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/2022/12/27/Issue%2049%20Shows%20of%20December%203-9,%202022</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/2022/12/27/Issue-49-Shows-of-December-3-9,-2022/"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png" alt="pro darin" class="restrict-width" /></p>

<h1 id="progress-chapter-144-the-deadly-viper-tour--codename-snake-charmer">Progress Chapter 144: The Deadly Viper Tour – Codename: Snake Charmer</h1>

<p>Let’s kick things off with a belated Progress recap!</p>

<p>The 144th chapter of Progress took place at the Tramshed in Cardiff, Wales in the United Kingdom; it also served as the tail end of the Deadly Viper Tour. Hosting the event was Session Moth Martina who took over for Simon Miller that day, and she did very well doing the ring announcing duties as well as have fun, drinking games and all.</p>

<p>Eight matches were on the card for this chapter, including three championship matches; one of the championship bouts that took place involved tables.</p>

<p><a href="/assets/posts/2022-12-27/deadly_viper_cardiff.jpg" class="restrict-width">progress cardiff</a></p>

<p>There were two matches that were my favorites on that chapter. One was the Progress Women’s Championship match between Kanji and Millie McKenzie. Millie came into this match with a win streak being built ever since she returned to Progress a couple chapters ago. Kanji entered the match showing and proving what it took to be a fighting champion. Both women were definitely impressive in this bout, and in the end, it was Kanji who would retain the belt.</p>

<p>The other match that was also my favorite was the reunited FSU—Mark Andrews and Eddie Dennis—taking on the team of Man Like Dereiss and Omari. Bear with me since I’m almost two years into watching Progress…this was the first time I’ve seen FSU in action (not counting footage of the teamwork done by Andrews and Dennis), and it was amazing. It was great back and forth action between two teams, one that was reunited and another that consisted of two wrestlers that teamed together for the first time. In the end, it was FSU who was victorious.</p>

<p>Here are the match results from Cardiff…</p>

<h2 id="match-1-lykos-gym-defeated-kidd-bandit--warhorse">Match #1: Lykos Gym defeated Kidd Bandit &amp; Warhorse.</h2>
<p>This was the debut of KB &amp; Warhorse. Warhorse had Kid Lykos in a Scorpion Death Lock, and was able to hit a charging Kid Lykos II with a back body drop until KL raked his eyes to get out of the hold; KB tagged in and they hit KL with a corkscrew splash for two while their partner Warhorse hit KL2 with a tope suicida, then—behind the referee’s back—KL2 hit KB with a baking tray and nailed a middle rope Spanish Fly, then KL hit them with the Casanova kick for the win. <strong>My score: 2.25/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="match-2-raven-creed-defeated-taonga">Match #2: Raven Creed defeated Taonga.</h2>
<p>After Taonga blocked the Hellmouth and Raven blocked the I’m Prettier, Taonga hit Raven with a reverse DDT for two, then Raven lifted her up and—despite being elbowed by Taonga—hit her with the Hellmouth for the win. <strong>My score: 3/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="match-3-lana-austin--la-taylor-defeated-rho--jetta">Match #3: Lana Austin &amp; L.A. Taylor defeated Rho &amp; Jetta.</h2>
<p>Lana sang “Let It Go” from the movie “Frozen” before the match. The team of Lana and L.A. won after L.A. hit Jetta with a Sky High (ala D’Lo Brown) and Lana picked up the scraps by tagging in and pinning her for the win. <strong>My score: 1.5/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="match-4-kanji-defeated-millie-mckenzie-to-retain-the-progress-womens-championship">Match #4: Kanji defeated Millie McKenzie to retain the Progress Women’s Championship.</h2>
<p>Millie surprised Kanji with rollups for two counts in the beginning. After Millie missed on a spear attempt and crashed out of the ring, Kanji hit her—and a couple crewmen—with a crossbody from the apron; as soon as the action returned to the ring, Millie threw Kanji off the top rope and hit her with a spear for a near fall. Kanji put Millie in a full nelson and then transitioned it into a triangle choke until Millie pinned her for two and hit her with a second spear before Kanji put her foot on the bottom rope. The two then went back and forth with strikes and pin attempts, even with exhaustion coming into play, until Kanji won with a discus elbow.</p>

<p>Both wrestlers hugged afterwards util Lana and L.A. ran in and attacked the two; Rhio ran in until Taonga evened the odds before Raven Creen ran in. Taonga and Lana were fought out of the ring, and Millie hit L.A. with a spear, then Kanji said that she, Rhio, Millie and Raven had enough of the Lana Austin Experience’s bullshit and challenged them to a four-on-four tag match for the next chapter. (Later on, Raven backed out of the match due to having bad luck with the LAE.) <strong>My score: 4.75/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="match-5-fsu-defeated-man-like-dereiss--omari">Match #5: FSU defeated Man Like Dereiss &amp; Omari.</h2>
<p>This was the first time that FSU competed together since 2019, and it was Mark Andrews’ first Progress match since February 2020. Omari hit Eddie Dennis with a double underhook DDT until Andrews broke up the pin with the Fall To Pieces (shooting star press), then Dennis pinned Omari until Dereiss broke it up with the Four Fiddy; then, Dennis went for the Gunslinger until Omari rolled him up for two and then hit him with a leg lariat and gut wrench powerbomb for another two. Dereiss tagged in and he and Omari hit Dennis with a 3D until Andrews broke up the pin, then Dereiss attempted to hit Dennis with the Four Fiddy, but missed; FSU then hit Dereiss with a Severed Bridge/jumping heel kick combo followed by a Neckstop Driver/double stomp combo for the win. Both teams showed respect to each other afterwards. <strong>My score: 4.75/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="match-6-nico-angelo-defeated-joe-lando-in-the-quarterfinal-round-of-the-natural-progression-series-tournament">Match #6: Nico Angelo defeated Joe Lando in the quarterfinal round of the Natural Progression Series tournament.</h2>
<p>Tate Mayfairs joined Olie Spring and SoCal Val on commentary; he was scheduled to compete against Tom Dawkins, but Dawkins was absent. Angelo forearmed away a tope attempt from Lando until Lando knocked him off the apron and was able to hit him with the tope suicida. The end of the match saw Lando hit Angelo with the Matrix Cutter followed by an Olympic Slam into a brainbuster for a near fall (P.S.: Happy birthday Kurt Angle!), and then Angelo blocked a shooting star press before pinning Lando for the win. After the match, Mayfairs confronted Angelo who almost struck him. <strong>My score: 4/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="match-7-the-sunshine-machine-defeated-the-greedy-souls-in-a-tag-team-tables-elimination-match-to-retain-the-progress-tag-team-championship">Match #7: The Sunshine Machine defeated the Greedy Souls in a tag team tables elimination match to retain the Progress Tag Team Championship.</h2>
<p>TK Cooper was unable to powerbomb Brendan White off the apron and through the table, even with Chuck Mambo’s help; a minute or so later, Mambo was shoved off the apron by White and put through the table, eliminating him. Later on, Danny Jones catapulted Cooper into White who went for a Black Hole Slam until Cooper countered it with a Canadian Destroyer through the table, eliminating White; both Mambo and White were still fighting despite being eliminated. After Mambo hit Jones with a reverse piledriver on the apron and then he and Cooper fought away a chair equipped White on the stage at the entryway, Mambo hit Jones with an assisted splash—from Cooper—from the stage and through the table for the win. Both teams bumped fists afterwards until Lykos Gym ran in and attacked both teams, using both the belts and baking trays as weapons; the two then brandished a pair of scissors and cut one of Mambo’s braids off, then ran to the stage and celebrated with the braid as if it were the FIFA World Cup trophy. <strong>My score: 3/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="main-event-spike-trivet-w-bullit-defeated-mike-bird-to-retain-the-progress-world-championship">Main event: Spike Trivet (w/ Bullit) defeated Mike Bird to retain the Progress World Championship.</h2>
<p>Before the match started, Bullit had Session Moth Martina announce Trivet as “The Prince of Wales.” During the match, Bird blocked the Birthright and he and Trivet exchanged suplexes; Trivet had Saito suplexes, and Bird had German suplexes. Bird knocked Bullit off the apron before, when the referee wasn’t looking, Trivet hit him with a low blow and the Birthright for a near fall; Trivet then hit him with a Swan Woo until the second Swan Woo knocked out the referee. Trivet hit Bird with another low blow and went for a package piledriver until Bird countered with a LeBell Lock until Bullit broke up the hold and hit him with a chokeslam; Trivet pinned Bird for two, and then put him in the Ascot which Bird powered out of until Trivet hit him with a package piledriver for a near fall and then incapacitated him with the Ascot for the win. After the match, Trivet and Bird attempted to attack Bird some more until Dan Moloney ran in and chased the two out of the ring, and stood on Trivet’s belt before the champion and bodyguard left; then, Moloney stayed in the ring and showed respect to Bird. <strong>My score: 3.75/5</strong></p>

<h1 id="icw-fight-club">ICW Fight Club</h1>

<p>Staying in United Kingdom, we’re heading to the Northumbria University Students Union in Newcastle Upon Tyne, England for an episode of ICW Fight Club.</p>

<p><a href="/assets/posts/2022-12-27/icw_fight_club.jpg" class="restrict-width">icw fight club</a></p>

<p>Four matches took place this week on Fight Club, and my favorite match of the episode was another match that was a warmup prior to Fear &amp; Loathing XIV; it involved Stevie James and Craig Anthony who—along with Leyton Buzzard—were scheduled to fight Kez Evans for the ICW World Heavyweight Championship at that event. The warmup matches prior to that championship bout have been amazing so far, and this includes this match between James and Anthony. Those two fought tooth and nail as if they were already fighting for gold prior to F&amp;L, and in the end, it was “The Natural” Anthony who was the winner of this bout. Seeing those warmup matches that featured those two wrestlers, as well as Buzzard and Evans, definitely showed that those four were ready for F&amp;L.</p>

<p>Here are the match results from Newcastle Upon Tyne…</p>

<h2 id="match-1-saqib-ali--andy-wild-defeated-coach-trip--jason-reed">Match #1: Saqib Ali &amp; Andy Wild defeated Coach Trip &amp; Jason Reed.</h2>
<p>Ali and Wild had a DX tribute before the match, with Ali posing like Shawn Michaels and Wild posing like Triple H. Almost one minute after the match began, it looked like that Reed and Wild would go at it until Reed decided to tag in his coach. Ali countered the Club Deck with a stunner before tagging in Wild who cleaned house and then hit his opponents with the Strowman Express at ringside. Then, Reed threw a chair to Trip who used it to block Wild’s Dad Bomb before Wild recovered and chased Reed out of the ring with the chair; Wild then hit Trip with the chair before Ali won with a Claymore. <strong>My score: 2/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="match-2-craig-anthony-defeated-the-outlaw-stevie-james">Match #2: Craig Anthony defeated “The Outlaw” Stevie James.</h2>
<p>Both wrestlers fought at ringside earlier where James hit Anthony with a Death Valley Driver on the apron and then hit him with a tope suicida. Towards the end, Anthony hit James with a back superplex, and then went for a snap moonsault until James countered with a superkick for two; Anthony came back with a roundhouse kick before winning with a pumphandle driver. After the match, James said that Anthony winning won’t happen again at Fear &amp; Loathing XIV, vowing to win the ICW World Heavyweight Championship before he and Anthony shook hands. <strong>My score: 3.75/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="match-3-glasgow-grindhouse-defeated-grant-mcivor--eddie-castle-w-adm-to-retain-the-icw-tag-team-championship">Match #3: Glasgow Grindhouse defeated Grant McIvor &amp; Eddie Castle (w/ ADM) to retain the ICW Tag Team Championship.</h2>
<p>This match was made after Lou King Sharp and Krieger saved Sha Samuels from K.O.E who attacked him during an episode of “The Polo Lounge” with “Jackie Polo” and Denise. Plus, this match was scheduled to be a non-title match until Glasgow Grindhouse decided to prove to be fighting champions prior to Fear &amp; Loathing XIV. Near the end, Dylan Thorn attacked ADM at the entryway, and it got the attention of McIvor and Castle until Krieger threw Sharp out of the ring and into the two. Glasgow Grindhouse then won after hitting McIvor with the Director’s Cut (wheelbarrow slam/middle rope bulldog combo). After the match, Moxie Malone came into the ring with a chain until McIvor and Castle attacked the distracted champions; then, Angel Hayze appeared and told Moxie to pay attention to her and not her “backup plan” in the form of Sharp and Krieger who fought McIvor and Castle to the back. <strong>My score: 2.5/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="main-event-moxie-malone-defeated-angel-hayze-in-a-newcastle-street-fight">Main event: Moxie Malone defeated Angel Hayze in a Newcastle Street Fight.</h2>
<p>Both wrestlers fought into the crowd and into the student lounge during the match where Moxie threw a fan’s drink at Angel, Angel fought with a trashcan, and both fought with a beanbag. As soon as the two left the lounge, there was a moment straight out of MTV’s “Jackass” as Angel put Moxie in a shopping cart and spun her into the wall before Moxie blinded her with some hand sanitizer. As soon as both Moxie and Angel brought the action back into the ring, ADM fought Dylan Thorn to the ringside area, and then tripped Angel which allowed Moxie to hit her with a neckbreaker for two; ADM then went after Angel until Thorn fought him before Moxie hit him with a chair. Then, ADM hit Angel with a chokeslam backbreaker, and Moxie incapacitated her opponent with a sleeper/bodyscissors combo for the win. After the match, Moxie threw Thorn back in the ring where ADM hit him with a chokeslam backbreaker and vowed to take away his career at Fear &amp; Loathing XIV. <strong>My score: 3/5</strong></p>

<h1 id="nxt">NXT</h1>

<p>We now head to Orlando, Florida in the United States for an episode of NXT.</p>

<p>Two more matches were made for Deadline; unfortunately, the Creed Brothers vs. Indus Sher wasn’t one of them because Julius Creed wasn’t cleared to compete. Perhaps we’ll see them clash next week or the following on NXT?</p>

<p>Onto the matches that WILL take place at Deadline…one will be a one-on-one match between Alba Fyre and Isla Dawn; this was made after Isla appeared and cost Alba the NXT Women’s Championship that Mandy Rose retained not too long ago.</p>

<p>The other will be for the NXT Tag Team Championship. This week, Pretty Deadly hosted a segment known as “A Real Christmas Story” which was their own rendition of “The Night Before Christmas” talking about not having any more teams going after them for the belts. As soon as they wrapped up their story, another team approached the two in the form of SmackDown’s Xavier Woods and Kofi Kingston, the New Day. Woods and Kingston told Elton Prince and Kit Wilson that the New Day was one of the teams that didn’t lose to the NXT Tag Team Champions yet, and this led to a brawl where we saw Prince thrown into a Christmas tree, and of course both him and Wilson being hit by gift boxes.</p>

<p>Not only does this bring a Worlds Collide feel to Deadline, but this is definitely a good challenge for the rising tag team that continues to reign NXT’s tag team division courtesy of a team from WWE’s main roster.</p>

<p><a href="/assets/posts/2022-12-27/nxt_2.0.jpg" class="restrict-width">nxt</a></p>

<p>Overshadowing a slew of short matches were the opener and closer that served as qualifying matches, in forms of triple threat matches, to determine who would participate in the Iron Survivor Challenge matches at Deadline. On the women’s side, we saw Indi Hartwell, Wendy Choo and Fallon Henley go at it for the spot. Even though it looked like the three rushed through a good amount of the match prior to “The Grayson Waller Show” (with Waller’s ISC opponents as his guests) that served as the conclusion of this episode, but I still thought it was a good closing bout.</p>

<p>As for the men’s qualifying match that kicked off this week’s episode, it was my favorite match of the night; in this match were Von Wagner, Axiom and Andre Chase. Last week, I predicted that Axiom would qualify for the Iron Survivor Challenge match mainly because Wagner has already fought Breakker (and I doubted that we would see an ongoing rivalry between Breakker and Wagner anytime soon) and Chase U has been having bad luck as of late as we’ve seen lately. That prediction came true this week as Axiom was able to not let the size advantage from Wagner throw him off track as well as what Chase had in store for the two.</p>

<p>Here are the NXT results from Orlando…</p>

<h2 id="match-1-axiom-defeated-von-wagner-w-mr-stone-and-andre-chase-w-duke-hudson-and-thea-hail-in-a-triple-threat-match-to-qualify-for-the-iron-survivor-challenge">Match #1: Axiom defeated Von Wagner (w/ Mr. Stone) and Andre Chase (w/ Duke Hudson and Thea Hail) in a triple threat match to qualify for the Iron Survivor Challenge.</h2>
<p>Backstage before the match, Hudson and Thea said that they had Chase’s back, and Chase vowed to give his opponents a “Chase University sized ass whooping.” Near the end, Wagner went for a Death Valley Bomb, but Axiom countered with a sleeper/bodyscissors combo and then put him in a triangle choke; Wagner powered out of the hold and hit him with a powerbomb onto Chase. Wagner then hit Axiom with the Death Valley Bomb, and then Chase hit Wagner and Axiom with—respectively—a DDT/reverse DDT combo, then hit Wagner with a top rope crossbody; then, Chase rolled out of the ring which allowed Axiom to hit Wagner with the Golden Ratio. <strong>My score: 3.75/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="match-2-bryson-montana-vs-javier-bernal-never-took-place-at-all">Match #2: Bryson Montana vs. Javier Bernal never took place at all.</h2>
<p>Indus Sher ran in and attacked Montana, then Bernal was heading to the ring until he pretended to have a leg injury and left. Then, Veer Mahaan and Sanga declined the Creed Brothers’ challenge to a match at Deadline after hearing about their injury, then hope that they don’t wait too long. Brutus and Julius appeared with referees, Ivy Nile and Tatum Paxley pushing them away from the ring. <strong>No score.</strong></p>

<h2 id="match-3-tony-dangelo-w-stacks-defeated-xyon-quinn-in-almost-two-minutes">Match #3: Tony D’Angelo (w/ Stacks) defeated Xyon Quinn in almost two minutes.</h2>
<p>This was D’Angelo’s first match back after suffering a leg injury; he won with a blue thunder bomb to Quinn. After the match, D’Angelo blamed Wes Lee for injuring his leg, then Lee appeared and said that he has unfinished business with Dijak and then told D’Angelo to wait until D’Angelo told him to face him instead of Dijak now. Then, Dijak appeared on the screen and called D’Angelo a scumbag, then told Lee to keep his name out of his mouth; after Dijak’s appearance, Stacks said that Lee had nowhere to run and shoved him until Lee fought back and left. <strong>My score: 0.5/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="match-4-charlie-dempsey-defeated-hank-walker-in-four-minutes">Match #4: Charlie Dempsey defeated Hank Walker in four minutes.</h2>
<p>Drew Gulak appeared at the entryway during the match. Dempsey won after making Walker submit to a half crab/crossface combo. <strong>My score: 1/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="match-5-isla-dawn-defeated-thea-hail-w-andre-chase-and-duke-hudson-in-almost-three-minutes">Match #5: Isla Dawn defeated Thea Hail (w/ Andre Chase and Duke Hudson) in almost three minutes.</h2>
<p>Isla has a new theme song that sounds like a symphonic metal version of her NXT UK theme with a choir. She made this match one sided and won with two elbow drop neckbreakers. After the match, smoke emerged from one side of the ring and Alba Fyre emerged and fought Isla; referees came to separate the two, and Isla attempted to spit black mist at Alba, but missed and sprayed the referee with it. <strong>My score: 0.5/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="match-6-josh-briggs--brooks-jensen-defeated-malik-blade--edris-enofé-w-odyssey-jones-in-three-minutes">Match #6: Josh Briggs &amp; Brooks Jensen defeated Malik Blade &amp; Edris Enofé (w/ Odyssey Jones) in three minutes.</h2>
<p>Kiana James’ assistant placed an envelope in Jensen’s jacket early in the match. Towards the end, Von Wagner appeared and he and Odyssey Jones brawled at ringside; this allowed Jensen to hit Enofé with a running heel kick before he and Briggs hit him with a chop block/clothesline combo for the win. Both teams bumped fists afterwards. Then, it was revealed that the envelope contained a VIP invite to Deadline by Kiana, which ticked off Fallon Henley. <strong>My score: 0.5/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="main-event-indi-hartwell-defeated-wendy-choo-and-fallon-henley-in-a-triple-threat-match-to-qualify-for-the-iron-survivor-challenge">Main event: Indi Hartwell defeated Wendy Choo and Fallon Henley in a triple threat match to qualify for the Iron Survivor Challenge.</h2>
<p>Toxic Attraction watched the match backstage. Indi attempted to hit Fallon with a superplex until Wendy surprised the two with a bottom rope German suplex; Wendy then hit Fallon with a brainbuster for two, and then hit her with a reverse splash until Indi threw Wendy out of the ring to pick up the scraps by hitting Fallon with a blindsiding forearm for the win. <strong>My score: 3.5/5</strong></p>

<h1 id="nxt-lvl-up">NXT: LVL UP</h1>

<p>Staying in Orlando, we wrap things up with an episode of NXT: LVL UP.</p>

<p><a href="/assets/posts/2022-12-27/nxt_lvl_up.jpg" class="restrict-width">nxt_lvl_up</a></p>

<p>My favorite match of this episode would have to go to the main event bout between Ikemen Jiro and Trick Williams. Williams continues to be impressive when it comes to working in singles competition. The same goes for Jiro who had a strong showing in this match. In the end, it was Williams who emerged victorious. This is no lie, but I still love seeing Williams in singles competition especially on NXT: LVL UP; I would still love to see him get one-on-one matches on NXT as well and not just LVL UP to be honest…</p>

<p>Here are the NXT: LVL UP results from Orlando…</p>

<h2 id="match-1-odyssey-jones-defeated-damon-kemp">Match #1: Odyssey Jones defeated Damon Kemp.</h2>
<p>Kemp worked on Jones’ left arm during the match until Jones came back and won with a Black Hole Slam. <strong>My score: 2/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="match-2-sol-ruca-defeated-valentina-feroz-in-four-and-a-half-minutes">Match #2: Sol Ruca defeated Valentina Feroz in four and a half minutes.</h2>
<p>Sol picked up her second win with a backflip from the middle rope into a cutter. <strong>My score: 2/5</strong></p>

<h2 id="main-event-trick-williams-defeated-ikemen-jiro">Main event: Trick Williams defeated Ikemen Jiro.</h2>
<p>Jiro went for the Ikemen Slash, but missed and it allowed Williams to win with the Trick Kick. <strong>My score: 2.5/5</strong></p>

<h1 id="next-time">Next time…</h1>

<p>Not only do I have my usual three as well as one more Progress recap to get out of the way (before focusing on wXw events…and a little bit more Christmas shopping), but I will also have recap of WWE’s (as well as NXT’s) last premium live event of the year which is of course NXT Deadline.</p>

<p>For my newsletters as well as any articles that are on the Wrestling With Johners website, the website is wrestlingwithjohners.com/articles</p>

<p>For just my newsletters on the WWJ website, it is wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/pro-darin/</p>

<p>Thanks for reading! Feel free to comment! I’ll see you next time!</p>

<p>(Photos shown in the newsletter are from WWE, Progress and ICW.)</p>]]></content><author><name>pro-darin</name></author><category term="articles" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Sam Gradwell’s Roman Reigns Story</title><link href="/videos/wrestling-with-johners/2022/12/27/Sam-Gradwells-Roman-Reigns-Story/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sam Gradwell’s Roman Reigns Story" /><published>2022-12-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-12-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/videos/wrestling-with-johners/2022/12/27/Sam%20Gradwells%20Roman%20Reigns%20Story</id><content type="html" xml:base="/videos/wrestling-with-johners/2022/12/27/Sam-Gradwells-Roman-Reigns-Story/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name>john</name></author><category term="videos" /><category term="wrestling-with-johners" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">WWE Divas !!!!! #wwe #shorts</title><link href="/da-call-up/videos/2022/12/26/WWE-Divas-wwe-shorts/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="WWE Divas !!!!! #wwe #shorts" /><published>2022-12-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-12-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/da-call-up/videos/2022/12/26/WWE%20Divas%20%20wwe%20shorts</id><content type="html" xml:base="/da-call-up/videos/2022/12/26/WWE-Divas-wwe-shorts/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name>da-call-up</name></author><category term="da-call-up" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Episode 66: Shooting Such Good Shoot</title><link href="/shootin-sht/2022/12/26/Episode-66-Shooting-Such-Good-Shoot/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Episode 66: Shooting Such Good Shoot" /><published>2022-12-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-12-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/shootin-sht/2022/12/26/Episode%2066%20Shooting%20Such%20Good%20Shoot</id><content type="html" xml:base="/shootin-sht/2022/12/26/Episode-66-Shooting-Such-Good-Shoot/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name>shootin-sht</name></author><category term="shootin-sht" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Chicagoland Championship Wrestling Saturday Night GrappleMasters.</title><link href="/pro-wrestling-tonight/videos/2022/12/25/Chicagoland-Championship-Wrestling-Saturday-Night-GrappleMasters/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Chicagoland Championship Wrestling Saturday Night GrappleMasters." /><published>2022-12-25T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-12-25T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/pro-wrestling-tonight/videos/2022/12/25/Chicagoland%20Championship%20Wrestling%20Saturday%20Night%20GrappleMasters</id><content type="html" xml:base="/pro-wrestling-tonight/videos/2022/12/25/Chicagoland-Championship-Wrestling-Saturday-Night-GrappleMasters/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name>chicagoland-championship-wrestling</name></author><category term="pro-wrestling-tonight" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">SWN Podcast | Billy’s Blast From The Past</title><link href="/scottish-wrestling-network/2022/12/25/SWN-Podcast-Billys-Blast-From-The-Past/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="SWN Podcast | Billy’s Blast From The Past" /><published>2022-12-25T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-12-25T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/scottish-wrestling-network/2022/12/25/SWN%20Podcast%20%20Billys%20Blast%20From%20The%20Past</id><content type="html" xml:base="/scottish-wrestling-network/2022/12/25/SWN-Podcast-Billys-Blast-From-The-Past/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name>scottish-wrestling-network</name></author><category term="scottish-wrestling-network" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry></feed>