<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-01-29T17:27:37+00:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Wrestling With Johners</title><subtitle>Pro Wrestling podcast with news, reviews and debate from WWE, NXT, NXT:UK, AEW, NJPW, Indy Wrestling and so much more. Listen to Wrestling With Johners on Apple Podcasts, Google Podcasts, Spotify, Podbean, Podcast Addict, Castbox, YouTube or wherever you get your podcasts.</subtitle><author><name>John Scott</name></author><entry><title type="html">Ep99 – Royal Rumble Review (with John Scott &amp;amp; Kieron Reed)</title><link href="/podcasts/EP99/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep99 – Royal Rumble Review (with John Scott &amp; Kieron Reed)" /><published>2020-01-28T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-28T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP99</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP99/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep98 - On Board The JERICHO CRUISE #2 (with Heather and ‘Half Decent’)</title><link href="/podcasts/EP98/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep98 - On Board The JERICHO CRUISE #2 (with Heather and 'Half Decent')" /><published>2020-01-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP98</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP98/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep97 – WORLDS COLLIDE Review</title><link href="/podcasts/EP97/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep97 – WORLDS COLLIDE Review" /><published>2020-01-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP97</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP97/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep96 – Jericho Cruise Part Deux | NEW Champ on NXT | Royal Rumble &amp;amp; Worlds Collide Predictions</title><link href="/podcasts/EP96/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep96 – Jericho Cruise Part Deux | NEW Champ on NXT | Royal Rumble &amp; Worlds Collide Predictions" /><published>2020-01-25T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-25T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP96</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP96/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">WrestleMania Card Still Wide Open</title><link href="/news/WrestleMania-Card-Wide-Open/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="WrestleMania Card Still Wide Open" /><published>2020-01-20T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/news/WrestleMania%20Card%20Wide%20Open</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/WrestleMania-Card-Wide-Open/">&lt;p&gt;It is being reported from sources within WWE that WrestleMania 36 is still “wide open in many regards.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-20/wrestlemania 36 logo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;wm36logo&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At this point in previous years, there would be run-sheets or tentative WrestleMania lineups around, though those have been made more secretive in recent years. According to Sean Ross Sapp from Fightful.com, no one he’s spoken to has seen a run sheet or anything related to WrestleMania 36 yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There have even been a couple of people at the WWE Performance Center who have been told to “be ready” in case a WrestleMania spot is there for them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-20/keith lee.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;keith lee&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This could be seen as a massive positive and a welcome change, as compared to previous years. One wrestler spoken to said that it leads them to think WWE will go with who is hot for certain spots, instead of trying to make certain talents hot to fit the roles they’ve already decided for them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-20/adam cole.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;adam cole&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WrestleMania 36 is more than 2 months away, but there is already speculation regarding potential match-ups and whether NXT talent could be a part of the “Showcase of the Immortals” on April 5th in Tampa, Florida.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html">It is being reported from sources within WWE that WrestleMania 36 is still “wide open in many regards.”</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">‘The Man’ and CM Punk on this week’s WWE Backstage</title><link href="/news/Becky-and-CM-Punk-on-WWE-Backstage/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="'The Man' and CM Punk on this week's WWE Backstage" /><published>2020-01-19T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-19T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/news/Becky%20and%20CM%20Punk%20on%20WWE%20Backstage</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/Becky-and-CM-Punk-on-WWE-Backstage/">&lt;p&gt;Current WWE RAW Women’s Champion Becky Lynch has been announced as the guest for Tuesday’s episode of WWE Backstage on FS1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-19/becky.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;becky lynch&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The show will also feature CM Punk’s third appearance as an analyst.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The combination of Becky Lynch and CM Punk should help to boost viewing figures for WWE Backstage. Which has struggled to maintain a strong viewing audience since the show began in October 2019.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-19/CM-Punk-2019.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;cm punk&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And with The Royal Rumble PPV just around the corner it will be interesting to hear Punk’s thought’s on the line-up and the build, to one of the most popular WWE Pay-Per-Views of the year.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html">Current WWE RAW Women’s Champion Becky Lynch has been announced as the guest for Tuesday’s episode of WWE Backstage on FS1.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">NXT:UK Review - January 16th, 2020</title><link href="/articles/NXT-Review-16th-January-2020/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="NXT:UK Review - January 16th, 2020" /><published>2020-01-17T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-17T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/NXT%20Review%2016th%20January%202020</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/NXT-Review-16th-January-2020/">&lt;p&gt;We are coming off the heels off NXT:UK Takeover Blackpool 2. Only 2 matches on this week’s episode on the WWE Network. 
First match is…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-17/ballroom.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;empress ballroom&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-kid-vs-joseph-connors&quot;&gt;A-Kid vs. Joseph Connors&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-17/conners.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;conners&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These matches were taped before takeover Blackpool 2. This was a good match. I do think Connors should have been on the main Takeover card. It’s cool we got a taping before Takeover. A-kid seems to have turned into a jobber. Connors with the win in this match.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-17/a-kid.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;a-kid&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WINNER OF THE MATCH: Joseph Connors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;kassius-ohno-vs-dave-mastiff&quot;&gt;Kassius Ohno vs. Dave Mastiff&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-17/ohno.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;ohno&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another good match here. Hard hitting as expected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-17/mastiff.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;mastiff&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is another match I enjoyed but I do think the wrong person won, on this occasion. I thought Ohno was being pushed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-17/mastiff2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;mastiff&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WINNER OF THE MATCH: Dave Mastiff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was a good episode of NXT:UK.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t forget to go and check out my YouTube channel - The people’s WWE channel. If you smell what rick the rock is cookin’&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>ricky-j</name></author><summary type="html">We are coming off the heels off NXT:UK Takeover Blackpool 2. Only 2 matches on this week’s episode on the WWE Network. First match is…</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">NXT:UK TakeOver Blackpool II Review - 12th Jan 2020</title><link href="/articles/nxtuk-takeover-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="NXT:UK TakeOver Blackpool II Review - 12th Jan 2020" /><published>2020-01-17T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-17T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/nxtuk%20takeover%20review</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/nxtuk-takeover-review/">&lt;p&gt;Well here we go! We are live and time to make review history. First match is…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;trent-seven-vs-eddie-dennis&quot;&gt;Trent Seven vs. Eddie Dennis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Very, very good match to start things out. The crowd are absolutely hot. Hard hitting action. Eddie threw Trent over the top rope for the high spot.  By the way I have a great view of the ring. I did enjoy this match. My prediction came true.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Winner of the match Eddie Dennis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;kay-lee-ray-vs-piper-niven-vs-toni-storm-in-a-triple-threat-match-for-the-nxt-uk-womens-title&quot;&gt;Kay Lee Ray vs Piper Niven vs Toni Storm in a triple threat match for the NXT UK women’s title.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What a match. Just incredible! All 3 women left it all in the ring. High spots and high flying action. The crowd were super-hot. I’m lost for words. Toni hit her  finisher and was so close to winning the title but it didn’t happen. So many pin fall attempts, by all 3 women. The title did not change hands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-17/toni piper ray.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;storm ray niven&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Winner of the match and still NXT UK Women’s champion: Kay Lee&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tyler-bate-vs-jordan-devlin&quot;&gt;Tyler Bate vs Jordan Devlin&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wow, wow, wow! What an incredible match. We get an “Are you watching Vince McMahon chant. Another great match. During this match I discovered the commentators are on the balcony above me. I got the prediction wrong for this one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-17/tylerbate.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;tyler &amp;amp; jordan&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Winner of the match: Tyler Bate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;gallus-vs-imperium-vs-mark-andrewsflash-morgan-vs-the-grizzled-young-veterans-in-a-fatal-four-way-ladder-match-for-the-nxt-uk-tag-team-titles&quot;&gt;Gallus vs. Imperium vs. Mark Andrews/Flash Morgan vs. The Grizzled Young Veterans in a fatal four way ladder match for the NXT UK tag team titles.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-17/gallus.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;tag titles&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet another incredible match. All tag teams in the hunt for the titles. High flying action. Tag Gold on the line. A really hot crowd. This is wrestling! The titles didn’t change hands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Winner of the match and still NXT UK tag team champions, Gallus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Review time for the main event&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;walter-vs-joe-coffey-for-the-wwe-uk-title&quot;&gt;Walter vs. Joe Coffey for the WWE UK title.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-17/referee bump.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;referee&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wow, just wow! What a match. What a main event. Hard hitting powerful action. I thought this was never going to end. Both men with big moves. The referee got knocked down during the match by Walter, so in comes Alexander Wolfe to help him. Here comes Ilja Dragunov to take out Wolfe, the match continues and didn’t end there. This was breath taking. I’m so happy I got to witness it live.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-17/imperium.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;walter&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The finish came out of nowhere. A sleeper hold. Yes a sleeper bold from Walter. But wait a minute they are here. It’s the Undisputed Era bay-bay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They destroy Imperium. Winner of the match and still WWE UK Champion, Walter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-17/undisputed.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;adam cole bay bay&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What a show and I give it 10 out of 10. I did get to meet the ring announcer, Andy Shepard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t forget to go and check out my channel the people’s WWE channel. If you smell what Rick the Rock is cookin!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>ricky-j</name></author><summary type="html">Well here we go! We are live and time to make review history. First match is…</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep95 - MAVERICK BLADE Interview (Independent Wrestling Elite UK)</title><link href="/podcasts/interviews/EP95/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep95 - MAVERICK BLADE Interview (Independent Wrestling Elite UK)" /><published>2020-01-16T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/interviews/EP95</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/interviews/EP95/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Comedy In Wrestling!</title><link href="/articles/Comedy-in-Wrestling/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Comedy In Wrestling!" /><published>2020-01-13T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/Comedy%20in%20Wrestling</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/Comedy-in-Wrestling/">&lt;p&gt;It’s important not to shy away from the big topics, so this time around I am focussing on…. Is there a place for comedy in wrestling?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I featured Orange Cassidy in my first piece and how much I have been taken in by the gimmick so far so it got me to thinking more about comedy in wrestling, in addition to this I am currently working my way through a hell of a lot of Chikara on Amazon Prime – there are about TEN seasons of content for FREE if you are a Prime Member (for the record this article is not sponsored by Amazon Prime and other streaming services are available….)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I think of comedy in wrestling I am looking at the more overt use of characters, gimmicks and spots, more so than being funny in promos and put downs – for example The Rock and John Cena are probably two of the best all time on the mic and could be hilarious at times but I would never consider them as comedic wrestlers so to that end I am ignoring the ‘cheap pop’ sort of comedy, which also means reluctantly I am not including Mick Foley, one of my all-time wrestling heroes and incredibly funny guy, in this piece.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Obviously in the Indies there is more scope for comedy and there is more opportunity to be a bit more silly and go all out with wild gimmicks and humour. To look at British Wrestling the like of Grado, Sebastian Radclaw and Mad Man Manson quickly spring to mind. Manson is someone that I saw loads of on DVD and YouTube before having the opportunity to see him live and meet him a couple of times and he really didn’t disappoint, and the fact that so many people would go along with it sums up how much fun wrestling can be. One of my personal Manson highlights occurred at a Pro Wrestling Kingdom show where he competed with another one of my favourite comedic wrestlers, Sebastian Radclaw in an “11 Stages of Hell” match which included thumb wrestling, a staring contest and playing noughts and crosses on the referees back. It was completely silly and stupid and yet at the same time completely engaging and entertaining!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grado tends to split opinions a little more as many would argue that his wrestling ability falls far short of how over his character was, but ultimately getting over is every wrestlers goal and Grado has done very well with what he does. Similarly, someone like Joey Ryan really polarises opinion, he has a tonne of talent but has really bought into his gimmick which doesn’t really work with a lot of people. In the earlier days the sleazy character worked but as the boundaries have been pushed it seems to have pushed a lot of people away – possibly it’s the typical wrestling thing of over using certain moves so they lose shock value and just become a bit tedious. Although arguably what I saw of him predominantly teaming with Candice LeRae in PWG I really enjoyed and felt that he was a good worker.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nick Dinsmore, who is likely better known to most as Eugene, Eric Bischof’s nephew in WWE is another name that springs to mind on this subject. When he arrived in WWE he was portrayed as being quite simple and copying famous moves etc to be honest the character seemed to get over really well with fans but I recall at the time thinking that there’s definitely a limit on how far the character can go and ultimately it would be incredibly difficult to repackage the character down the line … as Robert Downey Jr said as Kirk Lazarus in “Tropic Thunder” “…everyone knows you never go full retard.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Attack! Pro Wrestling is a promotion which I have followed for a long time and have been fortunate to get to a number shows in Birmingham, Bristol and even at the legendary Cathays in Cardiff. Attack is unique in that they have utilised arguably the best roster available from the UK but made their shows uniquely entertaining and fun with themed shows and top talent dressing up and becoming different characters from movies and computer games. I’d say that my visit to Cardiff for the Press Start 2 show a few years ago remains one of my favourite wrestling shows I have ever attended – just a few highlights from card include Pete Dunne, Damian Dunne, Chris Brookes and Ryan Smile in a fatal 4 way as Streetfighter and Mortal Kombat characters, Mark Andrews as Ash Ketchum against Tyler Bate as the Pokémon Machoke where he was painted silver head to toe not to mention the Hunters going head to head in the main event as Mario and Luigi! If you haven’t seen it, I highly recommend finding the DVD or heading over to their page on Vimeo. I am also fairly certain that Attack is the birthplace of No Fun Dunne which is one of the best gimmicks around at present in my opinion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Often the crowd can contribute to comedy in wrestling, it can be simply buying in to gimmicks and silly matches – let’s face it going into slow motion during a match doesn’t really go over if the crowd aren’t willing to suspend their disbelief! Or if you watch NXTUK the crowd really get into it resulting in some interesting songs and chants for different wrestlers, or chanting for VAR as they were at Takeover Blackpool II – which is topical but very unique to the UK/European audience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The flipside to that is that, at times, those in attendance forget that in reality they are just spectators and try to take over themselves and become a part of the show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The likes of Kris Travis and Martin Kirby deserve a mention in the discussion of comedic wrestling, individually they are both highly entertaining and when together as Project Ego they seemed to blend being a well-oiled, effective tag team perfectly with being very funny and entertaining - both in the ring and interacting with the crowd.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I mentioned above, I have been watching rather a lot of Chikara of late, and similar to Attack they have some amazing talent on their shows but manage to make it good fun and get a lot of interaction with their audience. Some of the characters are wacky but generally well developed including The Colony, I like the fact that each member of the Colony is different and has a different role and style. There are lots of outlandish characters and the variety works really well over a succession of shows, I can’t wait to watch more. Based on what I have seen so far, I would certainly recommend that if you haven’t seen Chikara yet it is worth checking them out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, in summary I definitely see a place for comedy in wrestling but as with a lot of things it does run a fine line and can go somewhat wrong if not done well. I think the major promotions do quite well with bringing comedy into promos and skits without making it too silly – in my last piece I mentioned some of the promo work in AEW in particular with Le Champion which I think works really well. WWE unfortunately often create “funny” moments unintentionally and some angles become laughable for all the wrong reasons…. cough cough…. Lana and Lashley….&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Name Drop… There are quite a few to choose from on this topic but I’ll go with Seb Radclaw. I was fortunate enough to see him in action numerous times including being selected to join him in the ring to learn the Gremlin dance at a Pro Wrestling Kingdom show, I even got chance to have a lengthy sit down chat with him at a Kamikaze Pro event in order to write a piece on him (which can be found here:  http://bit.ly/36eQAaU )&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-13/matt2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;matt2&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-01-13/matt1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;iron&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am on Twitter where I have a new profile – Matt Based Wrestling - just to focus on all things wrestling related, you can follow me at &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/mattbasedwres01&quot;&gt;@mattbasedwres01&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>matt-bayliss</name></author><summary type="html">It’s important not to shy away from the big topics, so this time around I am focussing on…. Is there a place for comedy in wrestling?</summary></entry></feed>