<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-03-27T19:10:56+00:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Wrestling With Johners</title><subtitle>Pro Wrestling podcast with news, reviews and debate from WWE, NXT, NXT:UK, AEW, NJPW, Indy Wrestling and so much more. Listen to Wrestling With Johners on Apple Podcasts, Google Podcasts, Spotify, Podbean, Podcast Addict, Castbox, YouTube or wherever you get your podcasts.</subtitle><author><name>John Scott</name></author><entry><title type="html">Impact Wrestling Multiverse of Matches Preview and Predictions</title><link href="/alliance-pro-wrestling-network/Impact-Wrestling-Multiverse-of-Matches-Preview-and-Predictions/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Impact Wrestling Multiverse of Matches Preview and Predictions" /><published>2022-03-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-03-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/alliance-pro-wrestling-network/Impact%20Wrestling%20Multiverse%20of%20Matches%20Preview%20and%20Predictions</id><content type="html" xml:base="/alliance-pro-wrestling-network/Impact-Wrestling-Multiverse-of-Matches-Preview-and-Predictions/"></content><author><name>lewis-carlan</name></author><category term="alliance-pro-wrestling-network" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Impact Wrestling World Champion Moose takes out Josh Alexander’s wife at indy show</title><link href="/alliance-pro-wrestling-network/Impact-Wrestling-World-Champion-Moose-takes-out-Josh-Alexanders-wife-at-indy-show/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Impact Wrestling World Champion Moose takes out Josh Alexander’s wife at indy show" /><published>2022-03-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-03-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/alliance-pro-wrestling-network/Impact%20Wrestling%20World%20Champion%20Moose%20takes%20out%20Josh%20Alexanders%20wife%20at%20indy%20show</id><content type="html" xml:base="/alliance-pro-wrestling-network/Impact-Wrestling-World-Champion-Moose-takes-out-Josh-Alexanders-wife-at-indy-show/"></content><author><name>lewis-carlan</name></author><category term="alliance-pro-wrestling-network" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Impact Wrestling Multiverse of Matches Preview and Predictions</title><link href="/alliance-pro-wrestling-network/videos/Impact-Wrestling-Multiverse-of-Matches-Preview-and-Predictions/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Impact Wrestling Multiverse of Matches Preview and Predictions" /><published>2022-03-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-03-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/alliance-pro-wrestling-network/videos/Impact%20Wrestling%20Multiverse%20of%20Matches%20Preview%20and%20Predictions</id><content type="html" xml:base="/alliance-pro-wrestling-network/videos/Impact-Wrestling-Multiverse-of-Matches-Preview-and-Predictions/"></content><author><name>lewis-carlan</name></author><category term="alliance-pro-wrestling-network" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Impact Wrestling World Champion Moose takes out Josh Alexander’s wife at indy show</title><link href="/alliance-pro-wrestling-network/videos/Impact-Wrestling-World-Champion-Moose-takes-out-Josh-Alexanders-wife-at-indy-show/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Impact Wrestling World Champion Moose takes out Josh Alexander’s wife at indy show" /><published>2022-03-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-03-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/alliance-pro-wrestling-network/videos/Impact%20Wrestling%20World%20Champion%20Moose%20takes%20out%20Josh%20Alexanders%20wife%20at%20indy%20show</id><content type="html" xml:base="/alliance-pro-wrestling-network/videos/Impact-Wrestling-World-Champion-Moose-takes-out-Josh-Alexanders-wife-at-indy-show/"></content><author><name>lewis-carlan</name></author><category term="alliance-pro-wrestling-network" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Triple H retires, Ric Flair claims Aj Styles is better than Bryant Danielson, Wrestling Round up, Impact, AEW, ROH News plus more!</title><link href="/chokeslam-wrestling-report/Triple-H-retires-Ric-Flair-claims-Aj-Styles-is-better-than-Bryant-Danielson-Wrestling-Round-up-Impact-AEW-ROH-News-plus-more/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Triple H retires, Ric Flair claims Aj Styles is better than Bryant Danielson, Wrestling Round up, Impact, AEW, ROH News plus more!" /><published>2022-03-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-03-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/chokeslam-wrestling-report/Triple%20H%20retires%20Ric%20Flair%20claims%20Aj%20Styles%20is%20better%20than%20Bryant%20Danielson%20Wrestling%20Round%20up%20Impact%20AEW%20ROH%20News%20plus%20more</id><content type="html" xml:base="/chokeslam-wrestling-report/Triple-H-retires-Ric-Flair-claims-Aj-Styles-is-better-than-Bryant-Danielson-Wrestling-Round-up-Impact-AEW-ROH-News-plus-more/"></content><author><name>chokeslam-wrestling-report</name></author><category term="chokeslam-wrestling-report" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Mickie Knuckles is hardcore #shorts</title><link href="/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/Mickie-Knuckles-is-hardcore-shorts/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mickie Knuckles is hardcore #shorts" /><published>2022-03-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-03-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/Mickie%20Knuckles%20is%20hardcore%20shorts</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/Mickie-Knuckles-is-hardcore-shorts/"></content><author><name>jofo-in-the-ring</name></author><category term="jofo-in-the-ring" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Proof The Rock did not win the 2000 Royal Rumble #shorts</title><link href="/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/Proof-The-Rock-did-not-win-the-2000-Royal-Rumble-shorts/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Proof The Rock did not win the 2000 Royal Rumble #shorts" /><published>2022-03-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-03-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/Proof%20The%20Rock%20did%20not%20win%20the%202000%20Royal%20Rumble%20shorts</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/Proof-The-Rock-did-not-win-the-2000-Royal-Rumble-shorts/"></content><author><name>jofo-in-the-ring</name></author><category term="jofo-in-the-ring" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">kWo Indie Round Up March 2022</title><link href="/kwo/kWo-Indie-Round-Up-March-2022/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="kWo Indie Round Up March 2022" /><published>2022-03-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-03-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/kwo/kWo%20Indie%20Round%20Up%20March%202022</id><content type="html" xml:base="/kwo/kWo-Indie-Round-Up-March-2022/"></content><author><name>kwo</name></author><category term="kwo" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Issue 5 - Shows of January 29-February 4, 2022</title><link href="/articles/Issue-5-Shows-of-January-29-February-4,-2022/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Issue 5 - Shows of January 29-February 4, 2022" /><published>2022-03-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-03-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/Issue%205%20Shows%20of%20January%2029-February%204,%202022</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/Issue-5-Shows-of-January-29-February-4,-2022/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png&quot; alt=&quot;pro darin&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;first-of-all&quot;&gt;First of all…&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would like to say thank you to all of my family and friends that not only congratulated me or wished me good luck on this newsletter, but—during what was also Royal Rumble weekend—wishing me a happy birthday. I really appreciate it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only that, I would also like to thank author and host John Scott of Wrestling With Johners for allowing me to use the Wrestling With Johners Facebook group to have me post this newsletter. I may be—as you can see on the top of the newsletter below the Pro-Darin logo—five issues too late, but I’m still sending my thanks to you John.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And now, onto the newsletter!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;royal-rumble&quot;&gt;Royal Rumble&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of WWE’s five major events took place this weekend, and it was the Royal Rumble.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those of you that keep score of home, it’s not the first time that Royal Rumble was the second Pay-Per-View/Premium Live Event of the year; I remember back in 2005 that New Year’s Revolution took place first, followed by Royal Rumble which took place on my birthday and that was before No Way Out—later renamed Elimination Chamber—became the official WWE event to have Elimination Chamber matches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both the 30-man Royal Rumble and the 30-woman Royal Rumble were very good, even though they do not get five-star ratings whatsoever; I wish there were better surprises besides those that were mentioned on episodes of Raw and SmackDown prior to this event (such as celebrities, WWE Hall of Famers, and past WWE competitors that are also labeled “WWE Legends”).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only did we have surprise additions as well as eliminations related to ongoing rivalries that occur on Raw and SmackDown (such as Naomi vs. Sonya Deville or RK-Bro vs. Alpha Academy who won the Raw Tag Team championship in Philadelphia early in January), but also some past rivalries renewed for a short time; this included Mickie James and Michelle McCool clashing during the 30-woman Royal Rumble, AJ Styles and Robert Roode renewing their TNA (or “Impact Wrestling” as we nowadays call it) rivalry, Bad Bunny competing in his second WWE Premium Live Event match (the first being last year’s WrestleMania of course), and so forth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-03-27/Royal Rumble.PNG&quot; alt=&quot;Royal Rumble&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I originally thought that AJ Styles and Sasha Banks would become winners of both of those prestigious battle royals, but I was wrong; in irony, both wrestlers that I predicted also started #1. Regardless of the lack of surprises that entered both battle royals like I mentioned, the well-known saying “Expect the unexpected” came true, especially when it came to who won both of those battle royals; we saw Brock Lesnar come in at #30 and win the men’s Royal Rumble, and a couple hours prior we saw the returning mixed martial artist turned pro wrestler Ronda Rousey come in at #28 and win the women’s Royal Rumble.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You read correctly…Brock Lesnar and Ronda Rousey. For those of you that missed the event, you’re probably asking “Wait, why was Brock Lesnar in the Royal Rumble? Wasn’t he defending the WWE championship against Bobby Lashley that night?” The answer is yes. The reason why Lesnar entered the Royal Rumble is because, an hour or so prior, he lost the title to Lashley after Roman Reigns—while the referee for the matchup was unconscious after being splashed in a corner, and then hit by Lashley’s legs during Lesnar’s F5—ran in and attacked Lesnar…even with help from the now former Lesnar advocate Paul Heyman.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What Reigns did to Lesnar that night made me a liar; I noted in the first newsletter that the feud between Lesnar and Reigns came to a screeching halt after Lesnar was inserted into a WWE championship match at Day 1 while Reigns had COVID-19 up until Lesnar defended that title at Royal Rumble.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I got a feeling that the feud will carry to this year’s WrestleMania, but this time with Reigns—once again—defending the WWE Universal championship.
Speaking of championships, the rest of the title matches that occurred that night weren’t that bad (Seth Rollins fighting the aforementioned Reigns for the Universal championship, and Becky Lynch defending the Raw Women’s championship against Doudrop).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay, time to cue “Ballin” by Logic featuring Castro, it’s time for the results of the matches that took place at the Dome at America’s Center in St. Louis, Missouri…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-seth-freakin-rollins-defeated-roman-reigns-by-disqualification&quot;&gt;Match #1: Seth Freakin Rollins defeated Roman Reigns by disqualification&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;…after Reigns refused to break the Guillotine while Rollins was holding the bottom rope; Reigns retained the WWE Universal title. Rollins unnerved Reigns throughout the entire match with the Shield entrance, as well as his Shield attire. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-ronda-rousey-won-the-30-woman-royal-rumble-order-of-entries&quot;&gt;Match #2: Ronda Rousey won the 30-woman Royal Rumble. Order of entries:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sasha Banks, Melina, Tamina, Kelly Kelly, Aliyah, Liv Morgan, Queen Zelina, Bianca Belair, Dana Brooke (w/ Reggie), Michelle McCool, Sonya Deville, Natalya, Cameron, Naomi, Carmella, Rhea Ripley, Charlotte Flair, Ivory (the Right To Center Ivory to be more specific), Brie Bella, Mickie James (with the Impact Knockouts championship), Alicia Fox, Nikki A.S.H., Summer Rae, Nikki Bella, Sarah Logan (who had a brief reunion with Liv Morgan before the two got eliminated by the Bella Twins), Lita, Mighty Molly, Ronda Rousey, Shotzi, and Shayna Baszler. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-3-becky-lynch-defeated-doudrop-to-retain-the-raw-womens-championship&quot;&gt;Match #3: Becky Lynch defeated Doudrop to retain the Raw Women’s Championship;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Doudrop dominated most of the match until Becky came right back and defeated her with the Manhandle Slam from the middle rope. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-4-bobby-lashley-w-mvp-defeated-brock-lesnar-w-paul-heyman&quot;&gt;Match #4: Bobby Lashley (w/ MVP) defeated Brock Lesnar (w/ Paul Heyman)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;to become the new WWE Champion after Roman Reigns—with help from Heyman—attacked Lesnar while the referee was unconscious (and before the second referee came in to count to three). &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-5-edge--beth-phoenix-defeated-the-miz--maryse&quot;&gt;Match #5: Edge &amp;amp; Beth Phoenix defeated the Miz &amp;amp; Maryse;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite the Miz and Maryse attempting to take an easy way out several times, Edge and Beth came right back several times including near the end with a double spear to the Miz followed by defeating the Miz and Maryse with a double Glam Slam (or “Glamazon Slam” as Jimmy Smith erroneously called on commentary). &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1.25/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-brock-lesnar-won-the-30-man-royal-rumble&quot;&gt;Main event: Brock Lesnar won the 30-man Royal Rumble.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Order of entries: AJ Styles, Shinsuke Nakamura, Austin Theory, Robert Roode, Ridge Holland, Montez Ford, Damian Priest, Sami Zayn, Johnny Knoxville (w/ Jasper Dolphin, Preston Lacy, and Wee Man), Angelo Dawkins, Omos, Ricochet, Chad Gable, Dominik Mysterio, Happy Corbin, Dolph Ziggler, Sheamus, Rick Boogs, Madcap Moss, Riddle, Drew McIntyre, Kevin Owens, Rey Mysterio, Sir Kofi Kingston, Otis, Big E, Bad Bunny, Shane McMahon, Randy Orton, and Brock Lesnar. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;progress-chapter-127-and-the-word-was-progress&quot;&gt;Progress Chapter 127: And the Word Was Progress…&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-03-27/Cara Noir Ridgeway.PNG&quot; alt=&quot;Cara Noir Ridgeway&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;January 2022 continues, and this time we head to the United Kingdom where Progress Wrestling’s first chapter of 2022 began.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last year, Progress Wrestling came back in action in an empty Theatre Beckham in England. This year, the first chapter of 2022 took place at a fan filled Electric Ballroom in London, England. It has been 700 days since Progress had a fan filled arena, going back to early 2020.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m so glad that I discovered Progress Wrestling last year after seeing WWE Network—a month or so before entering the Peacock era—advertise it on social media, along with ICW and wXw. Not only was I able to keep track of all empty arena episodes, but also taking a look at past episodes of those three aforementioned shows from Europe. Progress has been the best of my three favorite discoveries, and I am still enjoying it today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This includes the first chapter of 2022 known as “And the Word Was Progress…”, and not only did it start off with a welcome back and thank you to the fans courtesy of the master of ceremonies Simon Miller, but also with a great handful of matches that ranged from—taking this idea from the ratings in the magazine “Consumer Reports”—fair to excellent (and not a poor match in sight). Even though the show began with a slow yet fun start courtesy of “That Damn Dirty Dog” Gene Munny and Lykos Gym, the rest of the show did the same thing comedic rock group Spinal Tap did back then…go to 11.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All three women’s matches were pretty good—Taonga vs. Session Moth Martina, Charli Evans vs. Lana Austin, and Rhio vs. Mercedez Blaze—especially the final round of the Revelations of Divine Love tournament. I had a gut feeling that Rhio was going to win that match, mainly because of tension going on between Mercedez and Taonga ever since the tournament began late last year. Other than that, I really look forward to seeing Rhio fighting Gisele Shaw for the title.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Speaking of Gisele Shaw, good luck wishes go out to her as she heads to Impact Wrestling in the near future!)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The title matches were good as well. Like I said in the past, Cara Noir’s one-on-one matches have never disappointed me, and neither did the First To Three Falls match against Chris Ridgeway for the Progress World Championship that Cara Noir retained. The best of the title matches that occurred however was the tag team match between the Sunshine Machine and the Smokin’ Guns for the Progress World Tag Team championship; both Chuck Mambo and TK Cooper of the Sunshine Machine proved that they can be serious business besides being a fun-loving tag team (cream pies, airhorns, beach balls, and all).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the match results from London…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(NOTE: The only match I didn’t add was AEW competitor Anthony Ogogo defeating Hari Singh, mainly because it wasn’t on Peacock’s broadcast of Progress Chapter 127 for some reason.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-gene-munny-defeated-kid-lykos-w-kid-lykos-ii-with-a-jumping-ddt&quot;&gt;Match #1: Gene Munny defeated Kid Lykos (w/ Kid Lykos II) with a jumping DDT;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Munny came into the ring wearing an astronaut suit. After the match, Gene thanked the fans for coming, and also for cheering for him in the past. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-dean-allmark-defeated-tate-mayfairs-with-the-clash-driver&quot;&gt;Match #2: Dean Allmark defeated Tate Mayfairs with the Clash Driver;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Axel Tischer was supposed to face Allmark, but was pulled out due to a medical issue. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-3-session-moth-martina-defeated-taonga-with-a-codebreaker-from-the-middle-rope&quot;&gt;Match #3: Session Moth Martina defeated Taonga with a Codebreaker from the middle rope;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kind of like what happens when Popeye eats spinach or when Mario eats a mushroom, Martina would get fired up by drinking a can of beer during the match. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.25/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-4-the-smokin-aces-defeated-the-sunshine-machine-to-retain-the-progress-tag-team-titles-with-the-smokin-ace-crusher-all-four-men-shook-hands-afterwards&quot;&gt;Match #4: The Smokin’ Aces defeated the Sunshine Machine to retain the Progress Tag Team titles with the Smokin’ Ace Crusher; all four men shook hands afterwards.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the match, Lykos Gym ran in and attacked the champions Charlie Sterling and Nick Riley with powder and trays, and then took the titles from them; they challenged the Smokin’ Aces for the titles afterwards. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-5-charli-evans-defeated-lana-austin-with-a-saito-suplex-followed-by-a-burning-lariat&quot;&gt;Match #5: Charli Evans defeated Lana Austin with a Saito suplex followed by a Burning Lariat.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-6-warren-banks-defeated-man-like-dereiss-malik-w-kosta-konstantino&quot;&gt;Match #6: Warren Banks defeated Man Like Dereiss, Malik (w/ Kosta Konstantino)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Roy Johnson, Dan Moloney and Jody Fleisch in a six-pack challenge to become the #1 contender for the Progress World Championship. Before the match, Kosta mocked Danny Black—who was in the crowd—for being in attendance; later on, Malik and Kosta got distracted by Black.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Banks won after hitting three of his opponents with the Bullet Vehicle (spear), followed by a fireman’s carry into a falcon arrow to Dereiss. Afterwards, Banks said that he was fighting for the title on March 25 at the Progress 10th Anniversary Show at the Garage in London, England. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-7-rhio-defeated-mercedez-blaze-w-taonga-in-the-final-round-of-the-revelations-of-divine-love-tournament-to-become-the-1-contender-for-the-progress-womens-championship&quot;&gt;Match #7: Rhio defeated Mercedez Blaze (w/ Taonga) in the final round of the Revelations of Divine Love tournament to become the #1 contender for the Progress Women’s Championship.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the match, Taonga distracted the referee who was unable to count the pins for both Rhio and Mercedez; Mercedez got mad at the ejected Taonga afterwards. Rhio won after hitting Mercedez swinging neckbreaker. Post-match, Rhio vowed to defeat Gisele Shaw for the title, calling herself “North West Strong.” &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-cara-noir-defeated-chris-ridgeway-3-2-in-a-first-to-three-falls-match-to-retain-the-progress-world-championship&quot;&gt;Main event: Cara Noir defeated Chris Ridgeway 3-2 in a First To Three Falls match to retain the Progress World Championship.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cara Noir took the lead after surprising Ridgeway by counting the North West Crossface with a rollup. Then, Ridgeway tied it 1-1 after countering headscissors with a pin. Ridgeway would then take the 2-1 lead after a running punt to Cara Noir before working on his left leg for the rest of the match.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cara Noir came back with a 2-2 tie after making Ridgeway submit quickly to a sleeper hold. Near the end, Cara Noir gave Ridgeway three (you read correctly!) package piledrivers; one was on the apron, another was in the ring for a two count, and the third and final one was also in the ring and for the three count this time. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4.25/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;icw-fight-club&quot;&gt;ICW Fight Club&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, we stay in the United Kingdom in the month of January 2022; this time, we move from a fan filled Electric Ballroom in London, England to—once again—an empty GPWA in Glasgow, Scotland.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The countdown to Square Go! continues; not only do we have wrestlers throwing their hats into the battle royal of the same name, but also championship matches that will occur.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently added was the ICW Tag Team championship rematch between the Kings of the North and the Nine9. Bonesaw and Corvin accepted the challenge this week after hosting a “funeral” for the death of the careers of Dickie Divers and Jack Morris; the reason why the champions hosted the “funeral” is because they vowed to leave the Nine9 “dead and buried” once they defeat them at Square Go! and retain the tag team championship. I would love to see this rematch occur, even if the Kings of the North will have their first title defense in the form of that aforementioned rematch per se.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of tag teams, ICW’s tag team division has been on a roll as of late. A couple weeks ago on ICW, we saw Sinergy debut. This week, we saw a team that we have also seen on Progress and other shows; that team was the Greedy Souls, the team of Brendan White and Danny Jones. I’m not going to lie, I like seeing wrestlers from Progress, ICW, and wXw crossing over to compete; if seeing crossovers in movies, TV shows, comic books, and video games are good, why not in professional wrestling as well? Just my opinion…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back to ICW, the women’s division has been on a roll as well. Not only did we see Lizzy Evo debut on ICW, but also another competitor that we would see on NXT UK on occasion (including this week’s episode of NXT UK that I’ll talk about in the next two pages); that competitor is Myla Grace. Even though she ended up losing in her debut this week, she still did very well. Perhaps she can compete on ICW more often besides make appearances on NXT UK.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-03-27/Leyton Buzzard.PNG&quot; alt=&quot;Leyton Buzzard Theo Doros&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was a big fan of the main event between Leyton Buzzard and Theo Doros. Storylines coming into the matchup were Buzzard showing that he has what it takes to step foot into the Square Go! match and then eye on the ICW World heavyweight championship, and Doros being a hypocrite—besides a self-proclaimed “wrestling god” (ala JBL)—by sneaking in something like an eye rake during a match with a 20-minute time limit. (Remember those rules came into play after Doros defeated Ravie Davie in November of last year?)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the results of the matches that occurred in the empty GPWA…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-lj-cleary-defeated-tallon-jr-with-a-standing-meteora&quot;&gt;Match #1: LJ Cleary defeated Tallon Jr. with a standing Meteora.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-ravie-davie-defeated-eddie-castle-w-alexander-darwin-mcallen-in-a-scheme-rules-match&quot;&gt;Match #2: Ravie Davie defeated Eddie Castle (w/ Alexander Darwin McAllen) in a Scheme Rules match.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(Just a quick heads up, I thought Davie said “Extreme Rules” a few weeks ago until it turned out to be “Scheme Rules”; I apologize for that error I made a few weeks ago in the newsletter.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All hell broke loose near the end of the match as Xero appeared from under the ring until Grant McIvor—equipped with a chain—came and attacked Xero; then, Che Monet got involved, ditto Dylan Thorn and—Thorn’s future opponent—Daz Black. Davie and Castle joined in the brouhaha until, as soon as the smoke cleared, Davie defeated Castle with a spike DDT. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-3-the-greedy-souls-defeated-the-woke-academy-with-a-catapultboss-man-slam-combo-to-robbie-balfour&quot;&gt;Match #3: The Greedy Souls defeated the Woke Academy with a catapult/Boss Man Slam combo to Robbie Balfour.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My score: 2/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-4-molly-spartan-defeated-myla-grace-with-a-pop-up-powerbomb&quot;&gt;Match #4: Molly Spartan defeated Myla Grace with a pop-up powerbomb.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Post-match, Molly attacked Myla until Lizzy Evo ran in and chased Molly out with a steel chair. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-leyton-buzzard-defeated-theo-doros-with-the-x-marks-the-spot-450-splash&quot;&gt;Main event: Leyton Buzzard defeated Theo Doros with the X Marks the Spot (450 splash).&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My score: 4.25/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;nxt&quot;&gt;NXT&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now we leave both the United Kingdom and the month of January 2022, and enter Orlando, Florida and the month of February 2022.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though the women’s Dusty Rhodes Tag Team Classic didn’t begin this week (probably next week), we finally have a team that will be entering that tournament. That team is of course Cora Jade and Raquel Gonzalez. Raquel continuously declined Cora’s offer to team up with her for that upcoming tournament until—after a brief physical altercation with her last week—Cora decided to fight her in a match this week. After Raquel defeated Cora, she decided to team up with Cora for the upcoming women’s DRTTC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More on the women’s roster, I was pretty sure that we would see both the NXT Women’s championship and the NXT Women’s Tag Team championship on the line at NXT Vengeance Day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead, we will see Mandy Rose defend the NXT Women’s championship one week prior to Vengeance Day against Kay Lee Ray, whilst the tag team titles are defended by Gigi Dolin and Jacy Jayne against Indi Hartwell and Persia Pirotta. I believe they decided to have Mandy Rose vs. Kay Lee Ray take place next week because they already have—besides the women’s tag team title match—a lot of tag team matches such as the final round of the men’s DRTTC tournament and whatever matches coming from the women’s DRTTC tournament. By the way, the match for next week—Mandy against KLR—was done after KLR chased Mandy outside and inside the venue after Mandy was declining the offer of a title match repeatedly; KLR went to extreme lengths such as hiding Cora and Jacy elsewhere in Toxic Attraction’s own SUV, prior to chasing Mandy into the locker room (where she stumbled into Edris Enofé and Malik Blade in comedic fashion as the two gentlemen were fantasizing about Mandy) and then the catering room before heading back into the ring where she finally said yes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of teams, last week I thought that we were going to see a 2-on-3 handicap match for this week’s episode of NXT after Tommaso Ciampa came and teams with Bron Breakker when they encountered Legado del Fantasma. We would later learn as soon as the episode aired that it was a regular tag team match with Santos Escobar and Elektra Lopez managing Joaquin Wilde and Raul Mendoza who would take on Ciampa and Breakker that night. This match I was okay with besides the 2-on-3 handicap match. Plus, it was a good buildup for the feud between Breakker and Escobar for the NXT championship heading into NXT Vengeance Day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-03-27/Gunther.PNG&quot; alt=&quot;Gunther&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The opening match was my favorite out of all matches, mainly because we have a good rivalry between two heel stables, which are Diamond Mine and Imperium. The last time I saw a good rivalry involving two heel stables was in the mid-2000s, a year or so after Cornelia, Georgia’s Wild Side Wrestling/NWA Wild Side became NWA Anarchy (nowadays known simply as Anarchy Wrestling because it’s no longer affiliated with National Wrestling Alliance); it was between the NWA Elite led by Jeff G. Bailey and the Devil’s Rejects led by “The Rev” Dan Wilson. Back to February 1, 2022 in Orlando, Florida, the opener was very good, even with some moments such as Roderick Strong suffering effects from a cheap shot he received from Imperium prior to the bell being rung. In the end, Imperium was victorious, even though what’s happening between that trio and Diamond Mine isn’t over by a long shot, even with the Creed Brothers getting ready to focus on the DRTTC tournament.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the match results from Orlando…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-imperium-defeated-the-creed-brothers--roderick-strong-w-malcolm-bivens-and-ivy-nile&quot;&gt;Match #1: Imperium defeated the Creed Brothers &amp;amp; Roderick Strong (w/ Malcolm Bivens and Ivy Nile)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;…afterwards Gunther hit Brutus Creed with a powerbomb. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-raquel-gonzalez-defeated-cora-jade-with-the-chingona-bomb&quot;&gt;Match #2: Raquel Gonzalez defeated Cora Jade with the Chingona Bomb;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;…post-match, Raquel said yes to being Cora’s tag team partner for the women’s DRTTC tournament. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-3-sarray-defeated-kayla-inlay-with-a-uranage-into-a-capture-suplex&quot;&gt;Match #3: Sarray defeated Kayla Inlay with a uranage into a capture suplex.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My score: 1/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-4-joe-gacy-w-harland-defeated-la-knight&quot;&gt;Match #4: Joe Gacy (w/ Harland) defeated LA Knight.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Near the end, as soon as Knight was thrown out of the ring, he noticed Sanga at ringside, leading to Grayson Waller appearing and blindsiding Knight (despite having a restraining order against him); then, as soon as Knight came back in the ring, Gacy defeated him with a handspring clothesline. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-5-wendy-choo-defeated-amari-miller&quot;&gt;Match #5: Wendy Choo defeated Amari Miller.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Towards the end, Tiffany Stratton came and handed Amari her credit card (the deal from early in the day was that if Amari won, Tiffany would take her shopping) until Wendy defeated her with a running Polish hammer; post-match, Wendy took Tiffany’s credit card and walked away with it! &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-6-andre-chase-w-bodhi-hayward-defeated-draco-anthony&quot;&gt;Match #6: Andre Chase (w/ Bodhi Hayward) defeated Draco Anthony;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Near the end, Anthony took Hayward’s flag and stomped on it until Chase attacked him in anger before defeating him with an arm-trapped flatliner. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-bron-breakker--tommaso-ciampa-defeated-joaquin-wilde-and-raul-mendoza-w-santos-escobar-and-elektra-lopez&quot;&gt;Main event: Bron Breakker &amp;amp; Tommaso Ciampa defeated Joaquin Wilde and Raul Mendoza (w/ Santos Escobar and Elektra Lopez);&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Near the end, Ciampa pushed Wilde off the top rope and through the announce table, while Breakker pinned Mendoza after hitting him with a powerslam. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.25/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;nxt-uk&quot;&gt;NXT UK&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We now head back to the United Kingdom, but this time, it’s February. However, for some reason, the BT Sports Studios was empty this week. Probably because they decided to tape matches after showing us the empty arena match between Ilja Dragunov and Jordan Devlin, for the NXT United Kingdom Championship (which we saw Dragunov retaining after surviving that battle), we saw last week?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay, I’m done with the guessing games…right now, I want to focus on the storylines as well as the matches that occurred on this week’s episode of NXT UK.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-03-27/Ashton Smith Oliver Carter.PNG&quot; alt=&quot;Oliver Carter Ashton Smith&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This week, we had a pretty good start to the show, which was of course the final round match to determine the #1 contenders for the NXT UK Tag Team Championship; it was been the team of Ashton Smith &amp;amp; Oliver Carter and the team of Dave Mastiff &amp;amp; Jack Starz. I know that Mastiff and Starz are a fairly new tag team, but in my honest opinion, I think it’s too soon to have arguments that early in their run as a tag team; I mention this after seeing Mastiff and Starz arguing over who gets tagged in and who doesn’t. Long story short, it was still a good way to showcase two underdog teams that had the same goal in mind which was go after Moustache Mountain for tag team gold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, we move from an exciting opener to a main event that ended abruptly. The main event was Meiko Satomura defending the NXT UK Women’s Championship against Blair Davenport in a Japanese Street Fight. After seeing both women fight with kendo sticks (including one Blair brought to the ring), chairs, nunchaku, a chain, and a spare turnbuckle, Blair climbed to the top rope and hit Meiko with a double stomp to the apron which then ended with Blair breaking her left ankle in the process. Meiko was declared the winner, retaining the title, after the referee stopped the match due to injury.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is not the first time that a main event title match was marred by injury on NXT UK. Back in December of 2021, we saw Ilja Dragunov defend the NXT United Kingdom Championship against Rampage Brown; it ended with Dragunov KO’ing Brown with an enzuigiri.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Get well wishes go out to Blair Davenport and Rampage Brown; we hope to see them again real soon!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Onto the match results…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-oliver-carter--ashton-smith-defeated-dave-mastiff--jack-starz-in-the-final-round-of-the-nxt-uk-tag-team-title-tournament&quot;&gt;Match #1: Oliver Carter &amp;amp; Ashton Smith defeated Dave Mastiff &amp;amp; Jack Starz in the final round of the NXT UK Tag Team title tournament.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moustache Mountain joined Andy Shepherd and Nigel McGuinness on commentary. Towards the end, Mastiff argued with Starz who wanted to tag in, leading to him missing Carter on the Into the Void attempt; this led to Carter and Smith defeating Mastiff with an assisted moonsault. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.25/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-isla-dawn-defeated-myla-grace-in-three-minutes-with-the-alabaster-terror-firemans-carry-into-a-sidewalk-slam&quot;&gt;Match #2: Isla Dawn defeated Myla Grace in three minutes with the Alabaster Terror (fireman’s carry into a sidewalk slam).&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My score: 0.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-meiko-satomura-defeated-blair-davenport-in-a-japanese-street-fight-to-retain-the-nxt-uk-womens-championship-via-referee-stoppage&quot;&gt;Main event: Meiko Satomura defeated Blair Davenport in a Japanese Street Fight to retain the NXT UK Women’s Championship via referee stoppage.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.25/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;205-live&quot;&gt;205 Live&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last but not least, we wrap up this week’s lengthy newsletter with a return to Orlando for 205 Live.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the exception of the main event that lasted for around three minutes, the other matches that occurred were pretty good, fairly better than the matches that occurred in the last two episodes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was more of a Briggs &amp;amp; Jensen episode of 205 Live. Not only did we see Brooks Jensen defeat Bodhi Hayward in the opening match, but he and Josh Briggs got together to watch Kacy Catanzaro and Kayden Carter in tag team action; we have seen Briggs &amp;amp; Jensen getting together with Kacy and Kayden lately on episodes of NXT, hence the reason why they watched the second match which was my favorite on that episode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-03-27/Kacy Kayden.PNG&quot; alt=&quot;Kcy and Kayden&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the results of the matches that occurred in Orlando…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-brooks-jensen-w-josh-briggs-defeated-bodhi-hayward-w-andre-chase&quot;&gt;Match #1: Brooks Jensen (w/ Josh Briggs) defeated Bodhi Hayward (w/ Andre Chase)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;…after hitting Jensen with the Three Point Stance—ala “Hacksaw” Jim Duggan—twice, Hayward went for the third until Jensen countered with a knee to the face and pinned him for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-kacy-catanzaro--kayden-carter-defeated-fallon-henley--lash-legend-with-a-neckbreaker450-splash-combo-to-lash&quot;&gt;Match #2: Kacy Catanzaro &amp;amp; Kayden Carter defeated Fallon Henley &amp;amp; Lash Legend with a neckbreaker/450 splash combo to Lash;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As noted, Briggs &amp;amp; Jensen watched the match from ringside. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-kushida-defeated-damon-kemp-by-submission-with-the-hoverboard-lock&quot;&gt;Main event: Kushida defeated Damon Kemp by submission with the Hoverboard Lock.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My score: 1/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;next-time&quot;&gt;Next time…&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only am I recapping the usual four shows—ICW Fight Club, NXT, NXT UK, and 205 Live—but I am also taking a look back at part 1 of wXw Back To the Roots.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading! I’ll see you next time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Photos shown in the newsletter are from WWE, Progress and ICW.)&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>pro-darin</name></author><category term="articles" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Issue 6 - Shows of February 5-11, 2022</title><link href="/articles/Issue-6-Shows-of-February-5-11,-2022/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Issue 6 - Shows of February 5-11, 2022" /><published>2022-03-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-03-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/Issue%206%20Shows%20of%20February%205-11,%202022</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/Issue-6-Shows-of-February-5-11,-2022/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png&quot; alt=&quot;pro darin&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;happy-together&quot;&gt;Happy Together&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only am I quoting a song by the Turtles, but I am also congratulating a new couple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-03-27/Keith Lee 6.PNG&quot; alt=&quot;Keith Lee Mia Yim&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That couple I’m talking about is Keith Lee and Mia Yim, two wrestlers best known for their time on NXT (and appearances in other WWE shows such as Raw) as well as other companies…Keith Lee—nowadays on AEW after seeing him debut on AEW Dynamite this past Wednesday—also best known in Ring of Honor for being together with Shane Taylor as PBK or “Pretty Boy Killers” before he headed to other companies such as Evolve and PWG (Pro Wrestling Guerrilla), and Mia Yim also known for her time in Combat Zone Wrestling, Shine Wrestling, Shimmer Women Athletes, and—back when she competed as “Jade”—Impact Wrestling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Congratulations Keith Lee and Mia Yim! I wish the two of you the very best. Also, good luck to Keith Lee in AEW!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay then! I’m still happy as a clam, it’s time to check out the shows that I mentioned in the newsletter!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;icw-fight-club&quot;&gt;ICW Fight Club&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our first stop is the still empty GPWA in Glasgow, Scotland for an episode of ICW Fight Club.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only are the fans and employees playing it safe when it comes to COVID, but so are the wrestlers, especially Krieger who was scheduled to team with Lou King Sharp against Thatcher’s Cabinet members Mr. Charles Vyce and Ian Skinner; instead, Jimmy Pierce would substitute for Krieger in that episode. Pierce really needs to pick up wins, even if he has been closing in on them time and time again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The current ICW World heavyweight champion still makes not just a good champion but a good heel as well. I mention this after he was interviewed by one of ICW’s commentators Billy Kirkwood about Square Go! In that interview, Evans attempted to coerce anyone participating in the Square Go! battle royal to choose a different title instead of his title until Scott Reid came out and stopped him from doing so, as well as put him in a match at Square Go!—for the title—against a wrestler best known for his time on Impact Wrestling (during the TNA era), Ring of Honor and Progress, Mark Haskins. Afterwards, Evans put Reid in the Blood Clot Clutch and attempted to attack him even more until BT Gunn—returning from his neck injury caused by Evans—ran in and made the save. It looks like that we might see Gunn go after Evans either before or after Evans vs. Haskins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-03-27/Martin Kirby 6.PNG&quot; alt=&quot;Martin Kirby&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My favorite match of the episode was the main event match between Andy Wild and Martin Kirby. Both men would compete against one another for the first time ever in their ICW careers, and would give their all…Wild looking for more wins even after going toe-to-toe with Big Damo a couple months ago, and Kirby looking for more wins ever since returning to ICW before Fear &amp;amp; Loathing XIII. In the end, it was Andy Wild that emerged victorious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the match results from Glasgow…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-the-kings-of-the-north-defeated-the-greedy-souls-in-a-non-title-match-by-disqualification&quot;&gt;Match #1: The Kings of the North defeated the Greedy Souls in a non-title match by disqualification&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;…due to interference by the Nine9; all three teams brawled afterwards until Damian Corbin knocked out Jack Morris before leaving. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-levi-defeated-martin-macalistair-with-a-double-stomp&quot;&gt;Match #2: Levi defeated Martin MacAlistair with a double stomp;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Levi showed the same mannerisms as Sweeney, who tutored him months ago to get rid of his losing streak, which led to MacAlistair refusing to show sportsmanship to him afterwards. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.25/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-3-ian-skinner--mr-charles-vyce-w-thatcher-wright-defeated-lou-king-sharp--jimmy-pierce&quot;&gt;Match #3: Ian Skinner &amp;amp; Mr. Charles Vyce (w/ Thatcher Wright) defeated Lou King Sharp &amp;amp; Jimmy Pierce.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Towards the end, Thatcher threw the Margaret Thatcher book into the ring until Pierce got rid of it; unbeknownst to Pierce, Skinner gave Vyce a second copy of the book and hit Pierce with it before pinning him for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-andy-wild-defeated-martin-kirby-with-the-dad-bomb-vader-bomb&quot;&gt;Main event: Andy Wild defeated Martin Kirby with the Dad Bomb (Vader Bomb).&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My score: 4.25/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;wxw-back-to-the-roots-part-1&quot;&gt;wXw Back to the Roots part 1&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We then head to the Turbinenhalle in Oberhausen, Germany—on January 15, 2022—for part 1 of wXw Back to the Roots.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-03-27/Back to the Roots 6.PNG&quot; alt=&quot;wXw Back to the Roots&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason why this show was divided into two separate episodes is because of how many matches were added, as well as dealing with events that were either cancelled or rescheduled after bringing fans back to shows in mid-to-late 2021.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In one of the matches we saw in the first half of Back to the Roots, we saw an undefeated streak come to an end as Jurn Simmons defeated the then undefeated Oskar in a match that lasted for a little bit over five minutes. It was still a good match between two tough competitors regardless of how long it lasted. Simmons is doing very well ever since returning to wXw at Shortcut to the Top last year, as is Oskar who has competed in a few wXw matches including this one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first half also gave us a good match—for the wXw Shotgun Championship—between Absolute Andy and Dennis “Ca$h” Dullnig. Andy still has what it takes to compete after stepping down as the Director of Sports in wXw (and handing it to Francis Caspin), especially as the champion. Dullnig on the other hand does do a good job portraying as a delusional knucklehead heel, with and without Hektor Invictus; he proves it as usual in each wXw special and each We Love Wrestling episode, including in this title matchup. In the end, it was Andy retaining the title. The match was good, regardless of how one-sided it was most of the time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main event was a great way of ending the rivalry between Bobby Gunns and Michael Knight, even with the stipulation that there was no time limit and no count outs. Both wXw veterans gave their all, not only inside the ring but also outside it. If I had to choose which of the five matches that occurred in part 1 of Back to the Roots, it would have to be the main event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before I get to the match results, I would like to say that I am definitely ready for the 16 Carat Gold tournament, mainly because of how many competitors such as Oskar, Rott und Flott, and Bobby Gunns are heading to the tournament in a couple months.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plus, as a fan of nostalgia, I loved how the artwork for each promoted match looked like Super Nintendo videogame boxes!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay, I’m done acting like a kid in a candy store, here are the match results from Oberhausen…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-warm-up-match-michael-schenkenberg-w-nikita-charisma-defeated-gulyás-junior-with-a-michinoku-driver&quot;&gt;Match #1 (warm-up match): Michael Schenkenberg (w/ Nikita Charisma) defeated Gulyás Junior with a Michinoku driver;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Charisma used a can of spray deodorant, due to Gulyás’ odor, during the match. After the match, both members of Rott und Flott not only criticized what went on after Absolute Andy stepped down as Director of Sports, but announced that they were stepping into the 16 Carat Gold tournament. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-tristan-archer-defeated-carlos-romo-after-discus-clothesline-followed-by-the-coup-détat-double-knee-facebuster-from-a-powerslam-position&quot;&gt;Match #2: Tristan Archer defeated Carlos Romo after discus clothesline followed by the Coup d’état (double knee facebuster from a powerslam position).&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the match, Archer coerced Dan Mallman to interview him before announcing that—after blaming Levaniel for stealing the wXw Unified World Championship contract from him at Anniversary XXI—he was skipping the 16 Carat Gold tournament to go after the title his way; Jurn Simmons came in afterwards and told Archer to stop being jealous and bitter of Levaniel before telling him to leave. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-3-jurn-simmons-defeated-oskar-in-a-little-over-five-minutes-with-a-spear&quot;&gt;Match #3: Jurn Simmons defeated Oskar in a little over five minutes with a spear.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Post-match, Rott und Flott mocked Oskar from a stairway in the audience until Oskar chased them to the balcony and then to the backstage area. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-4-absolute-andy-defeated-dennis-cah-dullnig-to-retain-the-wxw-shotgun-championship-with-an-f-5&quot;&gt;Match #4: Absolute Andy defeated Dennis “Ca$h” Dullnig to retain the wXw Shotgun Championship with an F-5;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Andy used an F-5 early in the match less than 30 seconds or so after the bell rang. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.25/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-bobby-gunns-defeated-michael-knight-in-a-match-with-no-time-limit-no-count-out-and-there-must-be-a-winner&quot;&gt;Main event: Bobby Gunns defeated Michael Knight in a match with no time limit, no count out, and “There must be a winner.”&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both men got busted open, with Gunns getting the worst of it, after Knight hit him with a tope suicida during the match. Near the end, Gunns hit Knight with a running punt to the chest, followed by a backdrop driver and then a second running punt to the chest for the win. After the match, Gunns told Mallman that he’s entering the 16 Carat Gold tournament for the first time ever. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4.25/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;nxt&quot;&gt;NXT&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, not only do we return to the month of February 2022, but we also head to Orlando, Florida for NXT.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only was this match a buildup for next week’s special episode of NXT entitled “NXT Vengeance Day”, but it was also a buildup for the women’s Dusty Rhodes Tag Team Classic that will occur in two weeks now that we’re seeing female teams entering the tournament including those that are newly formed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-03-27/MSK 6.PNG&quot; alt=&quot;MSK&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of tournaments, we finally have the final round match of the DRTTC come next week; it will be between the Creed Brothers and defending tournament winners MSK. I predict that the Creed Brothers will win this tournament next week; to me, winning the tournament means that they’ll be one step closer to going after Imperium’s Fabian Aichner and Marcel Barthel for the NXT Tag Team championship. I got nothing against MSK whatsoever, even though they had a spectacular semi-final round matchup against Malik Blade and Edris Enofé this week; regardless of how much time they had to refocus after losing the tag team championship before getting help from a shaman in the form of former NXT competitor Riddle, I doubt that we’ll see a repeat tournament winner this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last week, Pete Dunne challenged Tony D’Angelo to a steel cage match for NXT Vengeance Day, a week after he surprised him with a cricket bat. However, after Dunne defeated Draco Anthony, he upped the ante by—after throwing weapons such as chairs, kendo sticks and a toolbox—making the cage match weaponized! Unless you’re not big on weaponized matches, a weaponized cage match will be pretty interesting to watch with both Dunne’s cricket bat and D’Angelo’s crowbar coming into play. It looks like something that two former NXT competitors Adam Cole—nowadays in AEW—and Johnny Gargano may approve. (Remember when they competed in one back in August of 2019?)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NXT had another surprise from a competitor that has never competed in this brand, and this time, it was Dolph Ziggler who had a Twitter war with Bron Breakker the night before this episode aired. Ziggler came into the ring during the NXT Championship submit—hosted by Wade Barrett—between Breakker and Santos Escobar, and said that the only title he has never won was the NXT Championship. What happened next would lead to fans changing their chants from “Triple threat” to “Fatal four way” as Tommaso Ciampa came into the ring and claimed to be “next in line” once Breakker was done with Escobar unless Ziggler said otherwise. Ziggler then got into a brawl with Ciampa after mocking him for staying on NXT for a while, then Escobar’s teammates Joaquin Wilde and Raul Mendoza attacked Breakker before putting him through the table. I’m curious to see where this will go after Breakker defends the title against Escobar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From one title to another, I wasn’t a big fan of the main event for the NXT Women’s Championship. Even though NXT goes overtime nowadays, it appears that everything was rushed to wrap up the match as soon as Gigi Dolin and Jacy Jayne—who were originally banned from the match after brawling with Vengeance Day opponents Indi Hartwell and Persia Pirotta (picture of Indi together with Duke Hudson and all)—interfered, leading to Mandy Rose defeating Kay Lee Ray to retain the title. However, it appears that we may have another team heading into the women’s DRTTC, and that being Io Shirai and Kay Lee Ray; this team came together after Io saved KLR from being beaten down by all three members of Toxic Attraction. I would love to see whether or not Io and KLR works together like a well-oiled machine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Onto the match results from Orlando…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-the-creed-brothers-w-roderick-strong-ivy-nile-and-malcolm-bivens-defeated-grizzled-young-veterans-in-the-semi-final-round-of-the-drttc&quot;&gt;Match #1: The Creed Brothers (w/ Roderick Strong, Ivy Nile and Malcolm Bivens) defeated Grizzled Young Veterans in the semi-final round of the DRTTC.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brutus’ throat was worked on during the match after Zack Gibson and James Drake hit him with a decavitator into the ring apron’s frame. Near the end, while Brutus rammed Gibson in a corner, Julius used his brother as a springboard before hitting Drake with a snap superplex; after some double teaming by the Creed Brothers, Brutus hit Gibson with a basement clothesline for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-tiffany-stratton-defeated-wendy-choo-with-a-corkscrew-vader-bomb&quot;&gt;Match #2: Tiffany Stratton defeated Wendy Choo with a corkscrew Vader Bomb;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This match was made after Wendy stole Tiffany’s credit card last week before it got cancelled after Wendy and Amari Miller’s shopping spree this week. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-3-pete-dunne-defeated-draco-anthony&quot;&gt;Match #3: Pete Dunne defeated Draco Anthony.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Joe Gacy and Harland watch from a stage during the match after they encountered him last week. Near the end, Tony D’Angelo appeared and attempted to attack Dunne with a crowbar until Dunne foiled that attempt. Seconds later, Dunne defeated Anthony with the Bitter End. Post-match, Dunne challenged D’Angelo to a weaponized cage match for NXT Vengeance Day. *8My score: 2.25/5**&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-4-la-knight-defeated-sanga-w-grayson-waller-in-a-little-over-three-minutes-with-a-jumping-neckbreaker-if-knight-won-waller-would-have-to-lift-the-restraining-order&quot;&gt;Match #4: LA Knight defeated Sanga (w/ Grayson Waller) in a little over three minutes with a jumping neckbreaker; if Knight won, Waller would have to lift the restraining order.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the match, Waller attempted to blindside Knight until Knight stopped him and hit him with a headlock driver. Moments later, Waller vowed to have Knight arrested next week. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-5-sarray-defeated-dakota-kai-with-the-sun-ray-running-basement-dropkick-followed-by-a-capture-suplex-from-a-rock-bottom-position&quot;&gt;Match #5: Sarray defeated Dakota Kai with the Sun Ray running basement dropkick followed by a capture suplex from a Rock Bottom position.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-6-msk-defeated-malik-blade--edris-enofé-in-the-semi-final-round-of-the-drttc-after-wes-lee-and-nash-carter-hit-enofé-with-a-spinebustertop-rope-corkscrew-blockbuster-combo&quot;&gt;Match #6: MSK defeated Malik Blade &amp;amp; Edris Enofé in the semi-final round of the DRTTC after Wes Lee and Nash Carter hit Enofé with a spinebuster/top rope corkscrew blockbuster combo.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My score: 4/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-mandy-rose-defeated-kay-lee-ray-to-retain-the-nxt-womens-championship-near-the-end-jacy-jayne-distracted-the-referee-allowing-gigi-dolin-to-knock-klr-off-the-top-rope-and-mandy-win-with-a-pump-knee&quot;&gt;Main event: Mandy Rose defeated Kay Lee Ray to retain the NXT Women’s Championship; near the end, Jacy Jayne distracted the referee, allowing Gigi Dolin to knock KLR off the top rope and Mandy win with a pump knee.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Post-match, Toxic Attraction had KLR surrounded until Io Shirai ran in and she and KLR fought all three members of Toxic Attraction. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;nxt-uk&quot;&gt;NXT UK&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We now head back to the United Kingdom, but this time to the—still empty for some reason—BT Sports Studios in London, England.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gallus has been busting the guts of Noam Dar and Sha Samuels lately, as they hijacked what would have been the first 2022 episode of Noam Dar’s Supernova Sessions. The reason why Wolfgang &amp;amp; Mark and Joe Coffey converted that episode into “Gallus Boys On Talk” is because Joe Coffey wants to fight Noam Dar for the NXT UK Heritage Cup championship. Jordan Devlin was also added to the mix because—besides that he supposed to be a guest on Supernova Sessions—he wanted his sunglasses back from Gallus member Wolfgang. (The sunglasses were stolen from Devlin’s locker room a couple months ago on NXT UK.) Devlin blindsiding Wolfgang in the hallway with a steel chair would then lead to a matchup between the two for next week. I would love to see Joe Coffey become Dar’s next challenger for the Heritage Cup to be honest, even after having a good match that ended in a draw with A-Kid weeks ago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of A-Kid, him teaching Saxon Huxley proper etiquette—from how to eat, to how to play chess, to how to enjoy classical music, to how to speak properly, and so forth—gave me a good laugh even before the two competed in a one-on-one match. I’m curious to see if they’ll also become a tag team, even whether or not A-Kid teaching him manners continues for a few more weeks or so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-03-27/nxtuk 6.PNG&quot; alt=&quot;NXTUK&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Making “teams” the keyword in this next paragraph (regardless of how short this paragraph will be before talking about the main event), we learned that Moustache Mountain will defend the NXT UK Tag Team Championship against Ashton Smith &amp;amp; Oliver Carter in two weeks. It will definitely be interesting to watch a match between a veteran tag team and an underdog tag team for gold. After all, it’s good to see Smith and Carter picking up more wins, even after they did so in a four-team tournament that occurred as soon as 2022 began.
Last but not least, I enjoyed the main event match between Nathan Frazer and Die Familie member Teoman. It was good to see Frazer on a roll after giving Walter (or Gunther as we nowadays call him) a run for his money weeks ago; his momentum continued after picking up a win over Teoman, as well as shooing away interference by the rest of Die Familie. I would love to see Frazer continue to build his momentum, even if it leads to closing in on gold in NXT UK. Plus, I’m also curious to see what other plans Die Familie has when it comes to being a heel stable wreaking havoc on this brand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the match results from London…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-amale-defeated-nina-samuels-with-the-hope-breaker-this-match-was-made-after-last-week-nina-mocked-amale-by-calling-her-hopeless-in-an-interview&quot;&gt;Match #1: Amale defeated Nina Samuels with the Hope Breaker; this match was made after, last week, Nina mocked Amale by calling her “hopeless” in an “interview.”&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My score: 2/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-a-kid-defeated-saxon-huxley-with-a-springboard-moonsault-into-a-ddt-both-men-showed-sportsmanship-afterwards&quot;&gt;Match #2: A-Kid defeated Saxon Huxley with a springboard moonsault into a DDT; both men showed sportsmanship afterwards.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My score: 2/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-nathan-frazer-defeated-teoman-w-rohan-raja-and-charlie-dempsey&quot;&gt;Main event: Nathan Frazer defeated Teoman (w/ Rohan Raja and Charlie Dempsey).&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Towards the end, Dempsey attempted to interfere while Raja distracted the referee until Frazer knocked him off the apron. Then, after knocking Teoman off the top rope, Frazer defeated him with a corkscrew 450 splash. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;205-live&quot;&gt;205 Live&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last but not least, we return to Orlando for 205 Live.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unlike the past episodes or so, we were able to have 16 minutes of action in three minutes for a show that’s nowadays 30 minutes long, and has been ever since 205 Live got together with NXT, back when it was still the black-and-gold brand, and back when the roster had cruiserweight in the double digits as well as the then active NXT Cruiserweight Championship. (That, as well as 205 originally meant for the weight limit for those that wanted to compete as cruiserweights and fight for that title until it became a run-in-the-mill three-digit number as soon as multiple cruiserweights were wished the best of luck in their future endeavors.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-03-27/205 Live 6.PNG&quot; alt=&quot;205Live&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Out of the three matches that occurred this week, the opening match between Ikemen Jiro and Trick Williams was my favorite of the three. Even though the opener looked like a match that you would normally see on NXT nowadays ever since the conversion from black-and-gold to multicolored, it was still a very good back-and-forth match that occurred on this episode. Plus, it was good to see Trick Williams in singles action after seeing him managing his friend—and current NXT North American champion—Carmelo Hayes, as well as tagging with Hayes on occasion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Onto the results of the three matches that occurred in Orlando…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-trick-williams-w-carmelo-hayes-defeated-ikemen-jiro-w-kushida-with-a-running-swinging-neckbreaker&quot;&gt;Match #1: Trick Williams (w/ Carmelo Hayes) defeated Ikemen Jiro (w/ Kushida) with a running swinging neckbreaker.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-lash-legend-defeated-erica-yan&quot;&gt;Match #2: Lash Legend defeated Erica Yan;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Towards the end, Erica went for a back elbow from the middle rope until Lash caught her and put her in a curved torture rack which then led to Lash winning by submission. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-joe-gacy-w-harland-defeated-xyon-quinn-before-the-match-started-gacy-took-credit-for-making-205-live-more-inclusive&quot;&gt;Main event: Joe Gacy (w/ Harland) defeated Xyon Quinn. Before the match started, Gacy took credit for making 205 Live “more inclusive.”&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Towards the end, Gacy attempted to get out of the ring, and Quinn tried to stop him until Harland grabbed Gacy by the arm; as soon as Harland pulled Gacy away from Quinn, Quinn ended up throat first into the top rope, leading to Gacy defeating him with a handspring clothesline. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;next-time&quot;&gt;Next time…&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you guessed that I’m taking a look back at part 2 of wXw Back To the Roots, you are correct. That, as well as recapping the four shows ICW Fight Club, NXT, NXT UK, and 205 Live.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading! I’ll see you next time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Photos shown in the newsletter are from WWE, ICW and wXw.)&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>pro-darin</name></author><category term="articles" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>