<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-12-31T14:45:07+00:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Wrestling With Johners</title><subtitle>Pro Wrestling podcast with news, reviews and debate from WWE, NXT, NXT:UK, AEW, NJPW, Indy Wrestling and so much more. Listen to Wrestling With Johners on Apple Podcasts, Google Podcasts, Spotify, Podbean, Podcast Addict, Castbox, YouTube or wherever you get your podcasts.</subtitle><author><name>John Scott</name></author><entry><title type="html">AEW - Just My Opinion!</title><link href="/articles/AEW-Just-My-Opinion/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="AEW - Just My Opinion!" /><published>2019-12-30T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-12-30T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/AEW%20Just%20My%20Opinion</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/AEW-Just-My-Opinion/">&lt;p&gt;This week I am focussing on AEW, a lot has been said and written about the new kids on the block over the last 12 months in FB groups, Pods, Vlogs and just about everywhere else you can imagine so I am just going to focus on my opinions and perceptions of what I have enjoyed or not and what I feel about All Elite Wrestling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To begin, I guess we start at the beginning… variety is the spice of life so when word of a new promotion came about I looked on it as a positive, the fact that the names associated with it were well known and popular in the industry, and looked like they would be getting some hefty financial backing I was certainly intrigued and hopeful that this would be good for wrestling on the whole.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What followed over the coming months actually turned me OFF the idea of AEW. We all know about keyboard warriors and how the IWC generally works but all this went into over drive in the build up to AEW – sign this guy, sign that guy, AEW will put Vince out of business etc etc. All this was way, WAY before a single episode of Dynamite had aired. It also came across in the shows too and felt a little desperate to grab attention and be controversial. But for the most part as things have progressed that seems to have stopped for the most part with only a few little references which have actually been quite amusing. like Jericho’s list and how he put down the crowd and corrected them that it’s NOT a list – although substituting it for the “Lexicon of Le Champion” didn’t actually mean what they were intending it to mean, but if you think about what we as fans are expected to accept in wrestling then I don’t really think anyone is too fussed by linguistics or grammar &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then there was the weekly argument for bragging rights over viewing figures, which became a much quieter argument once they levelled out!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall I think its excellent for wrestling on the whole to have competition, my opinion from the start is that it is hard to judge over a short period of time so I would be keen to see how things are going in 12 months – can AEW avoid the pitfalls that WWE periodically stumbles head first into? What changes will be seen in WWE to react to AEW? What individuals will step up to the plate for either company to strive for the next level?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Below, I am going to break down my thoughts into things I have seen as positives so far and areas that, in my opinion, need development going forwards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;positives&quot;&gt;Positives&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll start with the AEW Tag Division, growing up watching wrestling tag team teams were a big deal, teams stayed together for long periods of time with a large variety of gimmicks and styles until sometimes you’d get the break out singles star coming out of a team. More recently tag team matches have become increasingly more often used to give ring time/TV time to multiple singles wrestlers. Totally blame Teddy Long here playa!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its no surprise with The Young Bucks being key players in AEW that tag wrestling would get some attention and the teams signed from the start showed that there would be a big focus on this. There’s been a big focus on high flying tag matches, which obviously isn’t for everyone but several of the matches on Dynamite so far have been genuinely top drawer especially during the Tag Title tournament. Having proper teams who have been together for a long time and had matches previously has allowed the division to hit the ground running and most matches have been well put together to showcase the talent and variety of styles. It is also a breath of fresh air that AEW has steered clear of obvious booking decisions – like The Bucks losing early in the title tournament and SCU progressing without Christopher Daniels. It will be interesting to see how the division continues to develop from both talent and storyline perspectives. I’d expect to see Proud and Powerful take the titles in 2020 not only as they are a fantastic team but it would make sense for the Inner Circle to gain more gold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Promos, for the most part have been excellent week after week with Jericho obviously setting a pretty high bar which the likes of Cody, MJF and Scorpio Sky have really risen to. MJF in particular really shone in his back and forth with Le Champion after turning on Cody, the back and forth between the two was in equal parts amusing and intense while moving forward the narrative of the relationship between MJF and Cody.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The highlight for me though has been Cody Rhodes, the verbal sparring leading up to his title showdown with Jericho was brilliant, both with in ring promos and the taped vignettes. Cody has a great look with his expensive suits and how he represents the corporate side of the Brand but when he speaks in the ring, he portrays so much passion and respect for the business he commands attention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are a number of new names and faces appearing regularly in AEW who have impressed me, they may not be new to everyone but they are to me. Darby Allin and Joey Janela are both names I was aware of prior to watching Dynamite weekly and both have shown that they are more than simply gimmick wrestlers. Sammy Guevara in particular has grown on me rapidly, the opening Dynamite match vs Cody didn’t impress me much but how he has developed as a part of the Inner Circle he has gone up considerably in my estimation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jurassic Express as a unit are very new to me but both in ring and as a gimmick, they have been very impressive, Luchasaurus has a phenomenal look, hard hitting style and his brief bit of mic work facing off against Jericho was great and unexpected. Jungle Boy has impressed in his matches despite a losing record – he sells really well which is fortunate given the amount of time he spends on the receiving end but also has a good offensive move set. Marko Stunt is a phenomenon all of himself, he reminds me so much of Spike Dudley for obvious reasons. He always seems to be having fun despite being thrown around like a ragdoll!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, Orange Cassidy…. I absolutely love this gimmick, I probably shouldn’t but I do! I have spent far too much time recently watching match after match on YouTube and it just really works – obviously he is a really talented wrestler and athlete but his gimmick shows that he doesn’t need that to get over. From what I have seen in AEW he is being booked brilliantly and can’t wait to see what they do with him going forwards, but for now just being alongside the Best Friends with little involvements here and there is working really well for him as is evident by the pops he is getting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kenny Omega obviously isn’t a new face, but he is someone that I knew more by reputation than from seeing all that much of him, I have watched some NJPW over the last few years but never consistently. Early impressions in AEW for me were a bit mixed, I am not sure if he was deliberately being held back so it didn’t look like the execs were getting the rub from their positions, but in recent weeks the more I have seen of him I am starting to “get” the hype around him and would now say I am a fan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, I can’t talk about the positives of AEW without talking about Le Champion, Chris Jericho may be sporting a dad bod these days and the Judas Elbow is a People Elbow/Five knuckle shuffle type move in my opinion but I have always loved watching Jericho in the ring. Watching the way he moves around the ring, plays the crowd reacts and interacts with his opponents is always impressive and his mic work is consistently good and utilises it perfectly to go with the heel persona even down to how he pronounces Tony Schiavone’s name. Ignore the associated names and financial clout behind them AEW is still a fledgling company so to have Jericho involved and furthermore have him at the pinnacle of the Brand is vitally important.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;requires-development&quot;&gt;Requires development&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TV presentation – in my opinion from the PPVs so far and Dynamite there is a great deal of room for improvement in how AEW is presented technically, there have been a number of mistakes and gaffs so far which need to be ironed out – say what you want about Raw/Smackdown but the production values are sky high in comparison to AEW at this point. The highlight of this which will also lead onto my next point is the women’s Casino Battle Royale which I can only describe as a complete clusterf*** in terms of the presentation and commentary as well as the in-ring action. And remember when Tony Schiavone was off doing something else and they had some random stage hand on comms for a bit…. I don’t think anyone had any idea what was going on then!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before I start on the Women’s division, I have to say that improvements have been seen since I first started prepping this piece but there’s still a lot of scope to get better. The division is missing some top talent, a lot of what was making it to TV in the early weeks was a really low standard. I struggle to buy in to Rhio as champion – and I usually like an underdog – she seems far too timid and lacks in presence, on the flip side I think it would be equally bad had they put the title on Nyla Rose who I don’t feel has a great deal of in ring skill based on what I have seen so far. Hikaru Shida has really impressed me so far and Emi Sakura is great although arguably reaching the end of her career now – I recall seeing her about 10 years ago at an Indy show in Wolverhampton. The recent addition of Kris Statlander is a definite plus for AEWs women’s division though as she has looked very impressive in her matches so far, although would question her walking almost straight into the title picture&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Explaining the unknowns seems to have been a bit of an issue for AEW for example… “that’s the Butcher…. That’s the Blade…” but who are they? “It’s the Butcher and the Blade and the Bunny!” As a unit they are quite intriguing but the introduction was so random with zero build it didn’t make a whole heap of sense. Similarly, with Kris Statlander there seems to be zero build, and very little acknowledgement or explanation of her being “The Galaxy’s Greatest Alien”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And finally, Good Ol JR – it pains me to say it but I think his time is done, its almost like he has become a caricature of himself and speaks and shouts mostly nonsense throughout the broadcast. I quite like Excalibur and I can put up with Schiavone although I think they would be better off using new names on commentary who are more relevant and “in the know” for the modern product, I wouldn’t be averse to wheeling JR out for special matches or occasions but I’d prefer to hear a more modern voice alongside the in ring action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So that’s just my opinion on AEW so far, I remain open minded and hope to enjoy the ride over the coming months and see what changes in the business&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;name-drop&quot;&gt;Name Drop…&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With each article I will try to add in a relevant name drop for a wrestler I have met or experience I have had. Since we’re talking AEW I’ll throw back to meeting Trent Berreta at Kamikaze Pro’s “Project K” show. Trent had an amazing match against Pete Dunne, on a card which also included Eddie Dennis vs Tommaso Ciampa. Both matches were fantastic and it’s hard to pick between the two. Trent vs Pete was technically amazing and demonstrated great story telling throughout with some great spots and then was great meeting and chatting with fans at the end of the show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2019-12-30/Trent Barretta pic.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;trent baretta&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am on Twitter where I have a new profile – Matt Based Wrestling - just to focus on all things wrestling related, you can follow me at &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/mattbasedwres01&quot;&gt;@mattbasedwres01&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>matt-bayliss</name></author><summary type="html">This week I am focussing on AEW, a lot has been said and written about the new kids on the block over the last 12 months in FB groups, Pods, Vlogs and just about everywhere else you can imagine so I am just going to focus on my opinions and perceptions of what I have enjoyed or not and what I feel about All Elite Wrestling.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">WWJPod - Pro Wrestling End of Year &amp;amp; End of Decade Awards 2019</title><link href="/articles/End-Of-Year-Awards-2019/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="WWJPod - Pro Wrestling End of Year &amp; End of Decade Awards 2019" /><published>2019-12-30T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-12-30T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/End%20Of%20Year%20Awards%202019</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/End-Of-Year-Awards-2019/">&lt;p&gt;When I first started to enjoy professional wrestling in late 1991/early 1992, in a pre-internet era, I would search far and wide for every wrestling magazine title available in the UK during that period of time. I would read every magazine from cover to cover. From The Ring, to Pro Wrestling Illustrated, the WWF magazine and WCW magazine, to name but a few. But the one magazine that stood head and shoulders above all the others was a certain wrestling magazine, called Superstars of Wrestling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;S.O.W was a UK based wrestling magazine, written and edited by Findlay Martin. Superstars of Wrestling was the only magazine that took an objective view on pro wrestling, with a forthright writing style that gave us fans an honest peek behind the curtain of our beloved and favourite form of (sports) entertainment – Professional Wrestling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a couple of years, Superstars of Wrestling transitioned into being Power Slam magazine (1994) and became my monthly go-to wrestling magazine for another 20 years, until its demise in 2014. Besides being the best wrestling magazine on the shelves of W.H.Smith for over 20 years, it also gave us wrestling fans a fantastic range of articles and regular features that held my interest and had me genuinely excited for each new edition. One of those features was their annual Power Slam End of Year reader’s awards. I would spend hours fulling out my nominations for all of the categories on offer, and it would be an exciting opportunity to add my “expert” views on all that had gone down in the world of Pro Wrestling, from the previous 12 months.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, in honour of Power Slam’s End of Year Awards, I decided to do something similar, in the lead up to our End of Year Awards podcast special on 21st December 2019. By offering the listeners of the WWJ Pod an opportunity to vote on who they believe should be the deserved winners of our very own annual Pro Wrestling awards. And with 2019 being the last year from the 2010’s decade, there are also a few ‘End of Decade Awards’ up for grabs in amongst this year’s awards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember, all of the winners and all of those nominated were voted for by the listeners of the Wrestling With Johners podcast. So, thanks to everyone who took the time to cast their votes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enjoy the full run-down of nominees and winners to all 25 categories below!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol id=&quot;markdown-toc&quot;&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#breakout-star-of-the-year&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-breakout-star-of-the-year&quot;&gt;Breakout Star of the Year&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#announcer-of-the-year-2019&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-announcer-of-the-year-2019&quot;&gt;Announcer of the Year 2019&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#factionstable-of-the-year-2019&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-factionstable-of-the-year-2019&quot;&gt;Faction/Stable of the Year 2019&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#best-gimmick-for-2019&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-best-gimmick-for-2019&quot;&gt;Best Gimmick for 2019&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#indy-promotion-of-the-year-2019&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-indy-promotion-of-the-year-2019&quot;&gt;Indy Promotion of the Year 2019&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#indy-wrestler-of-the-year-2019&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-indy-wrestler-of-the-year-2019&quot;&gt;Indy Wrestler of the Year 2019&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#angle--storyline-of-the-year-2019&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-angle--storyline-of-the-year-2019&quot;&gt;Angle / Storyline of the Year 2019&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#worst-wrestler-of-the-year-2019&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-worst-wrestler-of-the-year-2019&quot;&gt;Worst Wrestler of the Year 2019&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#biggest-letdown-match-of-the-year-2019&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-biggest-letdown-match-of-the-year-2019&quot;&gt;Biggest Letdown match of the Year 2019&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#worst-ppvshow-of-the-year-2019&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-worst-ppvshow-of-the-year-2019&quot;&gt;Worst PPV/Show of the Year 2019&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#babyface-of-the-year-2019&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-babyface-of-the-year-2019&quot;&gt;Babyface of the Year 2019&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#heel-of-the-year-2019&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-heel-of-the-year-2019&quot;&gt;Heel of the Year 2019&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#biggest-shockmoment-of-the-year-2019&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-biggest-shockmoment-of-the-year-2019&quot;&gt;Biggest Shock/Moment of the Year 2019&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#most-improved-wrestler-for-2019&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-most-improved-wrestler-for-2019&quot;&gt;Most Improved Wrestler for 2019&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#comeback-of-the-year-2019&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-comeback-of-the-year-2019&quot;&gt;Comeback of the Year 2019&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#showppv-of-the-decade-2010-2019&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-showppv-of-the-decade-2010-2019&quot;&gt;Show/PPV of the Decade (2010-2019)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#match-of-the-decade-2010-2019&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-match-of-the-decade-2010-2019&quot;&gt;Match of the Decade (2010-2019)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#wrestler-of-the-decade-2010-2019&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-wrestler-of-the-decade-2010-2019&quot;&gt;Wrestler of the Decade (2010-2019)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#brightest-prospect-for-2020&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-brightest-prospect-for-2020&quot;&gt;Brightest Prospect for 2020&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#wrestling-promotion-of-the-year-2019&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-wrestling-promotion-of-the-year-2019&quot;&gt;Wrestling Promotion of the Year 2019&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#tag-team-of-the-year-2019&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-tag-team-of-the-year-2019&quot;&gt;Tag team of the Year 2019&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#showppv-of-the-year-2019&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-showppv-of-the-year-2019&quot;&gt;Show/PPV of the Year 2019&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#match-of-the-year-2019&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-match-of-the-year-2019&quot;&gt;Match of the Year 2019&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#female-wrestler-of-the-year-2019&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-female-wrestler-of-the-year-2019&quot;&gt;Female wrestler of the Year 2019&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#male-wrestler-of-the-year-2019&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-male-wrestler-of-the-year-2019&quot;&gt;Male wrestler of the Year 2019&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;breakout-star-of-the-year&quot;&gt;Breakout Star of the Year&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nominees:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MJF&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Private Party&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Jordan Devlin&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sammy Guevara&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Triple Winners:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rhea Ripley&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2019-12-30/end-of-year-awards-pics/Rhea Ripley.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;rhea ripley&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keith Lee&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2019-12-30/end-of-year-awards-pics/Keith Lee.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;keith lee&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Darby Allin&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2019-12-30/end-of-year-awards-pics/Darby Allin.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;darby allin&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;announcer-of-the-year-2019&quot;&gt;Announcer of the Year 2019&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nominees:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Nigel McGuiness&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cory Graves&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Excalibur&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tom Philips&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Vic Joseph&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Winner: Mauro Ranallo&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2019-12-30/end-of-year-awards-pics/Mauro Ranallo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;mauro ranallo&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;factionstable-of-the-year-2019&quot;&gt;Faction/Stable of the Year 2019&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nominees:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Jurassic Express&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Elite&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Inner Circle&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Winner: Undisputed Era&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2019-12-30/end-of-year-awards-pics/Undisputed Era.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;undisputed era&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;best-gimmick-for-2019&quot;&gt;Best Gimmick for 2019&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nominees:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Luchasaurus&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Viking Raiders&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;‘The Planets Champion’ Daniel Bryan&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cara Noir&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Winner: The Fiend&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2019-12-30/end-of-year-awards-pics/The Fiend 1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;the fiend&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;indy-promotion-of-the-year-2019&quot;&gt;Indy Promotion of the Year 2019&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nominations:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;NWA&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;IMPACT Wrestling&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;AAW&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Destiny&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;TNT&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Beyond Wrestling&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;IWE:UK&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Winner: Progress Wrestling&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2019-12-30/end-of-year-awards-pics/Progress logo.png&quot; alt=&quot;progress wrestling&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;indy-wrestler-of-the-year-2019&quot;&gt;Indy Wrestler of the Year 2019&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nominees:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Orange Cassidy&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Eddie Ryan&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;James Storm&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Damian Dunne&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Jordynne Grace&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Filthy Tom Lawler&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Marty Scurll&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Will Ospreay&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Winner: David Starr&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2019-12-30/end-of-year-awards-pics/David Starr.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;david starr&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;angle--storyline-of-the-year-2019&quot;&gt;Angle / Storyline of the Year 2019&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nominees:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Introduction to the Fiend/Firefly funhouse&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Cody/MJF storyline&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Jericho/Cody build to their Full Gear world title match&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Finn Balor’s heel turn&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Double Winners:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The NXT Invasion of Smackdown and main roster in build towards Survivor Series&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2019-12-30/end-of-year-awards-pics/NXT invades Smackdown.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;nxt invasion&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kofi-Mania and Kofi’s march to WrestleMania 35&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2019-12-30/end-of-year-awards-pics/Kofimania.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;kofimania&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;worst-wrestler-of-the-year-2019&quot;&gt;Worst Wrestler of the Year 2019&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nominees:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cody&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mike Kanellis&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Brock Lesnar&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Seth Rollins&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Becky Lynch&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bray Wyatt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Winner: King Baron Corbin&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2019-12-30/end-of-year-awards-pics/King Corbin.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;king baron corbin&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;biggest-letdown-match-of-the-year-2019&quot;&gt;Biggest Letdown match of the Year 2019&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nominees:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lynch vs. Rousey vs. Flair (WM 35 main event)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lynch vs. Bailey vs. Baszler (Survivor Series main event)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Brock Lesnar vs Kofi 10 sec SD match&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Brock vs Cain Velasquez (Crown Jewel)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Undertaker vs Goldberg (Super Showdown)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Kay Lee Ray vs Toni Storm (NXT:UK TakeOver Cardiff)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Winner: Hell In A Cell main event (The Fiend vs Seth Rollins – WWE Universal Championship)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2019-12-30/end-of-year-awards-pics/Rollins vs The Fiend HIAC 2019.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;fiend vs seth rollins&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;worst-ppvshow-of-the-year-2019&quot;&gt;Worst PPV/Show of the Year 2019&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nominees:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;WWE Crown Jewel&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;WWE Stomping Grounds&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;NWA Into the Fire&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;AEW Dynamite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Winner: WWE Hell In A Cell 2019&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2019-12-30/end-of-year-awards-pics/hELL IN A cELL ppv 2019.webp&quot; alt=&quot;hell in a cell 2019&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;babyface-of-the-year-2019&quot;&gt;Babyface of the Year 2019&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nominees:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Luchasaurus&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Johnny Gargano&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cody&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Keith Lee&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tyler Bate&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Kenny Omega&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Will Ospreay&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Winner: Kofi Kingston&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2019-12-30/end-of-year-awards-pics/kofi kingston.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;kofi kingston&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;heel-of-the-year-2019&quot;&gt;Heel of the Year 2019&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nominees:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MJF&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Fiend Bray Wyatt&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Adam Cole&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Seth Rollins (before the actual heel turn)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Winner: ‘Le Champion’ Chris Jericho&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2019-12-30/end-of-year-awards-pics/Chris Jericho.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;chris jericho&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;biggest-shockmoment-of-the-year-2019&quot;&gt;Biggest Shock/Moment of the Year 2019&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nominees:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Kenta’s heel turn on Shibata&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;NXT’S Invasion of Smackdown and the main roster&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Jon Moxley’s shocking arrival in AEW at Double or Nothing&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MJF throwing in the towel during Cody’s match with Jericho&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Kofimania and Kofi winning the WWE championship at WM35&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CM Punk’s return to the wrestling as a guest host of WWE Backstage on FOX&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Winner: Finn Balors heel turn on Johnny Gargano on NXT&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2019-12-30/end-of-year-awards-pics/Finn Balor heel turn.png&quot; alt=&quot;finn balors heel turn&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;most-improved-wrestler-for-2019&quot;&gt;Most Improved Wrestler for 2019&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nominees:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mustafa Ali&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Rhea Ripley&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Chad Gable (Shorty G)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Humberto Carrillo&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cody&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Winner: Bray Wyatt/The Fiend&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2019-12-30/end-of-year-awards-pics/Bray Wyatt 2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;bray wyatt the fiend&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;comeback-of-the-year-2019&quot;&gt;Comeback of the Year 2019&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nominees:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Jon Moxley&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CM Punk&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Finn Balor&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;NWA&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tony Shiavone&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tommaso Ciampa&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;IMPACT Wrestling&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Winner: Bray Wyatt/The Fiend&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2019-12-30/end-of-year-awards-pics/The Fiend 2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;bray wyatt/the fiend&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;showppv-of-the-decade-2010-2019&quot;&gt;Show/PPV of the Decade (2010-2019)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nominees:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;NXT Takeover New Orleans (2018)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;NXT Takeover Wargames 2017, 2018, 2019&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;NJPW WrestleKingdom 9, 10, 11, 12&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;WWE MITB 2011&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;WWE Survivor Series 2019&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;WrestleMania 26 &amp;amp; 28&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Winner: Wrestlemania 30 (2014)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2019-12-30/end-of-year-awards-pics/Wrestlemania 30.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;wrestlemania 30&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-of-the-decade-2010-2019&quot;&gt;Match of the Decade (2010-2019)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nominees:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cole vs Gargano - NXT Takeover: 25 (2/3 falls stipulation match - 2019)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Kenny Omega vs Okada - Wrestle Kingdom 11 (2017)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ciampa vs Gargano  - NXT Takeover: New Orleans (2018)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sasha Banks vs Bailey - NXT Takeover Brooklyn (2015)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cody vs Dustin Rhodes – AEW Double Or Nothing (2019)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Shawn Michaels vs Undertaker - WrestleMania 26 (2010)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Winner: CM Punk vs John Cena (WWE Championship – Money In The Bank 2011)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2019-12-30/end-of-year-awards-pics/Cena vs Punk MITB 2011.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;punk vs cena&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;wrestler-of-the-decade-2010-2019&quot;&gt;Wrestler of the Decade (2010-2019)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nominees:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Chris Jericho&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Kazuchika Okada&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Seth Rollins&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tatsuyo Naito&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Kenny Omega&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CM Punk&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Double Winners:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AJ Styles&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2019-12-30/end-of-year-awards-pics/AJ Styles decade.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;aj styles&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daniel Bryan&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2019-12-30/end-of-year-awards-pics/Daniel Bryan decade.png&quot; alt=&quot;daniel bryan&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;brightest-prospect-for-2020&quot;&gt;Brightest Prospect for 2020&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nominees:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Rhea Ripley&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Damien Priest&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Hangman Adam Page&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Luchasaurus&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Matt Riddle&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Io Shirai&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Camron Grimes&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Jack Evans&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MJF&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Winner: Keith Lee&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2019-12-30/end-of-year-awards-pics/Keith Lee 2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;keith lee&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;wrestling-promotion-of-the-year-2019&quot;&gt;Wrestling Promotion of the Year 2019&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nominees:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;WWE&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;AEW&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;New Japan Pro Wrestling&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;NWA&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;IMPACT Wrestling&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Progress wrestling&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;IWE:UK&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Winner: NXT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2019-12-30/end-of-year-awards-pics/NXT.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;nxt&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tag-team-of-the-year-2019&quot;&gt;Tag team of the Year 2019&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nominees:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Undisputed Era&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Young Bucks&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Private Party&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Viking Raiders&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;LAX (Santana &amp;amp; Ortiz)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Kabuki Warriors&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The New Day&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Bone Brothers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Winners: The Lucha Brothers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2019-12-30/end-of-year-awards-pics/LUCHA BROS.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;lucha bros&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;showppv-of-the-year-2019&quot;&gt;Show/PPV of the Year 2019&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nominees:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;AEW Double or Nothing&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;IWE:UK Road to Glory&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;NXT Takeover Wargames 2019&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Survivor Series 2019&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;NXT:UK Takeover Cardiff&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;AEW Full Gear&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Winner: NXT Takeover: New York&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2019-12-30/end-of-year-awards-pics/Takeover New York.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;nxt takeover new york&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-of-the-year-2019&quot;&gt;Match of the Year 2019&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nominees:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Adam Cole vs Johnny Gargano (NXT Takeover: New York)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Adam Cole vs Johnny Gargano (NXT Takeover: 25)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Kenny Omega vs Jon Moxley (Unsanctioned match at AEW Full Gear)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pete Dunne vs Adam Cole (Survivor Series 2019)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Will Ospreay vs Shingo Takagi (NJPW Best of Super Jr’s 2019)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cody vs Dustin Rhodes (AEW Double Or Nothing)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Winner: Tyler Bate vs WALTER (NXT:UK Takeover Cardiff)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2019-12-30/end-of-year-awards-pics/Bate Walter.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;bate vs walter&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;female-wrestler-of-the-year-2019&quot;&gt;Female wrestler of the Year 2019&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nominees:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Arisha Hoshiki&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Victoria Adams&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Rhea Ripley&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Io Shirai&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Shayna Baszler&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Double Winners:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Becky Lynch&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2019-12-30/end-of-year-awards-pics/Becky.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;becky lynch&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tessa Blanchard&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2019-12-30/end-of-year-awards-pics/Tessa.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;tessa Blanchard&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;male-wrestler-of-the-year-2019&quot;&gt;Male wrestler of the Year 2019&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nominees:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bray Wyatt/The Fiend&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Kenny Omega&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;WALTER&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;‘The Bastard’ PAC&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bob Sharpe&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Kofi Kingston&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pete Dunne&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Kazuchika Okada&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Chris Jericho&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Roderick Strong&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Winner: Adam Cole&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2019-12-30/end-of-year-awards-pics/Adam Cole 2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;adam cole&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html">When I first started to enjoy professional wrestling in late 1991/early 1992, in a pre-internet era, I would search far and wide for every wrestling magazine title available in the UK during that period of time. I would read every magazine from cover to cover. From The Ring, to Pro Wrestling Illustrated, the WWF magazine and WCW magazine, to name but a few. But the one magazine that stood head and shoulders above all the others was a certain wrestling magazine, called Superstars of Wrestling.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep89 - Interview with CHA CHA CHARLIE (Coastal Championship Wrestling)</title><link href="/podcasts/EP89/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep89 - Interview with CHA CHA CHARLIE (Coastal Championship Wrestling)" /><published>2019-12-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-12-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP89</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP89/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep88 - End of Year &amp;amp; End of Decade Awards 2019 (with @DitsOnWrestling)</title><link href="/podcasts/EP88/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep88 - End of Year &amp; End of Decade Awards 2019 (with @DitsOnWrestling)" /><published>2019-12-21T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-12-21T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP88</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP88/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">I Have An Addiction</title><link href="/articles/I-Have-An-Addiction/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I Have An Addiction" /><published>2019-12-18T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-12-18T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/I%20Have%20An%20Addiction</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/I-Have-An-Addiction/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;ladies-and-gentlemen-my-name-is-lexi-helms-and-i-have-an-addiction&quot;&gt;Ladies and Gentlemen: My name is Lexi Helms and I have an addiction…&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This addiction is something that affects my daily habits, actions in situations and the world, drains my money, is a habit that started as a child and is something I cannot live without. Sometimes, it hangs in my wardrobe, influencing my style and sometimes causes random strangers to come and speak to me. Most recently, it has influenced my hair style and Christmas Tree decorations. My addiction can take me on the highest high and send me into a blubbering mess. It also frequents my laptop, phone, social media stream and my DVD collection - not to mention my TV. It’s something my mother hates, something I watch mainly with males and something my significant other actively encourages… Ladies and Gentlemen, my name is Lexi Helms and my addiction is pro-wrestling [tell me you did NOT read that with Paul Hayman’s voice!].&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was two when this addiction started -my brother was watching it and I became hooked. I, to this day, cannot tell you why I liked it and for a while it was all I spoke about and wanted to play. Having two brothers who actively encouraged me to be Superfly Jimmy Snuka and jump off the sofa onto one of them only deepened my love for it. At one point I wanted to BE the Ultimate Warrior at the age of 3 [and yes, I cried when he was inducted into the HOF, cried when he died and yes, I cry at documentaries because I’m still not over it!] and was not ashamed to admit it to anyone that would listen. I have stuck with it for over 29 years.  It is a sad fact to admit that in this world, it’s often rare to come across a female pro-wrestling fan. I didn’t get into it simply to look at males in skimpy outfits. Case and point: I once got into a very public argument with a girl over Randy Orton because she insisted his name was a good marketing ploy merely based on his good looks. This coming from a girl who hated wrestling before seeing Orton…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have always loved WWF - until 1996… When, by coincidence, I stumbled across a little-known programme called “Nitro”. Back in the day, Cartoon Network changed to TNT at 9pm, and as a result, Nitro was shown on a Friday night. I was hooked - because I recognised Scott Hall. It was so different to what WWF was offering at the time, and with the absence of Sky Sports in the Sky Package, WCW gave me a guaranteed 2-hour wrestling fix on a Friday night. I remember watching WCW back on ITV in ’92 / 93, but 1996 WCW was different. At one point, on a family holiday to America, I my brothers and I traded rooms to catch the episodes of RAW for Nitro, briefly filling in the blanks during ad breaks. My desire to have wrestling in my life was so great that I used to listen to episodes of Livewire on the old Sky Sports 3 because you could still get sound from the channel, despite having no picture - much to my mother’s annoyance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a Teenager, wrestling was more accessible, and I had caught a few ECW matches here or there - but my confused brain both loved and hated ECW. Part of me loved it, because it was wrestling and especially because RVD blew my mind with what he could do. Part of me hated it, because I had a genuine fear for the safety of the performers in the company. Bear in mind, we were edging towards the tail end of the Attitude Era - Hardcore wrestling in WWF was much tamer than ECW and was the only “hardcore” wrestling I had seen up until this point. I remember only briefly watching ECW mainly because, finally, both mum and I agreed that it was TOO violent. Only now, with the benefit of hindsight, and with an adult mind (to fully understand who Jenna Jameson is, for example) can I fully appreciate ECW and the utter genius that is Paul Hayman. Despite Hayman’s’ brilliance, I must admit that parts of ECW and death matches in other promotions presently still make me uncomfortable – to me, that is not the wrestling that I love, but I understand their appeal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By this point in my addiction (circa 1999), I had also stopped watching Nitro after the decision was made to end Goldbergs’ streak and fell in love with Smack Down!, After Burn and Bottom Line. This was more than enough for the wrestling fix I craved… Until the Invasion storyline. We had gone from a guaranteed 9 hours of wrestling a week (RAW, SmackDown! Nitro and Thunder) to just 4 hours of main shows. So, I again by sheer chance, I stumbled across the “Wrestling Channel” on Sky. This exposed me to the likes of AJ Styles, Christopher Daniels, Jushin Liger and Frankie Kazarian. Their work was good, and it was reassuring that I came across them in other promotions.  During this time, my brother had pointed out that you could now purchase WWF attire over in this country, and, as a result, my brother and I proudly own a Shane O’Mac Baseball shirt - still my pride and joy to this day! From this, I quickly developed a collection of Wrestling-related t-shirts that I still wear to this day:  including Stone Cold, The Rock, John Cena [bring on the hate eh?], Evolution, Batista [more heat for me!], Wade Barrett, Charlotte Flair, AJ Styles, Shinskue Nakamura, DIY, Shane McMahon, Moustache Mountain,  Eddie Gurrereo and William Regal [to name but a few!].&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once the “Invasion” angle finished, wrestling fans were introduced to the “Brand Split”, which was fantastic. The idea that only the Champion would be on both shows was intriguing, making that person feel special and the split made you choose a brand and be loyal to it. I also loved the Raw and SmackDown! Sets respectively but favoured the SmackDown! Fist and, if truth be told, I long for its return.  The storylines were engaging, and both shows pushed and developed young talent. I loved the Nitro element of SmackDown! With the Lucha Libre style and quick paced matches and the fact that RAW had the comforting reassurance of Triple H, Shawn Michaels and… Dare I say it…? Chris Benoit (granted he was on SmackDown! initially). All these only furthered my need for my fix of wrestling - I would pull the all-nighters to watch the PPVs, at the sacrifice of schooling and potential friendships if matches didn’t go the way I wanted to the next day. Then Wrestlemania 21 happened. It was no X7 but it was good enough, and it was clear that some of the old guard were slowing down and the new boys were taking over. It was a fresh start and paved the way for new storylines and rivalries to happen. This era of peace was not going to replicate the Monday Night Wars, but would come close, especially with the addition of the draft picks and Team RAW vs Team SmackDown! matches at Survivor Series.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amongst all this, darker days came… Eddie Gurrereo passed away… then Chris Benoit. The feel of WWE changed, dramatically. But I still watched it. I still loved it. I still invested in it. The impact of the passing of these two greats (and no, I do NOT condone what Benoit did, but you cannot deny his talent pre-June 2007), made people more aware of the “violence” in pro-wrestling (living in America at the time, the news was full of reports on this tragedy, with most of the reports containing false allegations). Seemingly overnight the following happened: Chair shots?  Gone. Blood? Vanished. Weapons? Not used. Target Demographic? Altered, and it was clear I wasn’t in it. Then I noticed TNA Wrestling. And Aces and Eights. This hooked me in again - THIS is what pro-wrestling should be… but then TNA started to make their mistakes and quickly lost my interest, as they had done before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, I went crawling back to WWE, and I am not sorry. Over 4 years ago, I subscribed to the Network I discovered NXT and my word, does the future look bright. NXT Blackpool in 2015 was one of the greatest sporting events I have ever attended - moments still make me giggle and smile several years later. NXT Liverpool in 2016 was also a brilliant show too, but Blackpool just pips it! Then, in December 2016 I got a voicemail telling me I was getting a bonus Christmas present, tickets to see UK Championship Tournament in Blackpool. That night in January 2017 an epiphany happened, and I fell in love with the UK Wrestling scene. I cried when Tyler Bate won the title. I cried when he lost it to Pete Dunne. I cried because Pete Dunne was the UK Champion. I cried when Moustache Mountain won the NXT Tag Team Titles and was bereft when they lost them. I am so excited by other British promotions, and NXT UK. I was at the Liverpool tapings for NXT UK in 2018 (front row, I might add!) and began 2019 with another trip to Blackpool for NXT UK Takeover: Blackpool and the aftermath tapings. Let me tell you, there is nothing like being part of thousands of people calling out Vince McMahon and getting him to respond. Only the UK Fans have the balls to do this with the confidence and pride that you heard at Blackpool and Cardiff. It was deafening at Blackpool and, although I wasn’t there, I have a feeling it was the same in Cardiff. My only hope is that the NXT UK Roster follows the same and to the point format of its American father, seemingly knowing who to push and who to develop, with engaging storylines and there is a huge sense of competition between talent the future of wrestling is brighter than ever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the more refreshing aspects of NXT was their one hour shows, meaning you can go weeks without seeing a superstar, meaning I value their matches more. I’m still undecided if the 2-hour format works. I hope that the development of characters continues to be better than the main roster, seemingly because they’re not shoved down your throats. This environment reminds me of the fabled Attitude Era and how good it was. Because of NXT I have been exposed to the likes of Shinsuke Nakamura, Ricochet, Hedeo Itami, No Way Hose, Cien Almas, Finn Balor, Ember Moon, Alistair Black, Tomaso Ciampa and Johnny Gargano… I could go on and list more. But, more importantly, because of NXT, I have gone on to seek out and watch the likes of ROH and NJPW to see the earlier work of the talent mentioned. So much so, I consider Wrestle Kingdom 11 to be one of the best PPVs’ I’ve ever witnessed! This newfound discovery has created dream scenarios’ where I see Kenny Omega signing to NXT. Because of NXT, I am excited to be a wrestling fan again. I cannot wait for Wednesdays to come around, so I can watch NXT, not to mention how excited I get for NXT: Takeovers and how jealous I was that I couldn’t see NXT at Download this year. My one criticism… If only creative could continue this work with the talents when they’re called up to the main rosters… Let me leave this here, Tyler Breeze, Nakamura and Alistair Black STILL deserve better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also have a changing wrestling scene with the addition of AEW. This offers yet another alternative to the WWE product. I can’t say I’ve watched it religiously (i.e stayed up late to catch it in ‘real time’), but I have watched Dynamite on a regular basis. Despite it being early days, I do see so much potential in the promotion – not just because of the likes of the Young Bucks (they’ll always be Generation Me!), Omega, Cody and Dustin. The product, overall, feels more authentic and revives the sense of ‘anything can happen’. Something that WWE programming has been lacking for a while now (NXT Excluded, of course!). Not to mention the commentary team. Whilst WWE has Mauro, Graves and McGuinness (some of the best around in my opinion), it is comforting to hear Tony Schiavone and JR’s voice on commentary. Another reason why I tune in. Call me nostalgic, but I adore the two of them on commentary, although I must also give credit to Excalibur too. The ‘Wednesday Night War’ is another reason why I am excited to be a wrestling fan again – maybe, just maybe, this is what WWE needs to change its stale ways. This is what can happen when you allow talent to be themselves – Jon Moxley, PAK, Jericho, Sean Spears have become exciting to see again, because you never know what can happen when they’re around. Be it Jericho trolling the fans by calling out their chants, PAKs mean streak or Jon Moxley talking directly down the camera. It makes AEW must see TV. Lets just hope this continues…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I started this piece, I announced that Pro-Wrestling is my addiction. There is no escape from it, it simply is. I have used this piece to introduce myself to new websites that I write for to allow the depth of my addiction to shine through, especially as I know that others feel the same. We know that it is pre-determined and scripted. We know that people will tell us that its fake and will mock us for this admission. On a personal level, I know that people will dislike the fact that my main source of wrestling is WWE, and not independents’ like Progress, ROH or NJPW. I know that WWE make mistakes; If I had a quid (£1) for every time I’ve said “this is bull sh*t! I am Done with this!” I would be more than comfortable! I get why certain talents are pushed and others not. I understand that not every wrestling fan will see eye-to-eye on things like who is the greatest of all time? Who should be pushed now? Why aren’t such and such in the Hall of Fame yet? But this is one of the reasons why I adore the wrestling scene - not everyone agrees, but on that rare occasion when the stars align, and we see greatness (such as Eddie Gurrereo), our belief is suspended, and we unite as one, caught up in the moment, jaws slack, standing in awe. There are no words to describe the feeling of standing in a crowd of people, all sharing a passion and joy in what we’re seeing, chanting so loud it stops a match (American Alpha vs. Blake and Murphy at NXT Blackpool) or that it makes me lose my voice due to a throat infection that followed (I blame Finn and Nakamura at NXT Liverpool and AJ Styles winning the World Title in Manchester in 2017). It is these moments that fuels the addiction, makes me proud to admit that I adore professional wrestling; I crave more; my life is empty without it… and I hope this piece encourages others to admit their addiction too.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>lexi-helms</name></author><summary type="html">Ladies and Gentlemen: My name is Lexi Helms and I have an addiction…</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep87 - WWE TLC Review (John Scott &amp;amp; Jason Lee Wood)</title><link href="/podcasts/EP87/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep87 - WWE TLC Review (John Scott &amp; Jason Lee Wood)" /><published>2019-12-17T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-12-17T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP87</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP87/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep86 – Moxley to join Inner Circle! NXT Triple Threat Main Event WWE TLC Preview</title><link href="/podcasts/EP86/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep86 – Moxley to join Inner Circle!  NXT Triple Threat Main Event  WWE TLC Preview" /><published>2019-12-16T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-12-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP86</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP86/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep85 - 2 Min BRAINBUSTER Quiz (Bonus Ep w/ Kieron Reed)</title><link href="/podcasts/EP85/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep85 - 2 Min BRAINBUSTER Quiz (Bonus Ep w/ Kieron Reed)" /><published>2019-12-10T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-12-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP85</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP85/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep84 - Interview with CJ CARTER (Pro Wrestling CLASH &amp;amp; Turnbuckle TV)</title><link href="/podcasts/EP84/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep84 - Interview with CJ CARTER (Pro Wrestling CLASH &amp; Turnbuckle TV)" /><published>2019-12-05T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-12-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP84</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP84/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Welcome to the Wrestling with Johners website!</title><link href="/articles/Matt-Based-Wrestling/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to the Wrestling with Johners website!" /><published>2019-12-03T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-12-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/Matt%20Based%20Wrestling</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/Matt-Based-Wrestling/">&lt;p&gt;First up I am really looking forward to working with Johners to create content for this website, which I am sure is going to be a great experience. I have loved seeing, well hearing the progress and development of the Wrestling With Johners podcast over the last year or so as well as the growth of the community especially on Facebook!
I have previously written reviews and articles over on The Indy Corner as well as providing some content for the podcast too covering a load of British wrestling including Progress and Kamikaze Pro. A few years back I trained for a while with Kamikaze Pro which meant getting trained by Pete Dunne – although my time there was short lived, mostly due to lack of fitness and an injury plus boring stuff like work!
I was fortunate enough to meet Johners through work, it’s always good to make a friend with shared interests and we’ve been able to attend a variety of shows together including Attack!, 4FW and Progress.
I have been a wrestling fan for close to 30 years now – originally through WWF where the first match I saw was a Bret vs Owen bout and was hooked instantly! I started following British Wrestling much later on and have been to many promotions around the country and been fortunate to see so many talents up close who are now on global TV on a weekly basis, and also had some amazing experiences including camel clutches from Sabu and Uhaa Nation/Apollo Crews, commentating on a Juventud Guerera match as well as a multi person elimination match featuring Joe Coffey, Kay Lee Ray, Kenny Williams, Dan Moloney, Pete Dunne, Robbie X and Tyler Bate and of course I can’t leave out  harassing Eddie Dennis with an inflatable sheep for months with a little help from Uhaa Nation and Tomasso Ciampa!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have also been fortunate enough to meet some big names over the years including Bret Hart, Scott Hall, Sunny, Ted Dibiase, DDP and even the living legend Virgil who I actually had a really good chat with! Although my personal highlight would be meeting the Hardcore Legend Mick Foley on two occasions and in particularly getting a hug from my hero!
Where do I stand on the WWE/AEW battle? I have said from the start that AEW needs time, they need to do their thing but they will only be successful if they can do it over a long period of time and keep the quality high. WWE is far from perfect, although NXT is arguably the closest thing to it in the whole of wrestling at the moment. I actually think AEW is tracking better than I expected them to be at this stage – some of what they are doing so far is phenomenal especially with some of Jericho’s promo work and what they have achieved so far with their tag division.
I am always keen to find the positives in wrestling, anyone who steps inside the ring is there to entertain and put their bodies on the line to do so – are some better than others? Of course, but I don’t see the point in trying to slate people. Similarly I understand everyone is entitled to their opinion and always happy to listen and discuss different views. That’s part of what makes wrestling fandom amazing
I am on Twitter where I have a new profile – Matt Based Wrestling - just to focus on all things wrestling related; you can follow me at @mattbasedwres01&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>matt-bayliss</name></author><summary type="html">First up I am really looking forward to working with Johners to create content for this website, which I am sure is going to be a great experience. I have loved seeing, well hearing the progress and development of the Wrestling With Johners podcast over the last year or so as well as the growth of the community especially on Facebook! I have previously written reviews and articles over on The Indy Corner as well as providing some content for the podcast too covering a load of British wrestling including Progress and Kamikaze Pro. A few years back I trained for a while with Kamikaze Pro which meant getting trained by Pete Dunne – although my time there was short lived, mostly due to lack of fitness and an injury plus boring stuff like work! I was fortunate enough to meet Johners through work, it’s always good to make a friend with shared interests and we’ve been able to attend a variety of shows together including Attack!, 4FW and Progress. I have been a wrestling fan for close to 30 years now – originally through WWF where the first match I saw was a Bret vs Owen bout and was hooked instantly! I started following British Wrestling much later on and have been to many promotions around the country and been fortunate to see so many talents up close who are now on global TV on a weekly basis, and also had some amazing experiences including camel clutches from Sabu and Uhaa Nation/Apollo Crews, commentating on a Juventud Guerera match as well as a multi person elimination match featuring Joe Coffey, Kay Lee Ray, Kenny Williams, Dan Moloney, Pete Dunne, Robbie X and Tyler Bate and of course I can’t leave out harassing Eddie Dennis with an inflatable sheep for months with a little help from Uhaa Nation and Tomasso Ciampa!</summary></entry></feed>