<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-03-23T22:13:56+00:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Wrestling With Johners</title><subtitle>Pro Wrestling podcast with news, reviews and debate from WWE, NXT, NXT:UK, AEW, NJPW, Indy Wrestling and so much more. Listen to Wrestling With Johners on Apple Podcasts, Google Podcasts, Spotify, Podbean, Podcast Addict, Castbox, YouTube or wherever you get your podcasts.</subtitle><author><name>John Scott</name></author><entry><title type="html">Impact Wrestling News and Notes for March 22 2022 - AAA TripleMania XXX to feature Impact talent</title><link href="/alliance-pro-wrestling-network/videos/Impact-Wrestling-News-and-Notes-for-March-22-2022-AAA-TripleMania-XXX-to-feature-Impact-talent/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Impact Wrestling News and Notes for March 22 2022 - AAA TripleMania XXX to feature Impact talent" /><published>2022-03-23T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-03-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/alliance-pro-wrestling-network/videos/Impact%20Wrestling%20News%20and%20Notes%20for%20March%2022%202022%20%20AAA%20TripleMania%20XXX%20to%20feature%20Impact%20talent</id><content type="html" xml:base="/alliance-pro-wrestling-network/videos/Impact-Wrestling-News-and-Notes-for-March-22-2022-AAA-TripleMania-XXX-to-feature-Impact-talent/"></content><author><name>lewis-carlan</name></author><category term="alliance-pro-wrestling-network" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">‘This Journey Starts In Double 03’ #thennowforever #grime #rap #rapper #deverlish #ukhiphop #oxford</title><link href="/half-decent/videos/This-Journey-Starts-In-Double-03-thennowforever-grime-rap-rapper-deverlish-ukhiphop-oxford/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="‘This Journey Starts In Double 03’ #thennowforever #grime #rap #rapper #deverlish #ukhiphop #oxford" /><published>2022-03-23T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-03-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/half-decent/videos/This%20Journey%20Starts%20In%20Double%2003%20thennowforever%20grime%20rap%20rapper%20deverlish%20ukhiphop%20oxford</id><content type="html" xml:base="/half-decent/videos/This-Journey-Starts-In-Double-03-thennowforever-grime-rap-rapper-deverlish-ukhiphop-oxford/"></content><author><name>half-decent</name></author><category term="half-decent" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Colonel Parker Rober Fuller talks Jacques Rougeau, steroids, Ken Shamrock, Bob Roop, the territories</title><link href="/jofo-in-the-ring/Colonel-Parker-Rober-Fuller-talks-Jacques-Rougeau-steroids-Ken-Shamrock-Bob-Roop-the-territories/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Colonel Parker Rober Fuller talks Jacques Rougeau, steroids, Ken Shamrock, Bob Roop, the territories" /><published>2022-03-23T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-03-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/jofo-in-the-ring/Colonel%20Parker%20Rober%20Fuller%20talks%20Jacques%20Rougeau%20steroids%20Ken%20Shamrock%20Bob%20Roop%20the%20territories</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jofo-in-the-ring/Colonel-Parker-Rober-Fuller-talks-Jacques-Rougeau-steroids-Ken-Shamrock-Bob-Roop-the-territories/"></content><author><name>jofo-in-the-ring</name></author><category term="jofo-in-the-ring" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Kevin Sullivan &amp;amp; J.J. Dillon on the people’s court with Steve Harvey #shorts</title><link href="/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/Kevin-Sullivan-JJ-Dillon-on-the-peoples-court-with-Steve-Harvey-shorts/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Kevin Sullivan &amp;amp; J.J. Dillon on the people’s court with Steve Harvey #shorts" /><published>2022-03-23T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-03-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/Kevin%20Sullivan%20%20JJ%20Dillon%20on%20the%20peoples%20court%20with%20Steve%20Harvey%20shorts</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/Kevin-Sullivan-JJ-Dillon-on-the-peoples-court-with-Steve-Harvey-shorts/"></content><author><name>jofo-in-the-ring</name></author><category term="jofo-in-the-ring" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Shawn Michaels vs the internet #shorts</title><link href="/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/Shawn-Michaels-vs-the-internet-shorts/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Shawn Michaels vs the internet #shorts" /><published>2022-03-23T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-03-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/Shawn%20Michaels%20vs%20the%20internet%20shorts</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/Shawn-Michaels-vs-the-internet-shorts/"></content><author><name>jofo-in-the-ring</name></author><category term="jofo-in-the-ring" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Grimm &amp;amp; Grime vs The Ragnarockers</title><link href="/lucha-libre-and-laughs/videos/Grimm-Grime-vs-The-Ragnarockers/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Grimm &amp;amp; Grime vs The Ragnarockers" /><published>2022-03-23T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-03-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/lucha-libre-and-laughs/videos/Grimm%20%20Grime%20vs%20The%20Ragnarockers</id><content type="html" xml:base="/lucha-libre-and-laughs/videos/Grimm-Grime-vs-The-Ragnarockers/"></content><author><name>lucha-libre-and-laughs</name></author><category term="lucha-libre-and-laughs" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Scott Oberman vs Joey Hayes - Wrestle Island 🏝 (19/12/21) Highlights</title><link href="/my-britwres-journey/videos/Scott-Oberman-vs-Joey-Hayes-Wrestle-Island-191221-Highlights/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Scott Oberman vs Joey Hayes - Wrestle Island 🏝 (19/12/21) Highlights" /><published>2022-03-23T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-03-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/my-britwres-journey/videos/Scott%20Oberman%20vs%20Joey%20Hayes%20%20Wrestle%20Island%20%20191221%20Highlights</id><content type="html" xml:base="/my-britwres-journey/videos/Scott-Oberman-vs-Joey-Hayes-Wrestle-Island-191221-Highlights/"></content><author><name>my-britwres-journey</name></author><category term="my-britwres-journey" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Power Hour w:Counselor Erich Schultz</title><link href="/power-hour/videos/The-Power-Hour-wCounselor-Erich-Schultz/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Power Hour w:Counselor Erich Schultz" /><published>2022-03-23T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-03-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/power-hour/videos/The%20Power%20Hour%20wCounselor%20Erich%20Schultz</id><content type="html" xml:base="/power-hour/videos/The-Power-Hour-wCounselor-Erich-Schultz/"></content><author><name>power-hour</name></author><category term="power-hour" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Issue 1 - Shows of January 1-7, 2022</title><link href="/articles/Issue-1-Shows-of-January-1-7,-2022/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Issue 1 - Shows of January 1-7, 2022" /><published>2022-03-23T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-03-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/Issue%201%20-%20Shows%20of%20January%201-7,%202022</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/Issue-1-Shows-of-January-1-7,-2022/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png&quot; alt=&quot;pro darin&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;introduction-to-the-newsletter&quot;&gt;Introduction to the newsletter&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hello, everybody! My name is Darin Adamczyk, going by the name “Pro-Darin” in this newsletter. For those of you that have seen me in person, on social media, etc., I like to talk about many things such as my family, music, Philadelphia history that I like to learn about (especially what occurred during my lifetime in the city or before I was born), auto racing including NASCAR, the outdoors (such as fishing), and anything else I like to mention like a video of commercials from before my time (or during my time as a kid) on YouTube.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I also like to talk about—believe it or not—is professional wrestling. Yep, you read correctly. When I got into the double-digit years, my father and I—as well as my mother—would watch WWE as well as other shows such as the original ECW which was popular in South Philadelphia, especially at the venue nowadays known as the 2300 Arena. Even though I still like to watch WWE at times, I would also peek into or check out other shows—other major names such as Impact, AEW, Ring of Honor, National Wrestling Alliance, and MLW; independents such as Combat Zone Wrestling, GCW, Atomic Revolutionary Wrestling, Anarchy Wrestling, Underground Wrestling Federation, and House of Hardcore; and international shows such as New Japan, All Japan, Japan’s Freedoms and Mexico’s AAA just to name a few—regardless of how much has changed in the pro wrestling world since the time I started watching WWE. (I started watching WWE more often in the late 1990s back when the Attitude Era was still going on.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this newsletter, I will be talking about WWE shows that I like to watch on Peacock, as well as one show that’s currently on USA Network (and on Peacock one day later). Those shows that I would like to talk about—as well as review—are WWE Pay-Per-View events (starting off with WWE Day 1), NXT 2.0 (or simply NXT regardless of what it reads besides changing from a black-and-gold brand to a multicolored brand), NXT UK, 205 Live, and European indie shows Progress, ICW and wXw. (I might even sneak in a show from a different company and talk about it as well!)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope you enjoy this newsletter! You’re welcome to talk about it, as well as talk about the shows and matches (including your own opinions on them).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;wwe-day-1&quot;&gt;WWE Day 1&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Roman Reigns was scheduled to defend the WWE Universal championship against Brock Lesnar in a rematch from Crown Jewel; after news broke that Reigns was out due to getting COVID-19 (thankfully, we would end up seeing Reigns on SmackDown days later), Lesnar ended up being put in a fatal five-way match for the WWE championship against Big E (who came in as the champion), Seth Rollins, Kevin Owens and Bobby Lashley. Here’s what happened at the State Farm Arena in Atlanta, Georgia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-03-23/WWE DAY 1 Roman.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Day 1&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;pre-show-match-ridge-holland--sheamus-defeated-ricochet--cesaro&quot;&gt;Pre-show match: Ridge Holland &amp;amp; Sheamus defeated Ricochet &amp;amp; Cesaro.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An alright start before the PPV event officially began. A double-team maneuver by Ricochet and Cesaro went awry as one of Ricochet’s feet, during an assisted flip, landed on Holland’s face breaking his nose; this led to Sheamus fight by himself and being able to win via a Brogue Kick to Cesaro. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cue “Straightenin” by Migos, and it’s time for the PPV event!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-the-usos-defeated-the-new-day-to-retain-the-smackdown-tag-team-championship&quot;&gt;Match 1: The Usos defeated the New Day to retain the SmackDown Tag Team championship&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I liked that the Usos paid homage to both Reigns and, towards the end, the Dudley Boyz (or Team 3-D as we also call them) in that matchup; the Usos ended up defeating King Woods and Sir Kofi Kingston after Jimmy and Jey hit Kingston with the 3-D (or “1-D” as Pat McAfee called it…lol…). &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a couple interviews (one to Big E by Kevin Patrick, and one to Atlanta’s hip hop trio Migos by Kayla Braxton), it was time for…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-drew-mcintyre-defeated-madcap-moss-w-happy-corbin&quot;&gt;Match 2: Drew McIntyre defeated Madcap Moss (w/ Happy Corbin)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nothing special about this matchup or the corny jokes Moss made about Atlanta and Drew; Drew won via Claymore. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then came Kevin Owens’ interview, by Sarah Schreiber, where he called the fatal-five way matchup both a “tragedy” and a “travesty” (I believe he ad-libbed in that interview)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;followed by…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-3-rk-bro-defeated-the-street-profits-to-retain-the-raw-tag-team-championship&quot;&gt;Match 3: RK-Bro defeated the Street Profits to retain the Raw Tag Team championship&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hip hop trio Migos accompanied RK-Bro to the ring before sitting next to Raw’s announce team of Jimmy Smith, Byron Saxton and Corey Graves. Plus, I noticed that there was no pyro for when Riddle kicked off his sandals because one of the pipes used for the pyro got knocked off one of the posts during Moss vs. McIntyre. Like Migos, I too enjoyed the matchup; RK-Bro win after an assisted RKO by Riddle and Randy Orton to Montez Ford (after Angelo Dawkins was taken down at ringside). Both teams shook hands afterwards, even while together with Migos. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;McIntyre’s interview, by Megan Morant, was interrupted by Moss and Corbin who ambushed him backstage; the two put a chair around Drew’s throat before Corbin grabbed a steel rig and hit the chair with it. I got a gut feeling that those two aren’t finished with Drew yet. Then, Brock Lesnar—interviewed by Braxton—pretended to be Paul Heyman while vowing to win the WWE championship later that night, and then came…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-4-edge-defeated-the-miz-w-maryse&quot;&gt;Match 4: Edge defeated the Miz (w/ Maryse)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The best match of the night in my opinion. One of my favorite moments during the matchup was Edge giving the Miz, who was draped on the apron, an Edgecution to the floor. Plus, there were typical Miz/Maryse cheating moments; one where the fans told the Miz “You can’t do that!” after he was caught using the ropes to add leverage to the pin, and one where Maryse snuck in a purse shot to Edge. Near the end, another moment I liked occurred as Beth Phoenix appeared and chased Maryse away! This led to Edge defeating the Miz with the Spear. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Patrick interviewed Bobby Lashley with MVP speaking for him, we went to…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-5-becky-lynch-defeated-liv-morgan-to-retain-the-raw-womens-championship&quot;&gt;Match 5: Becky Lynch defeated Liv Morgan to retain the Raw Women’s championship&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the matchup, Liv hit Becky—who was on the top rope—with an awesome sunset flip powerbomb for two. After Liv stomped on Becky’s arm against the steps (just like Becky did to Liv a couple weeks prior), Liv went for the Ob-Liv-ion until Becky countered it with the Manhandle Slam and—while failing to use the ropes for leverage—won. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Seth Rollins was interviewed by Patrick, Johnny Knoxville—via Instagram—announced that he was entering the 2022 Royal Rumble. I know it’s nice to see celebrities attend pro-wrestling events just like MMA fighter Chris Bungard did prior to fighting Jason Reed at night #1 of ICW Fear and Loathing XIII, but I got a gut feeling that it’s not going to go well…lol…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event&quot;&gt;Main event:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brock Lesnar defeated Big E, Bobby Lashley, Seth Rollins, and Kevin Owens in a fatal five-way match to become the new WWE champion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yep, you read correctly. I got a gut feeling that the rivalry between Lesnar and Reigns will be scrapped because of this matchup, even with Reigns recovering from COVID-19. Anyway, it was Suplex City in the beginning until Lashley speared Lesnar through the barricade, then double teaming by Rollins and Owens prior to Big E putting Lashley through the announce table with a uranage. Lesnar recovered near the end of the matchup, F-5’ing his opponents until Lashley speared him for two. Then, Big E hit Lashley with the Big Ending until Lesnar defeated E with the F-5, dethroning E for that title. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;icw-fight-club&quot;&gt;ICW Fight Club&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was the 202nd episode of ICW Fight Club, and was the first episode shown in 2022.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plus, Jason Reed was still with Billy Kirkwood and James R. Kennedy at the announce table after suffering an arm injury at night #1 of Fear and Loathing XIII to Chris Bungard. Here’s what happened at the Glasgow Pro Wrestling Asylum in Scotland…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The show started off with Andy Wild coming into the ring, talking about his matchup against Big Damo in night #2 of F&amp;amp;L XIII which ended in a double count out (time limits occur nowadays, courtesy of Theo Doros who defeated Ravie Davie in a Glasgow Street Fight at night #1 of the aforementioned event); as soon as Wild asked for five more minutes that night, Damo declined.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wild then asked for a rematch against Damo until Damo appeared on the screen and said “no” because he was eyeing on the ICW World heavyweight championship; Damo then told Wild to find him in the Square Go! matchup instead (at the 10th Annual Square Go! on February 20), and Wild accepted that offer. I like seeing this ongoing rivalry now that Damo is back in the indies, especially ICW.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-martin-kirby-defeated-lj-cleary-and-logan-smith-in-a-triple-threat-match&quot;&gt;Match 1: Martin Kirby defeated LJ Cleary and Logan Smith in a triple threat match&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fun while it lasted, even after seeing all three wrestlers trading waistlocks and then pin attempts in the beginning up until—at the tail end of the match—Kirby surprised one of his opponents by countering one of their pins with a pin of his own. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.25/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then came the former DCT as “Jackie Polo” (Jaxn’s previous persona) hosting “The Polo Lounge”, saying that DCT “took his ball and went home” and that he created Jaxn vs. Kez Evans at night #2 of F&amp;amp;L XIII (with Evans winning the ICW World heavyweight title after “Polo” took down Jaxn, around 24 hours after Jaxn defeated Evans for the same title that was vacant at that time).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Polo” then said that Jaxn was supposed to be his guest, but Jaxn was absent; filling in for him was “hungry young talent” that “Polo” wanted instead, and out came Martin McAlistair (or “Marvin” as “Polo” called him). Martin introduced himself, vowing to step up and get his career first win in ICW. As soon as “Polo” ended the show, Martin called him DCT before “Polo” corrected him and then hit “Marvin Mick Alistair” with his polo mallet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Veronica LeStrange interviewed Luke Kyro who was building momentum and carrying it by defeating Leyton Buzzard later on and entering Square Go!, we had…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-she-wolves-defeated-rosie-nyte--ellie-armstrong&quot;&gt;Match 2: She-Wolves defeated Rosie Nyte &amp;amp; Ellie Armstrong&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This match, thanks to Doros, had a 20-minute time-limit and it ended—a couple minutes shy of half of the time limit—with Kasey and Molly Spartan hitting Rosie with a drop toehold/spear combo. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two more interviews took place; the first was Angel Hayze telling Jennifer Louise that she’s proud of being the ICW Women’s champion and confident of defending her title—on the next episode of ICW Fight Club—against Anastasia, and the second was Kez Evans telling LeStrange that “this guy’s on top” unlike Wolfgang and BT Gunn who were competing in the main event later on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-3-leyton-buzzard-defeated-luke-kyro&quot;&gt;Match 3: Leyton Buzzard defeated Luke Kyro&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-03-23/leyton buzzard 2.PNG&quot; alt=&quot;Leyton Buzzard&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My favorite match of the episode mainly because both of those competitors—to me—continue to carry their momentum, and have been since early-to-mid 2021. A pretty good matchup between the two with—near the end—Kyro hitting Buzzard with what looked like a Zigzag to the knee for a two count, and—in the end—Buzzard making Kyro submit to the Scorpion Death Lock. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Backstage, Anastasia told Louise that all women have worked hard and not just Angel Hayze, vowing to prove to be better than Angel by winning the championship on the next episode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-4-ian-skinner--mr-charles-vyce-w-thatcher-wright-defeated-robbie-balfour--ross-hunter&quot;&gt;Match 4: Ian Skinner &amp;amp; Mr. Charles Vyce (w/ Thatcher Wright) defeated Robbie Balfour &amp;amp; Ross Hunter&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Simply a matchup where newcomers were treated like jobbers. Plus, during the match, the two members of Thatcher’s Cabinet mocked the Kinky Party (Jack Jester &amp;amp; Sha Samuels) ever since they lost to the Kinky Party at night #2 of F&amp;amp;L XIII. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Post-match, all three members of Thatcher’s Cabinet ran in and ambushed Balfour and Hunter until the returning Krieger ran in and chased them out! Krieger called the three “Tory bastards”, warning them that he’s back in ICW. I would love to see what he has in store for the roster, including Thatcher’s Cabinet!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-wolfgang-defeated-bt-gunn-for-a-shot-at-the-icw-world-heavyweight-championship&quot;&gt;Main event: Wolfgang defeated BT Gunn for a shot at the ICW World heavyweight championship&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Courtesy of Theo Doros, this match felt like something straight out of Ring of Honor because it had a 20-count for anyone that remained at ringside instead of inside the ring. Gunn brought in a chair and a table during the match, especially while Wolfgang was recovering.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Near the end, Gunn almost flattened referee Thomas Kearns in a corner until he dodged Wolfgang who ended up splashing into the referee. Neither competitor would get a three count after Gunn pinned Wolfgang and vice versa. Gunn then fights Wolfgang out of the ring until all of the sudden, Kez Evans appeared and blindsided Gunn including putting him in the Blood Clot Clutch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Evans then wrapped a chair around Gunn’s neck and stomped it before hiding after seeing Wolfgang recovering at ringside. Wolfgang came back in the ring and speared Gunn through a table in the corner for the win and become the #1 contender for the ICW World heavyweight championship. Surprise ending, but still a pretty damn good battle regardless of Evans sticking his nose in their business, especially Gunn’s. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Afterwards, EMTs and creative/producer Scott Reid came and checked on Gunn while Wolfgang realized that Evans helped him win and was peeved about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;nxt-20-new-years-evil&quot;&gt;NXT 2.0 New Year’s Evil&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-03-23/NXT_NYE_2022.png&quot; alt=&quot;NXT New Year's Evil&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the second year in the row, NXT held New Year’s Evil; it was also the first time “New Year’s Evil” took place under the 2.0 banner. Here’s what happened in Orlando, Florida.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-carmelo-hayes-w-trick-williams-defeated-roderick-strong-w-malcolm-bivens-hachiman-the-creed-brothers-and-ivy-nile-in-a-championship-unification-match&quot;&gt;Match 1: Carmelo Hayes (w/ Trick Williams) defeated Roderick Strong (w/ Malcolm Bivens, Hachiman, the Creed Brothers, and Ivy Nile) in a championship unification match&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hayes is still the NXT North American champion, and the NXT Cruiserweight championship is no more. I kind of expected the Cruiserweight title to be unified with the North American title now that NXT has very few competitors that weigh less than 205 pounds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This match was a pretty damn good opener to me with lots of fast paced action; it was also my favorite matchup of the episode. Highlights included Hayes hitting Strong with a slingshot DDT to the apron until, back in the ring, Strong came back with a Claymore for two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plus, near the end after the two traded Boston crabs (or Stronghold as Strong calls it), Strong went for a superplex until Hayes countered with a swinging neckbreaker on the way down for two. Then, Hayes won the title unification match with a guillotine leg drop. Good to see Hayes on a roll, win streak, title reign and all. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4.25/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After seeing an “Earlier Today” highlight where AJ Styles wished Tommaso Ciampa good luck on his matchup, we saw that the Dusty Rhodes Tag Team Classic will return in two weeks; the women’s DRTTC will return in February. I’m definitely looking forward to those two tournaments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, AJ Styles came into the ring and—after talking about starting his WWE career at the Royal Rumble (in 2016) instead of the NXT brand—praised the NXT Universe for having passion “that makes NXT go around” until Grayson Waller appeared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Waller poked fun of Styles losing to Omos on Raw until Styles challenged him to a match; Waller declined at first—wanting to fight Styles “on Grayson Waller time”—until deciding to fight Styles next week on NXT. Afterwards, both men brawled until Waller escaped from a Phenomenal Forearm attempt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, we get a Pete Dunne promo, challenging Tony D’Angelo to a rematch and telling him to bring his crowbar with him; we would later learn that the rematch—taking place next week—would be a Crowbar On A Pole match, where the crowbar can be used as a weapon by whoever grabs it first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the promo, we see Kacy Catanzaro and Kayden Carter chatting with Amari Miller about winning the NXT Women’s Tag Team championship until Persia Pirotta and Indi Hartwell appeared, wanting to get the tag team championship shot first. A two-on-three handicap match is made at first until Indi showed concern about that idea, leading to Amari, Kacy, and Kayden asking her and Persia to choose a tag team partner. Tiffany Stratton was shown at first until she declined by scoffing at them and walking off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, Wendy Choo—whom we have seen sleeping everywhere on almost every 2.0 episode lately—was spotted; next week, we will see a six-woman tag team match between Indi, Persia, &amp;amp; Wendy and Amari, Kacy, &amp;amp; Kayden.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-msk--riddle-defeated-imperium&quot;&gt;Match 2: MSK &amp;amp; Riddle defeated Imperium&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DJ Tommy Carlucci performed a mashup of MSK and Riddle’s entrance songs during the intro. Also, the last time we have seen Riddle compete on NXT was in May of 2020, when he fought Timothy Thatcher in the inaugural Fight Pit at Full Sail University where then-future WWE/NXT superstars served as an audience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pretty good moments in the six-man tag team match such as MSK and Riddle diving onto Walter, Marcel Barthel, and Fabian Aichner—Wes Lee and Nash Carter doing tope suicidas, and Riddle with a springboard corkscrew crossbody—at ringside. Plus, we all thought that Imperium would steal the win after Walter powerbombed Riddle for two until Riddle and MSK came back; the match ended with Riddle defeating Barthel with the RKO. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Joe Gacy—with Harland—told McKenzie Mitchell that he and Harland will prove next week that they deserve to be in the DRTTC, Mandy Rose came to Orlando in a helicopter ala Charlotte Flair at WrestleMania in 2019. Then, Mitchell interviews Elektra Lopez who doesn’t want to talk about Xyon Quinn because she’s “attracted to success”, and then says that the winner of next week’s match between Quinn and Santos Escobar will walk out with her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-3-mandy-rose-defeated-cora-jade-and-raquel-gonzalez-to-retain-the-nxt-womens-championship&quot;&gt;Match 3: Mandy Rose defeated Cora Jade and Raquel Gonzalez to retain the NXT Women’s championship&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A decent triple threat match with some good moments from Raquel giving Mandy and Cora a double Samoan drop to all three women using a kendo stick as a weapon even during the picture-in-picture break.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plus, we thought that Cora was taken out of the match as soon as Mandy and Raquel went at it until Cora broke up the pin after Raquel hit Mandy with the Chingona bomb. Cora would then fight Raquel out of the ring, and then focus—in a hesitant state unfortunately—on Mandy until Mandy surprised with a pin of her own to retain the title.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe next time Cora can fight for the title again unless someone else like Kay Lee Ray can go after Mandy for the title. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.25/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After seeing Boa—while watching his face—vowing to fight Solo Sikoa by himself and without the power he received after Mei Ying was absorbed into him, we see MSK saying goodbye to Riddle who tells them to fulfill their destinies. As soon as Riddle leaves, MSK plans on going after the NXT Tag Team championship until the Creed Brothers appeared and said that they (Brutus and Julius Creed) will get a shot at the title first because they are entering the DRTTC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, Andre Chase comes into the ring, saying that his matchup with Harland last week was a “teachable moment” because one of his students, the flag waver, saved him from further damage (before being almost thrown off the roof the WWE Performance Center).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chase planned on making the flag waver a recipient for the “Andre Chase University scholarship” until Von Wagner came into the ring, telling the fans—that don’t matter to him because “I’m everything you’re not”—to tune into “The Von Wagner Party.” After some jaw jacking between Wagner and Chase, Wagner attacked him, then got out of the ring and fought not only the flag waver but two fans that were in attendance before being pulled away by security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Afterwards, as Wagner was being escorted out of the building, he told Malcolm Bivens and Ivy Nile—who were checking on Roderick Strong—to “get out of my face.” I got a gut feeling that not only will we see Chase becoming a babyface (which I will be glad to see since the “Chase U” gimmick has been growing on me lately), but also Wagner going after Strong or the Creeds of Diamond Mine; I think Diamond Mine are currently tweeners ever since fighting heels such as Joe Gacy and—this week—Carmelo Hayes lately.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, we had a promo by Cameron Grimes who vowed to take 2022 “to the moon” (or “2022 the moon!” as he said), it was main event time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-bron-breakker-defeated-tommaso-ciampa-to-win-the-nxt-championship&quot;&gt;Main event: Bron Breakker defeated Tommaso Ciampa to win the NXT championship&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Breakker’s entrance including pulling chains that broke apart the black-and-gold NXT logo on the screen, and then kicking a golden X while entering the ring; that didn’t impress Ciampa one bit…or anyone that’s part of, or a fan of, the black-and-gold era. Ciampa was busted open during the matchup, and that was before kneeing Breakker multiple times at ringside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some moments near the end of the match  included Ciampa countering Breakker’s gorilla press powerslam finisher with Willow’s Bell for two, and then taking apart the ring mats to DDT Breakker onto the exposed concrete until Breakker hit Ciampa with an Alabama slam through the announce table.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, Breakker hit his powerslam finisher until Ciampa grabbed the bottom rope to stop the pin count before kneeing the challenger some more and hitting him with the Fairytale Ending for a near fall. Breakker came right back with the Steiner Recliner; Ciampa tapped out, and Breakker became the new champion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ciampa showed respect to Breakker afterwards, nodding in approval to him. I too would nod the two gentlemen in approval as well since it was a good best-of-both-worlds matchup. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;nxt-uk&quot;&gt;NXT UK&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back to the United Kingdom we go, but this time, it’s to the BT Sports Studios in London, England for the first episode of NXT UK of 2022.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-ashton-smith--oliver-carter-defeated-tyson-t-bone--primate-w-eddie-dennis-in-an-nxt-uk-tag-team-championship-contenders-elimination-match&quot;&gt;Match 1: Ashton Smith &amp;amp; Oliver Carter defeated Tyson T-Bone &amp;amp; Primate (w/ Eddie Dennis) in an NXT UK Tag Team championship contenders elimination match&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A good match between two underdog teams. Plus, according to the entrance video, Smith &amp;amp; Carter are the “Hottest Tag Team Under the Sun”; I kind of like that slogan…lol…anyway, Smith &amp;amp; Carter won after hitting Primate with the Ash Carter (Doomsday Device/Ace Crusher combo). &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pretty Deadly was interviewed backstage, upset that Johnny Saint didn’t give them a rematch for the NXT UK Tag Team championship against Moustache Mountain until Sam Gradwell appeared and told both Sam Stoker and Lewis Howley to stop acting like babies after hearing them complain. An Ilja Dragunov promo was then shown, with Ilja—after his wife and son were shown—telling Jordan Devlin not to call his family his “weakness”; Ilja says that his family gives him high emotion, and that he doesn’t need anything like a new car because “I’m real and especially a real champion.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the promo, Noam Dar was watching A-Kid defeat Nathan Frazer three weeks ago to become the #1 contender for the NXT UK Heritage Cup before he and Sha Samuels predicted that he—Dar—would take the Heritage Cup match against A-Kid to the fourth round. Then came another promo, but it’s by Die Familia (Teoman, Rohan Raja, and Charlie Dempsey) this time; they vowed to go after the NXT UK Tag Team championship with a family bond once they go through Jack Starz and “Bomber” Dave Mastiff next week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-xia-brookside-defeated-myla-grace&quot;&gt;Match 2: Xia Brookside defeated Myla Grace&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I admit it…Xia does do a great job as a spoiled brat heel, even when she gets ticked off by fans chanting “Who’s your daddy?” during the match. Long story short, she defeated Myla with Broken Wings in a short bout. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two more promos were shown; the first one had A-Kid vowing to win back the Heritage Cup because it was the beginning of his legacy, and the second one was Jack Starz &amp;amp; Dave Mastiff vowing to make 2022 bigger, with Starz saying that Mastiff will smile—even though Mastiff wasn’t literally smiling…lol—if they win next week and then smile bigger if they win the NXT UK Tag Team championship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the promos, an interview with Amale from earlier this week was shown. Angel Hayze—yes, the same Angel Hayze we know and love from ICW (P.S.: I look forward to seeing what else she has in store on NXT UK besides ICW) — approached Amale and said that her story from weeks ago was inspirational. As Angel left after cheering up Amale, Jinny approached Amale and poked fun of her and her story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, as Jinny left, Stevie Turner pretty much did the same thing to Amale until Amale pinned her against the glass at the entrance and yelled at her in French. Then, Walter had a promo of his own as we learn that Walter will have one more NXT UK match next week (entitled “Walter’s Last Stand”); his opponent will be Nathan Frazer, whom Walter praised for being the “future of the brand” until he learns that “the mat is sacred.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-meiko-satomura-defeated-blair-davenport-to-retain-the-nxt-uk-womens-championship&quot;&gt;Main event: Meiko Satomura defeated Blair Davenport to retain the NXT UK Women’s championship&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-03-23/meiko davenport.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Meiko and Davenport&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was my favorite match of the week. Blair came into this match undefeated. During the match, after Blair took a breather at ringside, Meiko attempted to grab her back into the ring until Blair kicked her in the head before hitting her with a draping DDT to the floor for two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Later on, Meiko went for an STF—the same hold Blair put in her opponent’s protégé Emilia McKenzie weeks ago—until Blair blocked the attempt and put her in a Fujiwara armbar. Meiko came back with back-to-back Death Valley Drivers for two until Blair fought back and hit her with her running knee strike finisher for a near fall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, Meiko went for another Death Valley Driver until Blair got down and rolled her up until Meiko countered with a rollup of her own for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4.25/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the match, Blair blindsided Meiko before hitting her with her knee striker finisher three times, taking the title, and raising it. I got a gut feeling that it’s not over between Meiko and Blair…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;205-live&quot;&gt;205 Live&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Afterwards, it’s back to Orlando for an episode of a show that should change its name because it nowadays has very few cruiserweights…and no cruiserweight title.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps change it to “NXT Evolve” or something like that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-malik-blade-defeated-draco-anthony&quot;&gt;Match 1: Malik Blade defeated Draco Anthony&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-03-23/malik draco.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Malic and Draco&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, Blade was finally able to get his career first win, especially on 205 Live; he defeated Anthony with a springboard dropkick. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-nikkita-lyons-defeated-erica-yan&quot;&gt;Match 2: Nikkita Lyons defeated Erica Yan&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In her second match, Lyons shook off a Charlie horse that she got near the end and was able to defeat Yan with a spinning DDT. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-ikemen-jiro-defeated-ru-feng&quot;&gt;Main event: Ikemen Jiro defeated Ru Feng&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jiro flew solo without Kushida in this main event, even though it’s not the first time that Jiro competed as a singles competitor per se.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plus, the fans loved his watermelon jacket which was the reason why you would hear “Watermelon!” chants prior to the bell being rung. Jiro won with the Ikemen Slash. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;coming-next-week&quot;&gt;Coming next week&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only will I stick with ICW Fight Club, NXT, NXT UK, and 205 Live, but I will also take a look back at two wXw events; one is wXw We Love Wrestling 26, and the other is wXw Anniversary XXI.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope you enjoyed reading my newsletter! Like I said in the intro, you’re welcome to talk about it, as well as have your own opinions about the shows, matches, competitors, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll see you next time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Photos shown in the newsletter are from WWE and ICW.)&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>pro-darin</name></author><category term="articles" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Stinger/Jeff Hardy Debacle</title><link href="/refin-it-up-with-brian-hebner/StingerJeff-Hardy-Debacle/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Stinger/Jeff Hardy Debacle" /><published>2022-03-23T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-03-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/refin-it-up-with-brian-hebner/StingerJeff%20Hardy%20Debacle</id><content type="html" xml:base="/refin-it-up-with-brian-hebner/StingerJeff-Hardy-Debacle/"></content><author><name>refin-it-up-with-brian-hebner</name></author><category term="refin-it-up-with-brian-hebner" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>