<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-05-26T12:19:17+00:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Wrestling With Johners</title><subtitle>Pro Wrestling podcast with news, reviews and debate from WWE, NXT, NXT:UK, AEW, NJPW, Indy Wrestling and so much more. Listen to Wrestling With Johners on Apple Podcasts, Google Podcasts, Spotify, Podbean, Podcast Addict, Castbox, YouTube or wherever you get your podcasts.</subtitle><author><name>John Scott</name></author><entry><title type="html">AEW Double or Nothing Predictions</title><link href="/bob-culture/videos/AEW-Double-or-Nothing-Predictions/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="AEW Double or Nothing Predictions" /><published>2022-05-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-05-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/bob-culture/videos/AEW%20Double%20or%20Nothing%20Predictions</id><content type="html" xml:base="/bob-culture/videos/AEW-Double-or-Nothing-Predictions/"></content><author><name>bob-culture</name></author><category term="bob-culture" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Bucklebomb Live 5/25/22</title><link href="/bucklebomb-entertainment/videos/Bucklebomb-Live-52522/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bucklebomb Live 5/25/22" /><published>2022-05-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-05-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/bucklebomb-entertainment/videos/Bucklebomb%20Live%2052522</id><content type="html" xml:base="/bucklebomb-entertainment/videos/Bucklebomb-Live-52522/"></content><author><name>bucklebomb-entertainment</name></author><category term="bucklebomb-entertainment" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">AEW Dynamite Live Stream May 25th 2022 - Full Show live reaction</title><link href="/da-call-up/videos/AEW-Dynamite-Live-Stream-May-25th-2022-Full-Show-live-reaction/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="AEW Dynamite Live Stream May 25th 2022 - Full Show live reaction" /><published>2022-05-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-05-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/da-call-up/videos/AEW%20Dynamite%20Live%20Stream%20May%2025th%202022%20%20Full%20Show%20live%20reaction</id><content type="html" xml:base="/da-call-up/videos/AEW-Dynamite-Live-Stream-May-25th-2022-Full-Show-live-reaction/"></content><author><name>da-call-up</name></author><category term="da-call-up" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Johnny ELITE on #AEWdynamite #shorts</title><link href="/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/Johnny-ELITE-on-AEWdynamite-shorts/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Johnny ELITE on #AEWdynamite #shorts" /><published>2022-05-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-05-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/Johnny%20ELITE%20on%20AEWdynamite%20shorts</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/Johnny-ELITE-on-AEWdynamite-shorts/"></content><author><name>jofo-in-the-ring</name></author><category term="jofo-in-the-ring" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Wardlow hits MJF with a chair #shorts</title><link href="/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/Wardlow-hits-MJF-with-a-chair-shorts/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Wardlow hits MJF with a chair #shorts" /><published>2022-05-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-05-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/Wardlow%20hits%20MJF%20with%20a%20chair%20shorts</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/Wardlow-hits-MJF-with-a-chair-shorts/"></content><author><name>jofo-in-the-ring</name></author><category term="jofo-in-the-ring" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Wardlow vs 10 security guards #shorts</title><link href="/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/Wardlow-vs-10-security-guards-shorts/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Wardlow vs 10 security guards #shorts" /><published>2022-05-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-05-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/Wardlow%20vs%2010%20security%20guards%20shorts</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/Wardlow-vs-10-security-guards-shorts/"></content><author><name>jofo-in-the-ring</name></author><category term="jofo-in-the-ring" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Issue 20 - Shows of May 14-20, 2022</title><link href="/articles/Issue-20-Shows-of-May-14-20,-2022/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Issue 20 - Shows of May 14-20, 2022" /><published>2022-05-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-05-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/Issue%2020%20Shows%20of%20May%2014-20,%202022</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/Issue-20-Shows-of-May-14-20,-2022/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png&quot; alt=&quot;pro darin&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;20your-move-mr-bond&quot;&gt;20…Your Move Mr. Bond&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yep! It’s my 20th issue of the Pro-Darin newsletter! I hope you readers enjoy it just like you have from issues 1 to 19.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To answer the question “How does it feel to make 20 issues?”, the answer is this…it really feels good. Regardless of how much I’ve gone through such as cramming four or more shows into one issue, making issues lengthy or not really lengthy, and so forth, it still feels good to make that many issues of Pro-Darin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To my readers, thank you. To everyone at Wrestling With Johners including John Scott who has posted my articles from 1 to 20 on the website, thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s go for another 20 or so, shall we?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;icw-barred-ii&quot;&gt;ICW Barred II&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our first stop is Glasgow, Scotland in the United Kingdom; we head to the Garage for an ICW special event known as ICW Barred II. Like Impact Wrestling’s Lockdown, this ICW event had all matches taking place inside a steel cage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-05-26/icw-barred.png&quot; alt=&quot;ICW Barred II&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first time ICW held an event entitled “Barred” was on an episode of ICW Fight Club in the spring of 2021 at the then-empty GPWA in Glasgow; interestingly, that episode was my first taste of ICW prior to checking out past episodes and history of Scotland’s ICW. This year’s “Barred”—that took place on April 24, 2022— was one of ICW’s special events, taking place outside the GPWA and in one of the company’s well-known locations known as the Garage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this event were three title matches, one rematch from Fear &amp;amp; Loathing XIII, a match under hybrid rules courtesy of Rudo, a six-man tag team match that was more of a brawl than a match due to what happened prior to the match taking place, and a main event that reminds me of WarGames even with one ring and one cage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Out of all three title matches that took place at Barred II, my favorite would have to go to the ICW World Heavyweight Championship match between Kez Evans and BT Gunn. The beginning of the match was kind of confusing to me at first mainly because of rules that sounded like two-out-of-three falls rules. The rule was that if Evans or Gunn got the three count first, then one of the two competitors would have the opportunity to win by escaping; Evans got the three count first, and then Gunn got the same pin-first-then-escape opportunity minutes later. Regardless of what rules came into play, as well as Gunn adding extracurricular activities such as bringing in a table as well as storming back into the cage and going after Evans while attempting to leave (I wasn’t sure if Gunn was being hesitant on leaving at times until seeing both the table and his hatred towards Evans come into play), it was still a pretty good match.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, out of all cage matches that took place that night, my favorite would have to go to the Super Smokin’ Thunder Bowl which was like WarGames—as I mentioned moments ago—where a team would win by pinfall, submission or surrender as soon as all eight competitors entered the cage. If you like WarGames-like cage matches including those that we nowadays see near the end of each year in the NXT brand, ICW’s Super Smokin’ Thunder Bowl is definitely one to watch. Both Daz Black’s team—together as “Team ICW”—and the Manifesto gave each other hell even when they used weapons such as a chair, Jack Jester’s “Big Shiny”, a giant corkscrew, and—already in the cage—barbed wire boards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the match results from Glasgow…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-jason-reed-w-coach-trip-defeated-chris-bungard-w-rudo-in-a-match-under-hybrid-rules&quot;&gt;Match #1: Jason Reed (w/ Coach Trip) defeated Chris Bungard (w/ Rudo) in a match under hybrid rules&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The match was divided into five rounds, and the only way to win was by pinfall, submission or escaping the cage. If Bungard won, Reed and Trip would split up. Rudo joined Billy Kirkwood and James R. Kennedy on commentary. Reed survived rounds 1 through 3 after Bungard attempted to make him submit, and Reed was unable to escape as soon as time ran out in round 4. (Each round was three minutes long by the way.) In round 5, Bungard attempted to escape until Trip knocked him off the cage with a chair. Then, Bungard was escaping the cage, and Bungard had him in a sleeper until Reed—incapacitated—fell to the floor and won. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-the-kings-of-the-north-defeated-the-meat-wagon-to-retain-the-icw-tag-team-championship&quot;&gt;Match #2: The Kings of the North defeated the Meat Wagon to retain the ICW Tag Team Championship&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Wee Man watched the match while on commentary. During the match, Bonesaw escaped the cage, and Corvin attempted to do the same thing until Troy Ryan and Anderson Daniels locked him inside. Then, while Bonesaw was preventing Ryan from escaping, Daniels left; both members of each team were left inside the cage afterwards as Bonesaw and Daniels brawled at ringside. Towards the end, Ryan attempted to crawl out with his tag team partner Daniels holding the door open until Bonesaw shoved Daniels, causing the door to slam into Ryan’s face before Corvin picked up the win with a charging forearm (now known as the “Northern Right”). &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-3-ravie-davie-lou-king-sharp--krieger-defeated-thatchers-cabinet&quot;&gt;Match #3: Ravie Davie, Lou King Sharp &amp;amp; Krieger defeated Thatcher’s Cabinet&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If Davie’s team won, he would pick match stipulations for all three members of the Cabinet; if the Cabinet won, Davie’s team would have to join them. Early in the show, Thatcher Wright, Charles Vyce and Ian Skinner attacked Sharp and Krieger in the VIP area before Davie went after the Cabinet. Minutes later after match #2 came to a close, the Cabinet fought Davie to the ringside area before Davie hit them with his delayed springboard moonsault from one of the cage walls. As soon as the Cabinet fought Davie into the ring, the match began. The Cabinet appeared to have Davie outnumbered until Sharp and Krieger came and entered the cage, evening the odds. As soon as Skinner and Vyce were taken down, it was Wright’s turn to be outnumbered as the three took him down before Davie picked up the win with his delayed springboard moonsault (and before all three of Davie’s team pinned all three members of the Cabinet). &lt;strong&gt;My score: 0.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-4-kez-evans-defeated-bt-gunn-to-retain-the-icw-world-heavyweight-championship&quot;&gt;Match #4: Kez Evans defeated BT Gunn to retain the ICW World Heavyweight Championship&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I mentioned before the match results, if Evans and/or Gunn got the three count first, they would then win by escaping the match. In a few minutes, Evans picked up the pinfall win with a handful of tights before he and Gunn fought with a chair. Then, Evans took out brass knuckles until Gunn kneed him before taking the knuckles and punching him down with them before scoring the pinfall win. Gunn would then throw the knuckles out of the ring before hitting Evans with his own Kez Dispenser, and appeared to leave the cage before turning out that he was bringing in a table. Evans fought back and attempted to escape until Gunn put him through the table. As soon as Gunn waved goodbye while leaving, Evans spat at him, leading to Gunn storming back in and fighting him before Evans hit him with a low blow. Evans then grabbed another pair of brass knuckles that was hidden in a turnbuckle pad and hit Gunn with them before leaving the cage and winning. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-5-andy-wild-defeated-big-damo&quot;&gt;Match #5: Andy Wild defeated Big Damo&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After both competitors exchanged Dad Bombs earlier and during the match, Wild would win with a top rope Dad Bomb. Afterwards, Damo read Wild the riot act before the two shook hands and Damo raised the winner’s arm. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-6-molly-spartan-defeated-angel-hayze-to-become-the-new-icw-womens-champion&quot;&gt;Match #6: Molly Spartan defeated Angel Hayze to become the new ICW Women’s Champion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As soon as the match began, Molly hit Angel with a spear for two. Towards the end, Angel put Molly in a sleeper until the two staggered into the referee. Then, as Angel was escaping, Kasey appeared and threw in handcuffs, leading to Molly cuffing Angel to the cage before Molly escaped for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-team-icw-defeated-the-manifesto-in-the-super-smokin-thunder-bowl&quot;&gt;Main event: Team ICW defeated the Manifesto in the Super Smokin’ Thunder Bowl&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As soon as all eight members were in the ring, the only way to win was by pinfall, submission or surrender; escaping the cage meant forfeiting. The Manifesto had the advantage. Dylan Thorn and Daz Black started off the match, then five minutes later, Eddie Castle entered; there were two-minute intervals for each Team ICW and Manifesto entrant afterwards. Leyton Buzzard would enter next, followed by Grant McIvor, Luke Kyro, Alexander Darwin MacAllan (equipped with a steel chair) and Jack Jester (equipped with “Big Shiny”). Jester also attempted to stab ADM—who used his chair as a shield—with a large corkscrew until the rest of the Manifesto ambushed him before ADM threw “Big Shiny” and the corkscrew out of the cage. Both teams would then use two of the three barbed wire boards that were hanging on the cage; Jester stopped himself from being whipped into a board in the corner, then sent a charging ADM into the board before he and the rest of Team ICW stomped the board that was stuck to ADM. Afterwards, ADM was freed from the board before he hit Jester with a chokeslam onto the board; he and the rest of the Manifesto would then hit place another board on top of the trapped Jester, and Thorn sandwiched the boards onto Jester with a Coup de Grace (ala Finn Bálor). As soon as Team ICW fought back, Kyro hit Black with the Kyroscope, Buzzard hit Black with the X Marks the Spot, and Black hit Thorn with the Seth Rollins curb stomp onto ADM’s chair for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4.25/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;wxw-we-love-wrestling-28&quot;&gt;wXw We Love Wrestling 28&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We stay in the continent of Europe, but this time, we return to Oberhausen, Germany for the 28th episode of wXw We Love Wrestling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-05-26/wxw-we-love-wrestling-28.png&quot; alt=&quot;wXw We Love Wrestling 28&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This episode—that took place on March 6, 2022—occurred hours before night #3 of the 16 Carat Gold tournament began. Not only did the first and second rounds of the tournament occur in nights #1 and #2 of the tournament, but there were title changes that took place during night #2. Those title changes were:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Absolute Andy vacated the wXw Shotgun Championship due to illness, leading to Ninja Mack and Ace Romero fighting for the title; Mack would win the match and become the new wXw Shotgun Champion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fast Time Moodo &amp;amp; Stephanie Maze defeated the Arrows of Hungary to become the new wXw Tag Team Champions; prior to that, Bobby Gunns &amp;amp; Michael Knight won a tag team gauntlet to become #1 contenders for the titles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ava Everett defeated Iva Kolasky to become the new wXw Women’s Champion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tristan Archer defeated Axel Tischer, Jurn Simmons and Levaniel in a fatal four-way match to become the new wXw Unified World Wrestling Champion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There were eight matches in this episode of We Love Wrestling; half of the matches weren’t as good due to a short amount of time or weren’t as exciting as the rest, while the other half of matches were indeed good. The last two matches—that were title matches—were what I liked, with the wXw Unified World Wrestling Championship match between Tristan Archer and Fuminori Abe being the best of the last two. It’s often rare to see a heel like Archer save his dastardly tactics for before or after a match as well as come up with a clean pin, but on the other hand, it did show Archer being a fighting champion after refusing to fight Abe at first as soon as the episode began (and before Francis Kaspin made it official). The next to last match of the episode, which was for the wXw Tag Team Championship between Moodo &amp;amp; Stephanie and Knight &amp;amp; Gunns was good as well even though the end of the match was marred by injury.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the match results from Oberhausen…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-levaniel--jurn-simmons-defeated-the-gulyás-brothers&quot;&gt;Match #1: Levaniel &amp;amp; Jurn Simmons defeated the Gulyás Brothers&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I believe that Dave Bradshaw said that this was Vilmos Gulyás’ wXw debut. The team of Levaniel and Simmons worked together hours after fighting for what would become Tristan Archer’s belt, and were able to pick up the win after Simmons hit Vilmos with a press slam, a standing moonsault, and a piledriver. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-ava-everett-defeated-orsi-in-a-non-title-match-with-the-tunnel-vision&quot;&gt;Match #2: Ava Everett defeated Orsi in a non-title match with the Tunnel Vision&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My score: 1.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-3-maggot-baby-allison--vincent-heisenberg-defeated-oskar-feyyaz-aguila--the-rotation&quot;&gt;Match #3: Maggot, Baby Allison &amp;amp; Vincent Heisenberg defeated Oskar, Feyyaz Aguila &amp;amp; the Rotation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oskar came to the ring with the wXw Academy Trophy because he defeated Goldenboy Santos for the trophy at wXwNOW &amp;amp; Friends Showcase that occurred somewhere during the day of night #2 of 16 Carat Gold. Also, Robert Dreissker—earlier in the day—was ticked off about this match taking place because the wXw Wrestling Academy members, including the injured Anil Marik, didn’t give him the okay to have this match take place. Near the end, Maggot hit Aguila with an enzuigiri, then Allison hit him with a suplex before turning it into a front chancery; with Maggot assisting Allison with the hold, Aguila tapped out. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-4-ninja-mack-defeated-tamás-szabó-to-retain-the-wxw-shotgun-championship&quot;&gt;Match #4: Ninja Mack defeated Tamás Szabó to retain the wXw Shotgun Championship&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was Szabó’s wXw debut. Towards the end, Mack blocked Szabó’s frog splash, and then won with the Ninja 630. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 0.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-5-nikita-charisma-dennis-cah-dullnig-sebastian-suave--laurance-roman-defeated-michael-schenkenberg-psycho-mike-vaughn-vertigo--norman-harras&quot;&gt;Match #5: Nikita Charisma, Dennis “Ca$h” Dullnig, Sebastian Suave &amp;amp; Laurance Roman defeated Michael Schenkenberg, Psycho Mike, Vaughn Vertigo &amp;amp; Norman Harras&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;…in a wildcard eight-man tag match; the participants for both teams were chosen via lottery. Also, Charisma refused to fight Schenkenberg in this match after appearing at the entryway ringing a bell and protesting as if he were either a town crier or a village idiot. During the match, Mike stared at the venue’s hard camera while wrestling his opponents before Harras blind tagged in and coerced him to get back on the apron; Schenkenberg did the same thing after Mike was getting ready to fight again. Also, Rott und Flott refused to fight each other and sat in the middle of the ring, leading to ring announcer Frank Fehrmann announcing fines—from 20 euros to 80 euros—before they ended up having no choice but to fight. Near the end, Rott und Flott encouraged Mike to punch down Suave, and then went after Mike until Dullnig—who blind tagged in—rolled up Schenkenberg and pinned him for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-6-iva-kolasky-defeated-gaya-glass&quot;&gt;Match #6: Iva Kolasky defeated Gaya Glass&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Iva was frustrated over losing the wXw Women’s Championship to Ava Everett, and would end up taking her frustrations out on Gaya; Iva would then win with a cartwheel leg drop. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 0.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-7-stephanie-maze--fast-time-moodo-defeated-michael-knight--bobby-gunns&quot;&gt;Match #7: Stephanie Maze &amp;amp; Fast Time Moodo defeated Michael Knight &amp;amp; Bobby Gunns&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;…due to referee stoppage to retain the wXw Tag Team Championship. Near the end, Stephanie and Moodo hit Knight with a superkick/Pedigree combo, then Stephanie pinned Knight until Gunns broke up the pin before the referee realized that Knight was injured; the referee would stop the match afterwards as Stephanie, Moodo and Gunns checked to see if Knight was okay. As soon as Knight recovered, all four competitors—as well as the EMTs and referee—received a standing ovation. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-tristan-archer-defeated-fuminori-abe-to-retain-the-wxw-unified-world-wrestling-championship-with-the-coup-détat&quot;&gt;Main event: Tristan Archer defeated Fuminori Abe to retain the wXw Unified World Wrestling Championship with the Coup d’État&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Post-match, Archer refused to shake Abe’s hand, then told fans to get used to seeing his face everyday because “nothing can stop the French Revolution”, and that the only thing that matters is “liberté, égalité, décapité.” &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;nxt&quot;&gt;NXT&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We now head to Orlando, Florida in the United States—as well as the month of May 2022—for an episode of NXT.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We learned that In Your House is returning to NXT this year; it will take place on June 4, the night before Hell In A Cell. Matches made for this event—for now—are Cameron Grimes defending the NXT North American Championship against Carmelo Hayes, the Creed Brothers fighting Pretty Deadly for the NXT Tag Team Championship, and a rematch for the NXT Championship between Bron Breakker and Joe Gacy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The North American title match was made after Hayes noted that—two weeks ago—Grimes pinned Solo Sikoa instead of him in their triple threat match to retain the title at NXT Spring Breakin’. Grimes accepted the challenge at In Your House, and then told Sikoa—who asked for another shot at the title—“you got next.” I predict that Grimes will retain the title, and—since Sikoa appears to be getting a big push—Sikoa wins it days or so later; I say this because Sikoa has come really close to winning gold on NXT, whether it’s on a regular episode, a special episode, or even a premium live event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The NXT Championship rematch was also made for In Your House. After Joe Gacy and his hooded colleagues beat down and kidnapped Breakker out of the arena and got rid of him elsewhere, Gacy asked Breakker to join him so they could change the world together. Breakker—this week—announced that he refused to team with Gacy, before demanding what Gacy wanted from him. Gacy wanted another shot at the title, and then added a stipulation while poking fun of Breakker’s anger issues; if Breakker got himself disqualified, Gacy would win the title. This rivalry between Gacy and Breakker is definitely heating up, even with Gacy becoming an even more sinister version of his peacemaker-like heel character as well as adding hooded followers for him to the mix.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also heating up is a heel vs. heel rivalry between Tony D’Angelo and Santos Escobar, even though it looks like D’Angelo and his colleagues Stacks &amp;amp; Two Dimes (Channing Lorenzo &amp;amp; Troy Donovan respectively to be more specific) have become tweeners as of late with the dead giveaway being D’Angelo fighting Von Wagner not too long ago. The long awaited—in my point of view—match between D’Angelo and Escobar took place as this week’s main event, and I wasn’t sure what to except even with heelish tactics coming into play especially near the end of that bout. In the end, courtesy of what happened between Stacks &amp;amp; Two Dimes and Joaquin Wilde &amp;amp; Cruz del Toro, Escobar emerged victorious after sneaking in a weapon of his own—while D’Angelo looked for his crowbar—in the form of brass knuckles. I don’t think this rivalry between D’Angelo and Escobar is done by a long shot, even after seeing that main event; it is a pretty good heel vs. heel rivalry however.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-05-26/creed-viking.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Creed Brothers vs. Viking Raiders&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My favorite match of the night would go to the rematch between the Creed Brothers and SmackDown’s Viking Raiders. Unless you only count the Viking Raiders’ time on NXT—before the brand converted from black-and-gold to multicolored—as “War Raiders”, Erik and Ivar picked up their first NXT loss a couple weeks ago courtesy of Roderick Strong (who made the Creed Bros. vs. Pretty Deadly for IYH by the way) who sneaked in a running knee, leading to Brutus and Julius picking up the win as well as getting disgusted over how they won afterwards. The rematch took place this week, but this time, Strong—who was at ringside this time instead of coming from the crowd—and Damon Kemp were at ringside to manage the Creed Brothers. In the end, the Viking Raiders would emerge victorious after Brutus and Julius refused to pick up another tainted victory. Aside from enjoying this match, I can’t say that I can blame the Creed Brothers—storyline wise—for refusing to get back-to-back Strong-assisted wins. Not only that, but because of Strong becoming the new leader after Malcolm Bivens was released from WWE, there are more cracks forming in Diamond Mine’s teamwork; not even the new acquisition in the form of Kemp has helped it yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the NXT match results from Orlando…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-solo-sikoa--cameron-grimes-defeated-carmelo-hayes--trick-williams&quot;&gt;Match #1: Solo Sikoa &amp;amp; Cameron Grimes defeated Carmelo Hayes &amp;amp; Trick Williams&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hayes and Williams mocked Sikoa and Grimes before the match, saying that Sikoa “got last” and that Hayes would win back the NXT North American Championship. Near the end, Grimes attempted to hit Hayes with the Cave In until Sikoa blind tagged in. Then, as soon as Williams ran in, Grimes hit Williams with the Cave In while Sikoa—who took down Hayes before the interference—won with a top rope splash. Afterwards, Sikoa took the title from the referee that was handing it to Grimes before Sikoa handed it to the champion. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-lash-legend-defeated-tatum-paxley&quot;&gt;Match #2: Lash Legend defeated Tatum Paxley&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;…in almost four minutes in round 1 of the NXT Women’s Breakout Tournament after hitting her with a bicycle kick. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-3-the-viking-raiders-defeated-the-creed-brothers-w-roderick-strong-and-damon-kemp&quot;&gt;Match #3: The Viking Raiders defeated the Creed Brothers (w/ Roderick Strong and Damon Kemp)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Near the end, while Kemp distracted the referee, Strong attempted to interfere until Brutus and Julius stopped him from doing so. This led to Erik and Ivar winning after hitting Julius with a double chokeslam. After the match, the Creed Brothers argued with Strong in the ring and again backstage; then, as soon as Julius and Brutus left with Kemp trying to calm them down, Pretty Deadly poked fun of Diamond Mine including Strong and his leadership skills until Strong challenged the two to a tag team match against him and Kemp for next week. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4.25/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-4-grayson-waller-defeated-andre-chase-w-bodhi-hayward-in-four-minutes&quot;&gt;Match #4: Grayson Waller defeated Andre Chase (w/ Bodhi Hayward) in four minutes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sarray was in the audience with Chase U students. Towards the end, Chase accidentally threw Waller out of the ring and onto Hayward. Then, Chase checked Hayward afterwards before Waller picked up the ring with a through-the-ropes cutter. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-5-roxanne-perez-defeated-kiana-james&quot;&gt;Match #5: Roxanne Perez defeated Kiana James&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;…in round 1 of the NXT Women’s Breakout Tournament with a Code Red. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-6-nathan-frazer-defeated-wes-lee-by-disqualification-in-four-minutes-due-to-interference-by-von-wagner-with-mr-stone-in-tow&quot;&gt;Match #6: Nathan Frazer defeated Wes Lee by disqualification in four minutes due to interference by Von Wagner (with Mr. Stone in tow)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Frazer saw Sofia Cromwell in the hallway while heading to the ring prior to the ambush. Post-match, Lee went after Wagner until Wagner fought back and then—after spotting Sofia in the crowd—threw Lee out of the ring and to the announce table. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-santos-escobar-defeated-tony-dangelo&quot;&gt;Main event: Santos Escobar defeated Tony D’Angelo&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stacks &amp;amp; Two Dimes and Joaquin Wilde, Cruz del Toro &amp;amp; Elektra Lopez were barred from ringside. Near the end, D’Angelo looked for his crowbar while the referee wasn’t looking until he noticed that Wilde and Cruz—who appeared at the entryway—had the crowbar. Then, Stacks &amp;amp; Two Dimes appeared and fought Wilde &amp;amp; Cruz while—also behind the referee’s back—Escobar pulled out brass knuckles, hit D’Angelo with them, and pinned him for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;nxt-uk&quot;&gt;NXT UK&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, we return to the United Kingdom, but this time, we head to the BT Sports Studios in London, England for an episode of NXT UK.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though Ivy Nile, Von Wagner, Damon Kemp, and Lash Legend were in attendance, none of the NXT wrestlers were in action this week. They do however have matches made for future episodes of NXT UK.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One is Sam Gradwell taking on Von Wagner after seeing Wagner bully Johnny Saint’s assistant Sid Scala backstage not too long ago. Both Gradwell and Wagner would encounter each other again after the “Thunderstorm” heard Wagner badmouth the NXT UK roster over not being bigger or stronger than him, leading to the two brawling until referees separated the two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, as predicted even in the form of the well-known catchphrase “saw that coming”, Lash Legend will fight Emilia McKenzie next week. Lash, a couple weeks ago, made Emilia take her belongings to her locker room which then led to this match made between the two; the two would encounter each other again after Emilia took offense after hearing Lash says that Emilia only carries Meiko Satomura’s bags, leading to the two brawling until—another “saw that coming” moment (no pun intended)—referees separated the two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Damon Kemp also has a future NXT UK match taking place as he’ll take on Sha Samuels. This match was made after Kemp poked fun on Samuels making odds for matches and would then be attacked by Kemp who picked up his first NXT UK win afterwards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lastly, Ivy Nile has another NXT UK match in the future; this week, she walked into Meiko Satomura’s locker room and challenged her to a match for the NXT UK Women’s Championship, leading to Meiko saying “Okay” and Ivy saying “Thank you.” This is no lie…I would love to see both Ivy and Meiko clash, especially for the NXT UK Women’s Championship. If this match isn’t on your list of NXT UK matches that’s circled, you may as well circle it; not only will Meiko’s title be on the line, but so will Ivy’s undefeated streak.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-05-26/dennis-boar.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Eddie Dennis vs. Wild Boar&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Future matches aside, this week’s matches were okay, but only one match was fairly better than the rest in my opinion, and it was the main event which was a dog collar match between Eddie Dennis and Wild Boar. It definitely showed Wild Boar having enough of Dennis’ shenanigans with and without the rest of Symbiosis ever since Dennis threw him away like chewed up gum leading to his former team—the Hunt—breaking up. In the end, even with Primate trying to outnumber his former tag team partner, Wild Boar would come out on top.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the match results from London…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-xia-brookside--eliza-alexander-defeated-amale--angel-hayze&quot;&gt;Match #1: Xia Brookside &amp;amp; Eliza Alexander defeated Amale &amp;amp; Angel Hayze&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Near the end, while Xia distracted the referee after knocking Amale off the apron, Eliza kneed Angel from the apron before Xia picked up the win after hitting Angel with Broken Wings. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-rohan-raja--teoman-w-charlie-dempsey-defeated-dave-mastiff--jack-starz&quot;&gt;Match #2: Rohan Raja &amp;amp; Teoman (w/ Charlie Dempsey) defeated Dave Mastiff &amp;amp; Jack Starz&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;…for a spot in the triple threat tag match for the NXT UK Tag Team Championship. Towards the end, Starz attempted to hit Teoman with a powerbomb until he saw Dempsey whip his vest—given to him by Mastiff—on the ground several times; Starz attacked Dempsey until Raja shoved him into the post, leading to Teoman picking up the win with a flipping stunner. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-3-kenny-williams-defeated-josh-morrell&quot;&gt;Match #3: Kenny Williams defeated Josh Morrell&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Williams was distracted by two masked men in the crowd before defeating Morrell with Bad Luck (snapmare driver). Afterwards, Tiger Turan appeared at the entryway, surprising Williams. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 0.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-wild-boar-defeated-eddie-dennis-in-a-dog-collar-match&quot;&gt;Main event: Wild Boar defeated Eddie Dennis in a dog collar match&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wild Boar, who was wearing the collar, attacked Dennis to the ring before Dennis wore the collar. Towards the end, Primate appeared and Wild Boar knocked him off the apron, then took down Dennis until Primate came back in and broke up Wild Boar’s pin, leading to Dennis pinning Wild Boar for two. Then, Wild Boar fought Primate out of the ring before putting Dennis in an arm trapped crossface; Dennis tried to fight out of it until Wild Boar added the chain to the crossface, leading to Dennis tapping out. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;nxt-lvl-up&quot;&gt;NXT: LVL UP&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, we return to Orlando for an episode of NXT: LVL UP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-05-26/nile-yulisa.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ivy Nile vs. Yulisa Leon&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Out of the three matches that took place, the match between Ivy Nile and Yulisa Leon—a rematch from a November 2021 episode of the now defunct 205 Live—was my favorite. This win definitely helps build Ivy’s undefeated streak, even against an opponent that she wrestled in the past.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the NXT: LVL UP match results from Orlando…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-javier-bernal-defeated-bryson-montana-in-four-minutes&quot;&gt;Match #1: Javier Bernal defeated Bryson Montana in four minutes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Montana was part of the Ivy Nile Challenge segment that was aired during last week’s episode of NXT. Bernal picked up his career first win after hitting Montana with a Codebreaker. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-ivy-nile-defeated-yulisa-leon-w-valentina-feroz&quot;&gt;Match #2: Ivy Nile defeated Yulisa Leon (w/ Valentina Feroz)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;…after turning Yulisa’s pin attempt into the standing dragon sleeper, making Yulisa submit. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-josh-briggs-w-brooks-jensen-defeated-quincy-elliott&quot;&gt;Main event: Josh Briggs (w/ Brooks Jensen) defeated Quincy Elliott&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“#FindBrooksAGirl” was written on Jensen’s cast. Briggs won after hitting Elliott with a Clothesline From Hell (ala JBL). &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;next-time&quot;&gt;Next time…&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only does ICW Fight Club return to rejoin the rest of my usual “NXT” shows, but there is also the 29th episode of wXw We Love Wrestling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For my newsletters as well as any articles that are on the Wrestling With Johners website, the website is &lt;a href=&quot;https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/articles&quot;&gt;https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/articles&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For just my newsletters along on the WWJ website, it is &lt;a href=&quot;https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/pro-darin/&quot;&gt;https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/pro-darin/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading! Feel free to comment! I’ll see you next time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Photos shown in the newsletter are from WWE, ICW and wXw.)&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>pro-darin</name></author><category term="articles" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep 251, Jim Phillips</title><link href="/the-everett-lee-show/Ep-251-Jim-Phillips/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep 251, Jim Phillips" /><published>2022-05-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-05-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/the-everett-lee-show/Ep%20251%20Jim%20Phillips</id><content type="html" xml:base="/the-everett-lee-show/Ep-251-Jim-Phillips/"></content><author><name>the-everett-lee-show</name></author><category term="the-everett-lee-show" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Flashback Interview with Impact Wrestling’s Josh Mathews</title><link href="/alliance-pro-wrestling-network/videos/Flashback-Interview-with-Impact-Wrestlings-Josh-Mathews/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Flashback Interview with Impact Wrestling’s Josh Mathews" /><published>2022-05-25T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-05-25T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/alliance-pro-wrestling-network/videos/Flashback%20Interview%20with%20Impact%20Wrestlings%20Josh%20Mathews</id><content type="html" xml:base="/alliance-pro-wrestling-network/videos/Flashback-Interview-with-Impact-Wrestlings-Josh-Mathews/"></content><author><name>lewis-carlan</name></author><category term="alliance-pro-wrestling-network" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Death Match Russell PodCast Live With Pro Wrestler &amp;amp; Painter Dave Cole Aka Davey Painting</title><link href="/death-match-russell/videos/Death-Match-Russell-PodCast-Live-With-Pro-Wrestler-Painter-Dave-Cole-Aka-Davey-Painting/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Death Match Russell PodCast Live With Pro Wrestler &amp;amp; Painter Dave Cole Aka Davey Painting" /><published>2022-05-25T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-05-25T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/death-match-russell/videos/Death%20Match%20Russell%20PodCast%20Live%20With%20Pro%20Wrestler%20%20Painter%20Dave%20Cole%20Aka%20Davey%20Painting</id><content type="html" xml:base="/death-match-russell/videos/Death-Match-Russell-PodCast-Live-With-Pro-Wrestler-Painter-Dave-Cole-Aka-Davey-Painting/"></content><author><name>death-match-russell</name></author><category term="death-match-russell" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>