<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-09-12T17:30:44+00:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Wrestling With Johners</title><subtitle>Pro Wrestling podcast with news, reviews and debate from WWE, NXT, NXT:UK, AEW, NJPW, Indy Wrestling and so much more. Listen to Wrestling With Johners on Apple Podcasts, Google Podcasts, Spotify, Podbean, Podcast Addict, Castbox, YouTube or wherever you get your podcasts.</subtitle><author><name>John Scott</name></author><entry><title type="html">WWE2K22 Monday Night Raw</title><link href="/da-call-up/videos/WWE2K22-Monday-Night-Raw/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="WWE2K22 Monday Night Raw" /><published>2022-09-12T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-09-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/da-call-up/videos/WWE2K22%20Monday%20%20Night%20Raw</id><content type="html" xml:base="/da-call-up/videos/WWE2K22-Monday-Night-Raw/"></content><author><name>da-call-up</name></author><category term="da-call-up" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Who’s beating the Usos #shorts #wweraw</title><link href="/da-call-up/videos/Whos-beating-the-Usos-shorts-wweraw/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Who’s beating the Usos #shorts #wweraw" /><published>2022-09-12T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-09-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/da-call-up/videos/Whos%20beating%20the%20Usos%20shorts%20wweraw</id><content type="html" xml:base="/da-call-up/videos/Whos-beating-the-Usos-shorts-wweraw/"></content><author><name>da-call-up</name></author><category term="da-call-up" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Best Sharpshooter in 2022</title><link href="/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/Best-Sharpshooter-in-2022/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Best Sharpshooter in 2022" /><published>2022-09-12T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-09-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/Best%20Sharpshooter%20in%202022</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/Best-Sharpshooter-in-2022/"></content><author><name>jofo-in-the-ring</name></author><category term="jofo-in-the-ring" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Issue 31 Shows of August 7-13, 2022</title><link href="/articles/Issue-32-Shows-of-August-7-13,-2022/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Issue 31 Shows of August 7-13, 2022" /><published>2022-09-12T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-09-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/Issue%2032%20Shows%20of%20August%207-13,%202022</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/Issue-32-Shows-of-August-7-13,-2022/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png&quot; alt=&quot;pro darin&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;double-dose&quot;&gt;Double Dose&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Keeping this intro short and sweet, let’s start with a double dose of belated wXw recaps, shall we?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;wxw-broken-rules-xx&quot;&gt;wXw Broken Rules XX&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those of you that are new to wXw, Broken Rules is a special event that’s kind of like WWE’s Extreme Rules, where most of the matches are under hardcore wrestling rules or where there are no count outs or disqualifications whatsoever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-09-12/broken-rules.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;xWx Broken Rules XX&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This event took place at the Turbinenhalle in Oberhausen, Germany on June 11, 2022. Three of the seven matches that took place were under hardcore wrestling rules, which were—in order—a six-pack challenge, a last man standing match, and a tables elimination match. Other matches that took place included a mixed tag team match, a “first time ever” match, and a rematch from the final round of the 2022 16 Carat Gold tournament.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was definitely a good event, with matches ranging from average to very good. My favorite match that had the rulebook put aside would have to go to the last man standing match between Vincent Heisenberg and Jurn Simmons. It was definitely a hard-hitting battle between the two competitors not only in the ring but outside the ring as well, and it showed what both Heisenberg and Simmons are capable of both storyline wise and competition wise. In the end, we saw Heisenberg get taken down a peg—ever since he had a streak of count out victories—courtesy of Simmons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for the other matches that were of course traditional pro wrestling matches, my favorite of Broken Rules XX would have to go to the first-time bout between Cara Noir and Axel Tischer. I still stick to what I have said earlier this year that not a single Cara Noir one-on-one match has disappointed me; this match didn’t disappoint me either. Even though it also showcased Tischer trying to get back on track after losing to Tristan Archer in back-to-back wXw Unified World Wrestling Championship matches, both he and Cara Noir had an excellent back-and-forth showing from start to finish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the Broken Rules results from Oberhausen…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-orsi-defeated-the-rotation-hektor-invictus-peter-tihanyi-masha-slamovich-and-the-royal-hunter-aigle-blanc&quot;&gt;Match #1: Orsi defeated the Rotation, Hektor Invictus, Peter Tihanyi, Masha Slamovich and “The Royal Hunter” Aigle Blanc&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;…in a Surprise Benefit Scramble; it was in the form of a six-pack challenge, and the winner of this match would get a prize. Also, this was the wXw debut of Impact wrestler Masha. This match ended with Orsi hitting the Rotation with a Jackhammer. Afterwards, Orsi’s prize was announced; she will be a participant in wXw Femme Fatales on October 1. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-der-prinz-der-sterne-levaniel-defeated-psycho-mike&quot;&gt;Match #2: “Der Prinz der Sterne” Levaniel defeated Psycho Mike&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before the match started, an excited Mike came out with a microphone claimed to see a bodyslam while looking past the moon and stars, and then asked the fans “Who wants to see a bodyslam?” Then, Levaniel came into the ring and angrily said that it was his mic and not Mike’s; Mike pouted and Levaniel apologized to Mike who said that he wanted to make people like him, and then said that he wanted to give Levaniel a bodyslam which led to Levaniel telling him to “chill out” before the bell rang. Mike watched the hard camera during the match while fighting Levaniel. There was also a Three Stooges moment that occurred where Mike kept sitting up while Levaniel attempted to hit him with an elbow drop; in the last attempt, Levaniel missed the target who of course sat up. Mike made the fans feel fulfilled by hitting Levaniel with three bodyslams for a two count, and then went for the fourth bodyslam until Levaniel countered with the Galactic Facecrusher for the win. Afterwards, Levaniel helped up Mike who wanted to perform another bodyslam and ended up getting a hug instead. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.25/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-3-cara-noir-defeated-axel-axeman-tischer&quot;&gt;Match #3: Cara Noir defeated Axel “Axeman” Tischer&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As noted above, it was the first time that both the Black Swan and the Axeman competed. The match ended with Cara Noir making Tischer submit to a sleeper/bodyscissors combo (or “Black Swan” according to Dave Bradshaw on commentary). &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-4-sebastian-suave--iva-kolasky-defeated-maggot--baby-allison&quot;&gt;Match #4: Sebastian Suave &amp;amp; Iva Kolasky defeated Maggot &amp;amp; Baby Allison&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Towards the end, Maggot hit Suave with a spear and the Crucifixion crucifix driver for a near fall, and then he and Allison hit Suave with a double spear. Then, Allison—with help from Maggot—put Suave in an assisted front chancery until Iva crotched Maggot while the referee wasn’t looking; this led to Suave hitting Allison with an emerald frosion for the win. After the match, Andy Jackson interviewed Suave and Iva, and Suave said that he proved to be the “most dangerous wrestler” and praised Iva for being strong, smart and fast; Norman Harras appeared and granted Suave and Iva matches for the wXw Shotgun Championship and the wXw Women’s Championship respectively. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-5-jurn-simmons-defeated-vincent-heisenberg-in-a-last-man-standing-match&quot;&gt;Match #5: Jurn Simmons defeated Vincent Heisenberg in a Last Man Standing match&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Heisenberg came into the ring with a chair. Less than a minute into the match, Simmons surprised his opponent by hitting him with a press slam followed by a moonsault. A handful of chairs were broken in this match as both wrestlers fought in and outside the ring as well as into the crowd and at the entryway where Heisenberg hit Simmons with a backdrop and powerslam on the stage. As soon as both came back into the ring, Simmons hit Heisenberg with a spear and piledriver until his opponent got up at nine, then attempted to use a chair until Heisenberg fought back and hit him with a Rikishi driver onto the chair for nine. Then, when both wrestlers fought outside the ring again, Simmons tied his opponent’s hands together at a ring post with zip ties—that he found in a toolbox—before hitting him several times with a chair. Simmons would then cut the zip ties to bring Heisenberg back into the ring and hit him with a piledriver onto two chairs; Heisenberg didn’t get up at ten, and Simmons won. Simmons sat next to the unconscious Heisenberg afterwards. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-6-peacock-main-event-rott-und-flott-defeated-only-friends-in-a-tables-elimination-match-to-retain-the-wxw-tag-team-championship&quot;&gt;Match #6 (Peacock main event): Rott und Flott defeated Only Friends in a Tables Elimination match to retain the wXw Tag Team Championship&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bobby Gunns and Michael Knight were equipped with a table and set it up on the stage at the entryway until the championships took the table and put it under the ring before fighting seconds before the bell rang. Michael Knight was the first to be eliminated after he dove at the champions until Nikita Charisma and Michael Schenkenberg threw the table at him; it caused Knight to crash through the table on the way down. Then, Rott und Flott set up another table until Gunns eliminated Charisma with a fisherman’s suplex through the table. With Gunns and Schenkenberg left in the match, Gunns went for a superplex until the eliminated Charisma grabbed Schenkenberg’s leg to stop the attempt before Schenkenberg hit Gunns with a powerbomb through a table for the win. Post-match, EMTs checked on Gunns who had a gash on his leg; they bandaged it up and, Gunns had trouble attempting to walk to the batch, stretchered him out of the arena. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-jonathan-gresham-defeated-robert-dreissker-by-disqualification&quot;&gt;Main event: Jonathan Gresham defeated Robert Dreissker by disqualification&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Near the end, Dreissker punched Gresham into the referee, then hit him with a fallaway slam and the Dreissker Bomb for a delayed near fall. Dreissker then attempted to leave until he was blocked by other wrestlers including Peter Tihanyi, the Rotation, Danny Fray, Elijah Blum, Orsi, Aigle Blanc, the Arrows of Hungary and Laurance Roman from both sides of the ring. All of the sudden, the Arrows of Hungary and Roman teamed up with Dreissker to attack Gresham, giving Gresham the DQ win. Everyone else that blocked Dreissker’s exit attempted to stop him and his team, but were overpowered by the four who then stood tall afterwards. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;wxw-we-love-wrestling-33&quot;&gt;wXw We Love Wrestling 33&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Staying in the same venue as Broken Rules XX, this episode of wXw We Love Wrestling took place the day after that event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-09-12/we-love-wrestling.png&quot; alt=&quot;xWx We Love Wrestling 33&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new faction of Robert Dreissker, Arrows of Hungary and Laurance Roman are collectively known as Amboss (German for “Anvil”); to me, this group reminds me of the short-lived team Retribution which was led by Mustafa Ali with the exception that it involved a corrupt coach and didn’t involve invasions in the ring, backstage area or ringside. Dreissker said that he felt good about leading a team that hates despair in wXw before praising Icarus and Dover as the best tag team in the world, Roman no longer being underrated and underappreciated, and berating fans for only recognizing him by a simple name such as “Avalanche”; Arrows of Hungary said that wXw is no longer a working environment after seeing kindness, brotherhood and empathy backstage as well as seeing wrestlers—like fans—getting attention on social media instead of being “real” wrestlers, and Roman said that he’s no longer being a “warmup” competitor before vowing to rebuild wXw with the rest of Amboss. I’m curious to see what Amboss has in store besides, storyline wise, looking to make wXw even better by having the rest of the wrestlers—including those Dreissker trained in the past—be like this new team; to me, they appear to be “serious business” heels as we have seen on this episode of We Love Wrestling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Six matches took place on the episode, including two that involved members of the new team Amboss; half of the matches I disliked because they were either short lived or had me asking for more action from the participants, and the other half were—in my opinion—good back and forth bouts. Out of the six matches that took place, my favorite would have to go to the second match of the episode which was between Peter Tihanyi and Axel Tischer. Tihanyi is still proving to be a rising star on wXw even after seeing him compete against top and mid-card names on the roster, including those carrying gold such as Maggot, as we have seen on past episodes of We Love Wrestling as well as select special events. This match also showed what Tischer could do to make his losing streak—that started off with back-to-back losses to Tristan Archer for the wXw Unified World Wrestling Championship—short lived even in the form of a one-on-one bout with Tihanyi, and I’m sure that the “Axeman” has more wins to pick up in order to start off another road to the belt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the We Love Wrestling results from Oberhausen…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-laurance-roman-w-robert-dreissker-and-arrows-of-hungary-defeated-nick-schreier&quot;&gt;Match #1: Laurance Roman (w/ Robert Dreissker and Arrows of Hungary) defeated Nick Schreier&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;…in less than three minutes by making submit to an arm-trapped crossface. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 0.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-axel-tischer-defeated-peter-tihanyi&quot;&gt;Match #2: Axel Tischer defeated Peter Tihanyi&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The last time both men competed in a one-on-one match was on the 24th episode of We Love Wrestling, back when Tischer was the wXw Unified World Wrestling Champion. Also, Tihanyi competed with tape on his lower back. During the match, Tihanyi performed the “ballin’” gesture (ala MVP and recently Carmelo Hayes) and Tischer caught the “basketball”; he and the referee then passed the “ball” to each other before Tischer threw it into the audience. Towards the end, Tihanyi went for a moonsault, but the pain in his lower back stalled him and made him miss the target, leading to Tischer winning with a suplex converted into a uranage. After the match, Andy Jackson interviewed Tihanyi who blamed his trainers—that are now his enemies and are part of Amboss—for the loss. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-3-aigle-blanc-defeated-michael-schenkenberg-w-nikita-charisma&quot;&gt;Match #3: Aigle Blanc defeated Michael Schenkenberg (w/ Nikita Charisma)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As soon as the match began, Charisma distracted Aigle Blanc, allowing Schenkenberg to sneak attack his opponent. The match ended with Schenkenberg slithering to Charisma before Aigle Blanc hit him with a coast-to-coast dropkick followed by a 450 splash for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-4-fast-time-moodo-defeated-masha-slamovich&quot;&gt;Match #4: Fast Time Moodo defeated Masha Slamovich&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Masha’s right shoulder was taped, but wasn’t worked on in this match. Moodo won after hitting her with the Blackbelt Kick. Both wrestlers shook hands afterwards. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-5-peacock-main-event-arrows-of-hungary-w-robert-dreissker-and-laurance-roman-defeated-vincent-heisenberg--maggot&quot;&gt;Match #5 (Peacock main event): Arrows of Hungary (w/ Robert Dreissker and Laurance Roman) defeated Vincent Heisenberg &amp;amp; Maggot&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;…to qualify for the wXw Tag Team Festival. After Heisenberg cleaned house, Icarus and Dover double teamed on him and then hit Maggot—who attempted to rescue his tag team partner—with a hip toss into the back of Heisenberg; they then won after hitting Heisenberg with the Crossfire. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-jonathan-gresham-defeated-tristan-archer-by-count-out&quot;&gt;Main event: Jonathan Gresham defeated Tristan Archer by count out&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Archer retained the wXw Unified World Wrestling Championship. Archer fought Gresham at the entryway before the match started. During the match, Archer attempted to use the ring bell as the weapon until the referee took it away from him; he then hit Gresham with the championship belt until Gresham was able to put his foot on the bottom rope. Later on, Archer and Gresham went at it at ringside, and Archer threw the challenger into rows of chairs in the crowd; he wanted to get a count out victory until fans helped Gresham back into the ring to stop the ring out count (ironically similar to how fans helped Warren Banks back into the ring in his match against Gresham at Progress’ 10th anniversary show). Towards the end, both wrestlers fought at ringside again, and Archer put Gresham back into the ring before walking away and giving his opponent the count out win on purpose. Afterwards, Gresham blasted Archer for his actions including the count out victory, and then vowed to fight Amboss with three competitors of his choosing on the next episode of We Love Wrestling. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.25/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;icw-fight-club&quot;&gt;ICW Fight Club&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that the belated recaps are out of the way, let’s head to the GPWA in Glasgow, Scotland in the United Kingdom for an episode of ICW Fight Club, shall we?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This week’s episode was the go-home edition of ICW Fight Club prior to Shug’s Hoose Party 7. The storylines heading into that event came into play in all three matches that took place this week; one involved the ICW Women’s Champion Molly Spartan before defending the belt against Session Moth Martina, one involved Thatcher Wright and Levi before facing Chris Bungard and Aaron Echo respectively, and one involved a tag team match that had two teams of strange bedfellows in the forms of BT Gunn &amp;amp; Jack Jester and Leyton Buzzard &amp;amp; Kez Evans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-09-12/icw-fight-club.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;ICW Fight Club&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Out of the three matches that took place, my favorite match would have to go to the opening bout that was also a warmup to Molly Spartan prior to facing Session Moth Martina at SHP7; both she and Regina Rosendahl, who made her debut, had a great showing in this non-title bout. I can definitely see why Regina is often called the best in Finnish wrestling by fans, pro wrestlers, critics and such, and she didn’t disappoint me one bit in her ICW debut where she gave the champion a run for her money. As for Molly, seeing her clash with Regina and picking up the win definitely got her ready prior to defending the title against Martina; the “Beautiful Bruiser” is indeed a force to be reckoned with when it comes to women’s wrestling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the match results from Glasgow…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-molly-spartan-defeated-regina-rosendahl-in-a-non-title-match&quot;&gt;Match #1: Molly Spartan defeated Regina Rosendahl in a non-title match&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As noted moments ago, this was Regina’s ICW debut. She went for a guillotine leg drop, but missed, allowing Molly to win with a spear. After the match, Molly chastised the fans for cheering for Session Moth Martina instead of her ever since she was announced as her Shug’s Hoose Party 7 opponent; Molly then said that Martina is just like her, but then vowed to make her know her place at SHP7. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-levi-defeated-thatcher-wright-by-disqualification&quot;&gt;Match #2: Levi defeated Thatcher Wright by disqualification&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Towards the end, Wright attempted to use his Margaret Thatcher book as a weapon, but Levi hit him with a kick and a cutter for a near fall before kicking the book out of the ring. Then, Aaron Echo came from the crowd and attacked Levi out of the ring—giving Levi the DQ win—and to the back. Afterwards, Wright declared himself the winner and then had a moment of silence for Boris Johnson until Chris Bungard chased him out of the ring; after Bungard shouted out “[f-bomb] Boris Johnson”, “[f-bomb] Margaret Thatcher” and “[f-bomb] the Tories”, he vowed to make Wright’s match his last time in a wrestling ring at SHP7. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-bt-gunn--jack-jester-defeated-leyton-buzzard--kez-evans&quot;&gt;Main event: BT Gunn &amp;amp; Jack Jester defeated Leyton Buzzard &amp;amp; Kez Evans&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As soon as the match began, Evans refused to fight Jester and tagged in Buzzard who then wanted to face Gunn who was also tagged in. Near the end, Evans punched Jester into Gunn, knocking him off the apron; Gunn would then refuse to tag out Jester and, less than a minute later, walked to the back. Then, after Buzzard went to work on Jester, Evans tagged himself in and beat down Buzzard before eyeing on his SHP7 opponent. When Jester made a comeback, K.O.E. appeared on the apron, and Jester knocked them off until Evans crotched him from behind. Evans then attempted to hit Jester with brass knuckles until Buzzard blindsided the champion with his Square Go! briefcase; this led to Jester taking Evans’ knuckles and slugging him with them for the win. Post-match, Jester took the ICW World Heavyweight Championship and posed with it over the unconscious Evans. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;nxt&quot;&gt;NXT&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We now head to Orlando, Florida in the United States for an episode of NXT.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are one week away from NXT Heatwave, and there were three more matches added to the card this week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One match was made during the final accord between Santos Escobar and Tony D’Angelo. This was made after Escobar returned and cost D’Angelo and Stacks a chance to win the NXT Tag Team Championship over the Creed Brothers. The accord took place without Stacks or the rest of Legado del Fantasma, and the two agreed on a match that will take place next week; their match at Heatwave will be a street fight. There is a stipulation added to this match however. If D’Angelo wins, Escobar is gone from NXT; if Escobar wins, Legado del Fantasma is free from the D’Angelo Family. I knew all along that adding all members of Legado del Fantasma to the D’Angelo Family wouldn’t go so well, and thankfully this match—no matter what the result will be—will hopefully be one way to kiss this expanded faction turned dumpster fire goodbye.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another match that was made was Carmelo Hayes defending the NXT North American Championship against Giovanni Vinci. Hayes has started issuing challenges for his belt recently, and Vinci was the next person to answer the challenge even by making Hayes and the fans think that Nathan Frazer—theme song and all—was coming to the ring. Originally, Vinci wanted a shot at the title last week before Frazer surprised him by getting to the ring first; this week, it was Vinci’s turn and he said that he sees Hayes as “A guy” instead of “the A-Champion” until Hayes said that he saved Vinci from Frazer and not Vinci saved him from the previous challenger. This led to both Hayes and Vinci brawling until the two got separated. It’s good to see Vinci going for gold in singles competition besides—back then—seeing him go for tag team gold in the past, although I’m leaning towards Hayes retaining the title since his second reign as the North American Champion is running as strong as his first reign as the holder of that belt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The third match that was made was between Cora Jade and Roxanne Perez, friends turned enemies. Roxanne was disgusted over Cora’s actions from costing her the NXT Women’s Championship against Mandy Rose to throwing the NXT Women’s Tag Team Championship belt into a trash can—two weeks before Kayden Carter &amp;amp; Katana Chance won them—which then led to challenging her to a match at Heatwave. Cora originally declined the challenge last week, but after Roxanne returned the favor by having her former friend lose to Zoey Stark in this week’s main event, this match was made for Heatwave. I knew that a match between Cora and Roxanne would be made, especially for either a special episode of NXT or one of their premium live events; I’m also hoping that this isn’t the only one-on-one match that the two will compete in, and—like Seth Rollins and Cody Rhodes from WrestleMania to Hell In A Cell—will have more bouts including matches that have stipulations such as a street fight, “I Quit”, or something like that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-09-12/nxt.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;NXT&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay, now that I’m done getting ahead of myself, this week’s episode had six matches. Like the 33rd episode of wXw We Love Wrestling, half of the matches weren’t as good as the other half due to three of the six being short lived, while the other three were indeed good bouts. My favorite of the good three would go to the one-on-one match between Apollo Crews and Roderick Strong. This contest was made after Strong berated Crews for getting along with the rest of Diamond Mine—especially the Creed Brothers and Damon Kemp—behind his back, leading to him challenging Crews to that match. This was a great match showcasing two black-and-gold originals clashing in the ring on the nowadays multicolored brand, and I do agree with Wade Barrett—who said this on commentary—on seeing WWE making this bout one of their “match of the year” candidates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the NXT results from Orlando…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-nikkita-lyons-defeated-kiana-james-in-four-minutes&quot;&gt;Match #1: Nikkita Lyons defeated Kiana James in four minutes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kiana, who came to the ring equipped with her laptop bag, worked on Nikkita’s left leg. Nikkita came back before hitting Kiana with a jumping heel kick followed by a split-legged leg drop for the win. Afterwards, Kiana blindsided Nikkita with her bag. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-wes-lee-defeated-trick-williams-w-carmelo-hayes-2-1-in-a-rounds-match&quot;&gt;Match #2: Wes Lee defeated Trick Williams (w/ Carmelo Hayes) 2-1 in a rounds match&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Similar to Heritage Cup matches on NXT UK, this match was divided into six rounds, with falls won by pinfall, submission or knockout. Both wrestlers came into the ring with boxing gloves, and fought with them in round 1 until Williams came close to hitting Lee with a knockout punch as time ran out. In round 2, both wrestlers fought without gloves, and Williams took the 1-0 lead after hitting Lee—who was distracted by Hayes—with a bicycle kick. Round 3 ended after Lee was unable to make Williams submit to a half crab, but he ended up tying the score 1-1 in round 4 after a crucifix rollup to his opponent who then—with one glove he put on later in that round—hit him with a left hook. In round 5, Lee put on one of his gloves while Williams was recovering from a bulldog and returned the favor with a hook of his own for the 2-1 win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-3-arianna-grace-defeated-thea-hail-w-andre-chase-and-bodhi-hayward-in-almost-four-minutes&quot;&gt;Match #3: Arianna Grace defeated Thea Hail (w/ Andre Chase and Bodhi Hayward) in almost four minutes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This match was made after Arianna accused Thea for giving her a black eye during training, leading to Chase—in his Chase U office—making the match. Near the end, Arianna pretended that she was hit in the eye again before hitting Thea with a boot followed by the Wasteland (ala Wade Barrett) for the win. &lt;strong&gt;No score.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-4-apollo-crews-defeated-roderick-strong&quot;&gt;Match #4: Apollo Crews defeated Roderick Strong&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Crews’ lower back was worked on during the match. Strong had Crews in the Stronghold crab until Crews kicked Strong out of the ring to get out of the hold. The match ended with Crews hitting Strong with a pop up uranage. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4.25/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-5-pretty-deadly-defeated-malik-blade--edris-enofé-in-four-minutes&quot;&gt;Match #5: Pretty Deadly defeated Malik Blade &amp;amp; Edris Enofé in four minutes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the match, Kit Wilson and Elton Prince mocked Josh Briggs &amp;amp; Brooks Jensen by hitting Blade with Briggs &amp;amp; Jensen’s sliding out-of-the-ring punch until the NXT UK Tag Team Champions—with Fallon Henley in tow—appeared. Near the end, Prince handed Wilson a steel chair before Blade dove onto him. Then, Briggs attempted to take the chair away from Wilson until Wilson threw Enofé into the chair and Briggs before Pretty Deadly won with Spilled Milk to Enofé. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 0.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-zoey-stark-defeated-cora-jade&quot;&gt;Main event: Zoey Stark defeated Cora Jade&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mandy Rose joined Vic Joseph and Wade Barrett on commentary. Cora came to the ring with a black kendo stick. During the match, Cora attempted to hit Zoey with the stick until Zoey dodged the shot and hit her with a German suplex. Then, towards the end, Cora attempted to use the stick again until Roxanne Perez appeared and took the weapon from her; this led Zoey to hitting Cora with a flipping GTS for the win. Afterwards, Roxanne chased Cora out of the ring and to the back with the kendo stick, then Mandy attempted to blindside Zoey until Zoey hit her with the flipping GTS before posing with the NXT Women’s Championship. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;nxt-uk&quot;&gt;NXT UK&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We return to the United Kingdom, but this time we head to the BT Sports Studios in London, England for an episode of NXT UK.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The NXT United Kingdom Championship tournament began this week with two matches; one was between Oliver Carter and Charlie Dempsey, and the other was between Wolfgang and Trent Seven. The other round 1 matches—Mark Andrews vs. Joe Coffey, and Kenny Williams vs. Tyler Bate—will take place next week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both round 1 matches were better than the two shorter matches (yes, I am aware that I’m pissing and moaning about short matches once again…lol…) that were sandwiched between the tournament bouts. Carter and Dempsey had a good showing that kicked off this week’s episode of NXT UK, with the storyline being Carter both looking to go 3-0 against Die Familie (after defeating Teoman followed by Rohan Raja in back-to-back matches) as well as eyeing on the vacant NXT United Kingdom Championship belt. Both Wolfgang and Seven also had a good showing in their match that wrapped up this week’s episode, with the storyline being Seven working on his heel character especially on his run for the title.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the match results from London…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-oliver-carter-defeated-charlie-dempsey-w-teoman-and-rohan-raja&quot;&gt;Match #1: Oliver Carter defeated Charlie Dempsey (w/ Teoman and Rohan Raja)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;…in round 1 of the NXT United Kingdom Championship tournament. Teoman and Raja closed in on Carter until Carter fought them out of the ring before the match started. Carter’s left leg was worked on during the match; it wasn’t at 100% due to Dempsey putting him in a half crab during the Die Familie ambush not too long ago. Dempsey had the same hold applied to Carter until Carter got out of it with a rollup for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-eliza-alexander-defeated-thea-hail-w-andre-chase-and-bodhi-hayward-in-four-minutes&quot;&gt;Match #2: Eliza Alexander defeated Thea Hail (w/ Andre Chase and Bodhi Hayward) in four minutes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After blocking Thea’s moonsault, Eliza won with a sliding boot. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-3-sam-gradwell-defeated-teoman-w-rohan-raja-in-five-minutes&quot;&gt;Match #3: Sam Gradwell defeated Teoman (w/ Rohan Raja) in five minutes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the match, Teoman pretended to have an ankle injury, leading to Raja hitting the distracted Gradwell from behind with a hotshot across the top rope. Raja would then interfere again by pushing Gradwell off the top rope until the referee ejected him from ringside. In the end, Teoman went for the Seek and Destroy, but Gradwell kicked it away before winning with a Michinoku driver. &lt;strong&gt;My score 0.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-trent-seven-defeated-wolfgang-in-round-1-of-the-nxt-united-kingdom-championship-tournament&quot;&gt;Main event: Trent Seven defeated Wolfgang in round 1 of the NXT United Kingdom Championship tournament&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wolfgang’s lower back was worked on during the match. Towards the end, Wolfgang came back and went for a Swanton Bomb, but Seven blocked it with his knees before winning with the Birminghammer. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;nxt-lvl-up&quot;&gt;NXT: LVL UP&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, we return to Orlando, Florida for an episode of NXT: LVL UP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-09-12/nxt-lvl-up.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;NXT: LVL UP&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All three matches had NXT regulars going toe-to-toe with wrestlers that either need a win or were debuting. My best of the three would have to go to the tag team match between Bodhi Hayward &amp;amp; Andre Chase and newcomers Bronco Nima &amp;amp; Lucien Price. Not only was Chase U finally able to pick up a win this week after seeing Thea Hail’s back-to-back losses on two different shows, but we were also able to see what Nima and Price were capable of. Even though the new additions to the roster didn’t pick up a win, I would love to see more of what Nima and Price have in store in the near future including future episodes of NXT: LVL and/or NXT after seeing them give Chase U’s Hayward and Chase a run for their money this week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the NXT: LVL UP results from Orlando…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-ikemen-jiro-defeated-myles-borne-with-the-ikemen-slash&quot;&gt;Match #1: Ikemen Jiro defeated Myles Borne with the Ikemen Slash&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My score: 2/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-elektra-lopez-defeated-sol-ruca-in-three-minutes&quot;&gt;Match #2: Elektra Lopez defeated Sol Ruca in three minutes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After blocking Sol’s standing moonsault, Elektra won with a blue thunder bomb. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-bodhi-hayward--andre-chase-w-thea-hail-defeated-bronco-nima--lucien-price&quot;&gt;Main event: Bodhi Hayward &amp;amp; Andre Chase (w/ Thea Hail) defeated Bronco Nima &amp;amp; Lucien Price&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As noted above, this was Nima &amp;amp; Price’s debut. The team of Hayward and Chase won after hitting Nima with the Fratliner. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;next-time&quot;&gt;Next time…&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another belated recap or two? Check.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A recap of night #1 of ICW Shug’s Hoose Party 7? Check.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A recap of NXT 2.0 Heatwave? Check.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recaps of two other shows that have “NXT” in the name? Check.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other things that may or may not be part of the shows? I guess you can say “check.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For my newsletters as well as any articles that are on the Wrestling With Johners website, the website is wrestlingwithjohners.com/articles&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For just my newsletters along on the WWJ website, it is wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/pro-darin/&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading! Feel free to comment! I’ll see you next time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Photos shown in the newsletter are from WWE, wXw and ICW.)&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>pro-darin</name></author><category term="articles" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A Special Interview with the Barrie Wrestling Heavyweight Champion Reverso</title><link href="/alliance-pro-wrestling-network/interviews/A-Special-Interview-with-the-Barrie-Wrestling-Heavyweight-Champion-Reverso/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Special Interview with the Barrie Wrestling Heavyweight Champion Reverso" /><published>2022-09-11T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-09-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/alliance-pro-wrestling-network/interviews/A%20Special%20Interview%20with%20the%20Barrie%20Wrestling%20Heavyweight%20Champion%20Reverso</id><content type="html" xml:base="/alliance-pro-wrestling-network/interviews/A-Special-Interview-with-the-Barrie-Wrestling-Heavyweight-Champion-Reverso/"></content><author><name>lewis-carlan</name></author><category term="alliance-pro-wrestling-network" /><category term="interviews" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A Special Interview with the Barrie Wrestling Heavyweight Champion Reverso</title><link href="/alliance-pro-wrestling-network/videos/A-Special-Interview-with-the-Barrie-Wrestling-Heavyweight-Champion-Reverso/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Special Interview with the Barrie Wrestling Heavyweight Champion Reverso" /><published>2022-09-11T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-09-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/alliance-pro-wrestling-network/videos/A%20Special%20Interview%20with%20the%20Barrie%20Wrestling%20Heavyweight%20Champion%20Reverso</id><content type="html" xml:base="/alliance-pro-wrestling-network/videos/A-Special-Interview-with-the-Barrie-Wrestling-Heavyweight-Champion-Reverso/"></content><author><name>lewis-carlan</name></author><category term="alliance-pro-wrestling-network" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Impact Wrestling Review for September 9 2022 - Eddie Edward vs Heath. Aussie Open debuts!</title><link href="/alliance-pro-wrestling-network/videos/Impact-Wrestling-Review-for-September-9-2022-Eddie-Edward-vs-Heath-Aussie-Open-debuts/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Impact Wrestling Review for September 9 2022 - Eddie Edward vs Heath. Aussie Open debuts!" /><published>2022-09-11T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-09-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/alliance-pro-wrestling-network/videos/Impact%20Wrestling%20Review%20for%20September%209%202022%20%20Eddie%20Edward%20vs%20Heath%20Aussie%20Open%20debuts</id><content type="html" xml:base="/alliance-pro-wrestling-network/videos/Impact-Wrestling-Review-for-September-9-2022-Eddie-Edward-vs-Heath-Aussie-Open-debuts/"></content><author><name>lewis-carlan</name></author><category term="alliance-pro-wrestling-network" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Breakdown of CM Punk Scrum Rant. Why he deserve to get fired, and was this a wake up call for Tony Khan!</title><link href="/chokeslam-wrestling-report/The-Breakdown-of-CM-Punk-Scrum-Rant-Why-he-deserve-to-get-fired-and-was-this-a-wake-up-call-for-Tony-Khan/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Breakdown of CM Punk Scrum Rant. Why he deserve to get fired, and was this a wake up call for Tony Khan!" /><published>2022-09-11T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-09-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/chokeslam-wrestling-report/The%20Breakdown%20of%20CM%20Punk%20Scrum%20Rant%20Why%20he%20deserve%20to%20get%20fired%20and%20was%20this%20a%20wake%20up%20call%20for%20Tony%20Khan</id><content type="html" xml:base="/chokeslam-wrestling-report/The-Breakdown-of-CM-Punk-Scrum-Rant-Why-he-deserve-to-get-fired-and-was-this-a-wake-up-call-for-Tony-Khan/"></content><author><name>chokeslam-wrestling-report</name></author><category term="chokeslam-wrestling-report" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">NBA2k23 #shorts</title><link href="/da-call-up/videos/NBA2k23-shorts/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="NBA2k23 #shorts" /><published>2022-09-11T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-09-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/da-call-up/videos/NBA2k23%20shorts</id><content type="html" xml:base="/da-call-up/videos/NBA2k23-shorts/"></content><author><name>da-call-up</name></author><category term="da-call-up" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Talking With Tom is back only on Guilmy Talks</title><link href="/guilmy-talks/Talking-With-Tom-is-back-only-on-Guilmy-Talks/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Talking With Tom is back only on Guilmy Talks" /><published>2022-09-11T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-09-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/guilmy-talks/Talking%20With%20Tom%20is%20back%20only%20on%20Guilmy%20Talks</id><content type="html" xml:base="/guilmy-talks/Talking-With-Tom-is-back-only-on-Guilmy-Talks/"></content><author><name>justin-guilmette</name></author><category term="guilmy-talks" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>