<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-02-08T18:05:47+00:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Wrestling With Johners</title><subtitle>Pro Wrestling podcast with news, reviews and debate from WWE, NXT, NXT:UK, AEW, NJPW, Indy Wrestling and so much more. Listen to Wrestling With Johners on Apple Podcasts, Google Podcasts, Spotify, Podbean, Podcast Addict, Castbox, YouTube or wherever you get your podcasts.</subtitle><author><name>John Scott</name></author><entry><title type="html">Ep102 – 10 LASHES FOR CODY | Velveteen Returns | The Queen on NXT | All NEW Features (with Mags @BadlandsPod)</title><link href="/podcasts/EP102/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep102 – 10 LASHES FOR CODY | Velveteen Returns | The Queen on NXT | All NEW Features (with Mags @BadlandsPod)" /><published>2020-02-08T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-02-08T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP102</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP102/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">‘Transformative’ Changes Ahead For WWE Network</title><link href="/news/Major-changes-to-WWE-network/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="'Transformative' Changes Ahead For WWE Network" /><published>2020-02-07T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-02-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/news/Major-changes-to-WWE-network</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/Major-changes-to-WWE-network/">&lt;p&gt;On Thursday’s investors conference call, WWE chairman Vince McMahon said the company has had advanced talks with major OTT players (alternative streaming services) about changes to the WWE Network that could mean a significant revenue increase for the company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;McMahon called the potential deals “transformative”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-02-07/network.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;network&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those changes could be content rights with marquee events like WrestleMania and the Royal Rumble or perhaps a different distribution model for the WWE Network altogether. McMahon said if a change is made, it will be announced this quarter as the talks are that far along.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When asked about the plans for the Network, McMahon said they have a lot of options. One is to remain as they are now with a free and paid tier while the other is to distribute more content to “the majors”. He later clarified “majors” as OTT companies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This could mean that some or all of WWE’s LIVE Pay-Per-Views will no longer be available on the WWE Network. With the possibility of WrestleMania and Royal Rumble only being available via an alternative ‘Paid Service’.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“There’s no better time as of right now to exercise the selling of our rights,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a follow-up answer, interim CFO Frank Riddick said that while the devil is in the details, there is nothing that would stop them from selling those rights if they chose to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;McMahon was asked about whether they would consider adding advertising to the Network and he said they would be interested if they kept the model as is. If they brought on other partners, that decision would be up to them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As of last quarter, the WWE Network had 1.43 million subscribers worldwide, a 10% drop from the previous quarter, and generated $184.6 million in yearly revenue, down $15 million from 2018. The company predicted a modest increase for Q1 2020 for 1.47 million.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WWE signed two massive five-year TV deals with both Fox (SmackDown) and NBCUniversal (Raw), giving the company $2.35 billion from 2019-2024.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html">On Thursday’s investors conference call, WWE chairman Vince McMahon said the company has had advanced talks with major OTT players (alternative streaming services) about changes to the WWE Network that could mean a significant revenue increase for the company.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">NXT UK Review - 6th February 2020</title><link href="/articles/NXT-Review-6th-February-2020/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="NXT UK Review - 6th February 2020" /><published>2020-02-07T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-02-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/NXT%20Review%206th%20February%202020</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/NXT-Review-6th-February-2020/">&lt;p&gt;WWE NXT UK Review - February 6th 2020&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;piper-niven-vs-dani-luna&quot;&gt;PIPER NIVEN Vs. DANI LUNA&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ok match to start. Piper really needs to build up those wins again. Not to much else to be said here. Dani unsuccessful on this occasion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-02-07/piper-luna.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;piper luna&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WINNER OF THE MATCH: PIPER NIVEN&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tyler-bate-vs-a-kid&quot;&gt;TYLER BATE Vs. A-KID&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-02-07/tyler-akid.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;tyler akid&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a match between Mentor vs Student in this one. Good match. Great back and fourth action. Kid gave Tyler his all unfortunately he seems to have become a more of an Enhancement talent. But it is early days for A-Kid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WINNER OF THE MATCH: TYLER BATE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the match Joesph Connors came out and cut a promo on Tyler. Setting up a possible feud between these two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;pretty-deadly-vs-ashton-smith-and-oliver-carter&quot;&gt;PRETTY DEADLY Vs. ASHTON SMITH AND OLIVER CARTER&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pretty Deadly consist of Sam Stoker and Lewis Howley. I have actually met Stoker at PCW. Both these tag teams need the win. This was a good match here. Pretty Deadly take the loss.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-02-07/carter.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;carter&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WINNER OF THE MATCH: OLIVER CARTER AND ASHTON SMITH&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Out comes Kay Lee Ray to cut a promo. KLR is interupted by Toni Storm. They will have an I quit match for the NXT title at some point soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-02-07/toni-klr.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;toni klr&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MAIN EVENT….&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;eddie-dennis-vs-trent-seven---in-the-first-ever-steel-corners-street-fight&quot;&gt;EDDIE DENNIS Vs. TRENT SEVEN - IN THE FIRST EVER STEEL CORNERS STREET FIGHT&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is my first time seeing a match like this. NXT UK seem to a have a lot of firsts. Good match right here. They fought everywhere and into the crowd. Steel steps were involved. What a match. They fought to the announce table and Trent puts Eddie through a table. Very brutal. Hard hitting action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-02-07/trent-eddie.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;trent eddie&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my opinion the wrong person won.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WINNER OF THE MATCH: TRENT SEVEN&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I give it 8 out of 10.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a very good episode of NXT UK this week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t forget to go check out my YouTube channel the people’s wrestling channel&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IF YOU SMELL WHAT RICK THE ROCK IS COOKIN!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>ricky-j</name></author><summary type="html">WWE NXT UK Review - February 6th 2020</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">AEW Announce Double Or Nothing 2 - May 23rd 2020, MGM Grand Las Vegas</title><link href="/news/AEW-Double-or-Nothing-2-announcement/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="AEW Announce Double Or Nothing 2 - May 23rd 2020, MGM Grand Las Vegas" /><published>2020-02-06T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-02-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/news/AEW%20Double%20or%20Nothing%202%20announcement</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/AEW-Double-or-Nothing-2-announcement/">&lt;p&gt;All Elite Wrestling announced last night that they’ll be returning to the MGM Grand on May 23rd, for a second Double Or Nothing PPV, with tickets going on sale February 14.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-02-06/double-or-nothing-aew-2020.png&quot; alt=&quot;DoN2&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The news was first announced by Justin Barrasso of Sports Illustrated. Barrasso spoke to AEW President &amp;amp; CEO Tony Khan, who touted the success the company has had since the first Double Or Nothing pay-per-view.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Last May, we sparked a revolution with our inaugural Double or Nothing pay-per-view event in Las Vegas,” Khan said. “Double or Nothing rocked the wrestling industry and led to Wednesday Night Dynamite, a top-rated weekly show on TNT reaching millions of viewers worldwide, and over 140,000 live event tickets sold to date.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;As reported by &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/JustinBarrasso?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;@JustinBarrasso&lt;/a&gt; from &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/SInow?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;@SInow&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/AEW?src=hash&amp;amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;#AEW&lt;/a&gt; DOUBLE or NOTHING will return to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/MGMGrand?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;@MGMGrand&lt;/a&gt; Garden Arena on Saturday, May 23rd. Tickets go on sale Friday, February 14th at &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/UN1cNiJJrQ&quot;&gt;https://t.co/UN1cNiJJrQ&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/eg2PabwikF&quot;&gt;https://t.co/eg2PabwikF&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/ELK2uKMoRS&quot;&gt;pic.twitter.com/ELK2uKMoRS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; All Elite Wrestling (@AEWrestling) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/AEWrestling/status/1225164694505148416?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;February 5, 2020&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Khan continued, “It’s been an incredible run, and only fitting that we return to Las Vegas to celebrate our one year anniversary with AEW’s marquee event. On Saturday, May 23, Double or Nothing is back for round two at the MGM Grand Garden Arena. Last year’s event changed the world of wrestling, and this year the stakes will be even higher.”&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html">All Elite Wrestling announced last night that they’ll be returning to the MGM Grand on May 23rd, for a second Double Or Nothing PPV, with tickets going on sale February 14.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Killer Kross &amp;amp; Timothy Thatcher sign with WWE</title><link href="/news/Kille-Kross-Officially-Signs-with-WWE/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Killer Kross &amp; Timothy Thatcher sign with WWE" /><published>2020-02-05T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-02-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/news/Kille-Kross%20Officially%20Signs%20with%20WWE</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/Kille-Kross-Officially-Signs-with-WWE/">&lt;p&gt;As announced on last night’s WWE Backstage on FS1, former IMPACT and Lucha Underground wrestler Killer Kross has officially signed with WWE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-02-05/kross-tim.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;killer kross&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After many weeks of speculation Ryan Satin confirmed on WWE Backstage that Killer Kross has signed with the company. It is not clear which brand Kross will appear on first. Although it is expected that Kross will join the NXT brand and appear on NXT weekly TV within the next few weeks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-02-05/kross.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;killer kross&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was also confirmed last night that another Indy superstar, Timothy Thatcher has signed with WWE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-02-05/timothey.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;killer kross&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thatcher is well-known for wrestling on the Indy circuit around the States and Europe, and is also renowned for being a former stable-mate of Walter and Marcel Barthell, as part of Ring Kampf in wXw in Germany. Similar to Kross, it is expected that Thatcher will join the Black &amp;amp; Gold brand within the next few weeks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expect new ring names for both wrestlers when they officially make their TV debuts.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html">As announced on last night’s WWE Backstage on FS1, former IMPACT and Lucha Underground wrestler Killer Kross has officially signed with WWE.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep101 - KEVIN ISAAC Interview (Independent Wrestling Elite UK)</title><link href="/interviews/podcasts/EP101/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep101 - KEVIN ISAAC Interview (Independent Wrestling Elite UK)" /><published>2020-02-04T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-02-04T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/interviews/podcasts/EP101</id><content type="html" xml:base="/interviews/podcasts/EP101/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Charlotte to answer Rhea’s challenge on this week’s NXT</title><link href="/news/Ripley-confronts-Charlotte-on-Raw/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Charlotte to answer Rhea's challenge on this week's NXT" /><published>2020-02-04T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-02-04T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/news/Ripley%20confronts%20Charlotte%20on%20Raw</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/Ripley-confronts-Charlotte-on-Raw/">&lt;p&gt;On last night’s Monday Night RAW Charlotte Flair conducted an in-ring promo to address which championship she will be challenging for as the Royal Rumble winner, at WrestleMania 36 on 5th April.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-02-04/rhea-charlotte.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;charlotte &amp;amp; ripley&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Charlotte announced that “She has held the RAW Women’s championship multiple times and has beaten Becky” and that “She’s held the Smackdown Women’s champion multiple times and has beaten Bailey”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-02-04/charlotte.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;charlotte&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the fans in the arena started to chant NXT, Charlotte said that “The Queen has love for NXT and NXT has love for the Queen”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-02-04/rhea.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;ripley&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Current NXT Women’s champion Ripley came out to address Charlotte. Ripley told Charlotte “That The Queen has already beaten Becky and Bailey. But she has not beaten her”. Ripley continued by saying that she has however beaten the Queen, as Charlotte walked out of the ring, with Ripley holding her NXT gold above her head.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-02-04/Charlotte-on-NXT.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;charlotte &amp;amp; ripley&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Later in the evening it was announced that Charlotte will be on NXT this Wednesday on the USA Network, to address Rhea Ripley’s challenge and to announce which title she will be challenging for at WrestleMania 36.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the storyline would suggest it looks certain that the Women’s NXT Championship will be defended at WrestleMania, with Charlotte going up against current NXT Women’s champion Rhea Ripley.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-02-04/takeover-portland.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;takeover&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s not forget that Ripley will be defending her NXT Championship on 16th February at NXT Takeover Portland against current No.1 contender Bianca Belair.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We could also see Charlotte make a cameo apperence during the Ripley vs. Belair match in Portland, further setting up their match for Mania 36.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And with Belair’s very strong showing at this year’s Royal Rumble I wouldn’t be surprised to see Belair featured in a WrestleMania match as well. With the possibility of the NXT Women’s championship match becoming a Triple-Threat match between all three.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html">On last night’s Monday Night RAW Charlotte Flair conducted an in-ring promo to address which championship she will be challenging for as the Royal Rumble winner, at WrestleMania 36 on 5th April.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">NXT UK Review - 30th January 2020</title><link href="/articles/NXT-Review-30th-January-2020/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="NXT UK Review - 30th January 2020" /><published>2020-02-03T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-02-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/NXT%20Review%2030th%20January%202020</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/NXT-Review-30th-January-2020/">&lt;p&gt;NXT UK Review - 30th January 2020&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-hunt-vs-oney-lorcan-and-danny-burch&quot;&gt;THE HUNT Vs. ONEY LORCAN AND DANNY BURCH&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-02-03/primate.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;primate&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good match. I do think Danny should be just NXT UK from now on. This was a fresh match. I do like fresh matches. The Hunt really need that big win, but they didn’t get it here. An assited DDT by Burch and Lorcan for the win.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WINNER OF THE MATCH: ONEY LORCAN AND DANNY BURCH&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eddie Dennis comes out to cut a promo. Trent Seven interrupts him wanting a rematch and wants it to be a street fight. Eddie and Trent brawl to end this segment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-02-03/eddie-trent.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;eddie trent&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;nina-samuels-vs-isla-dawn&quot;&gt;NINA SAMUELS Vs. ISLA DAWN&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ok match here, even though it was a rematch. Isla was in control for most of the match. She seems to have got alot better. Isla goes over.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-02-03/nina-isla.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;nina and isla&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WINNER OF THE MATCH: ISLA DAWN&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tyson-t-bone-vs-ridge-holland&quot;&gt;TYSON T-BONE Vs. RIDGE HOLLAND&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-02-03/ridge.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;ridge&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was a scrap. A brawl. Hard hitting action. Both men laying in the punches. I liked T-Bone’s attitude here, he needs to show more of it. He also needs a big win, but didn’t get it here. Ridge Holland wins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-02-03/ridge2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;ridge2&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WINNER OF THE MATCH: RIDGE HOLLAND&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tonight’s Main Event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;imperium-vs-dave-mastiff-mark-andrews-and-flash-morgan-webster&quot;&gt;IMPERIUM Vs. DAVE MASTIFF, MARK ANDREWS AND FLASH MORGAN WEBSTER&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good match. All men getting some offense in. The crowd was hot for this match.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-02-03/6-man.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;6-man&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Walter gets involved, taking out Dave Mastiff. I liked this match. Imperium win.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-02-03/mastiff-walter.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;mastiff-walter&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WINNER OF THE MATCH: IMPERIUM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2020-02-03/imperium.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;imperium&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Good episode of NXT UK. I give it 7 out of 10&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t forget to go check out my YouTube channel the people’s wwe channel&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IF YOU SMELL WHAT RICK THE ROCK IS COOKIN!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>ricky-j</name></author><summary type="html">NXT UK Review - 30th January 2020</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep100 – Fantasy Booking Mania | Q&amp;amp;A Special | NXT &amp;amp; Dusty Cup Final</title><link href="/podcasts/EP100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep100 – Fantasy Booking Mania | Q&amp;A Special | NXT &amp; Dusty Cup Final" /><published>2020-02-01T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-02-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP100</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP100/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">NXT UK Review - 23rd January 2020</title><link href="/articles/nxt-uk-23-January-2020/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="NXT UK Review - 23rd January 2020" /><published>2020-01-29T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-29T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/nxt%20uk%2023%20January%202020</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/nxt-uk-23-January-2020/">&lt;p&gt;NXT UK Aiden English is on commentary to replace Nigel McGuinness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Johnny Saint and Sid Scala in the ring. Out come Imperium Johnny and Sid present Walter with the new NXT UK title belt. Walter cuts a promo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First match of the night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JORDAN DEVLIN Vs. LIGERO.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good match. Plenty of back and fourth action. Ligero really needed the win here but it didn’t happen. I believe Devlin has been on a roll on NXT UK for a while. Devlin with the devlin-side for the win.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WINNER OF THE MATCH: JORDAN DEVLIN.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next match up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ILJA DRAGUNOV Vs. JOSH MORRELL&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was mostly a squash match. I was impressed with Josh here. I have actually met Josh under the name Josh Turbo at a local show in Blackburn. Ok match here. Ilja hitting his finisher for the win.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WINNER OF THE MATCH: ILJA DRAGUNOV&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the match Ilja took the microphone and spoke. Joe Coffey came out and spoke.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Main event now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TRAVIS BANKS Vs. THE BRIAN KENDRICK.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Great to see Brian Kendrick on NXT UK. This was a good match. They fought to the outside. Kendrick got a good pop from the crowd. I’m not too sure when I last saw Kendrick wrestle last on WWE tv. Good main event and the right person one. Banks with a much needed win.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WINNER OF THE MATCH: TRAVIS BANKS&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DON’T FORGET TO GO AND CHECK OUT MY YOUTUBE CHANNEL THE PEOPLE’S WWE CHANNEL IF YOU SMELL WHAT RICK THE ROCK IS COOKIN!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>ricky-j</name></author><summary type="html">NXT UK Aiden English is on commentary to replace Nigel McGuinness.</summary></entry></feed>