<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-10-13T17:12:41+00:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Wrestling With Johners</title><subtitle>Pro Wrestling podcast with news, reviews and debate from WWE, NXT, NXT:UK, AEW, NJPW, Indy Wrestling and so much more. Listen to Wrestling With Johners on Apple Podcasts, Google Podcasts, Spotify, Podbean, Podcast Addict, Castbox, YouTube or wherever you get your podcasts.</subtitle><author><name>John Scott</name></author><entry><title type="html">Bucklebomb Live presents After Elite.</title><link href="/bucklebomb-entertainment/videos/Bucklebomb-Live-presents-After-Elite/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bucklebomb Live presents After Elite." /><published>2022-10-13T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-10-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/bucklebomb-entertainment/videos/Bucklebomb%20Live%20presents%20After%20Elite</id><content type="html" xml:base="/bucklebomb-entertainment/videos/Bucklebomb-Live-presents-After-Elite/"></content><author><name>bucklebomb-entertainment</name></author><category term="bucklebomb-entertainment" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Da Call Up Podcast : Conversations With Kenny</title><link href="/da-call-up/videos/Da-Call-Up-Podcast-Conversations-With-Kenny/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Da Call Up Podcast : Conversations With Kenny" /><published>2022-10-13T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-10-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/da-call-up/videos/Da%20Call%20Up%20Podcast%20%20Conversations%20With%20Kenny</id><content type="html" xml:base="/da-call-up/videos/Da-Call-Up-Podcast-Conversations-With-Kenny/"></content><author><name>da-call-up</name></author><category term="da-call-up" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Acclaimed R.I.P. SCISSORING 2021-2022 #shorts #aewdynamite #aew</title><link href="/da-call-up/videos/The-Acclaimed-RIP-SCISSORING-20212022-shorts-aewdynamite-aew/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Acclaimed R.I.P. SCISSORING 2021-2022 #shorts #aewdynamite #aew" /><published>2022-10-13T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-10-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/da-call-up/videos/The%20Acclaimed%20RIP%20SCISSORING%2020212022%20shorts%20aewdynamite%20aew</id><content type="html" xml:base="/da-call-up/videos/The-Acclaimed-RIP-SCISSORING-20212022-shorts-aewdynamite-aew/"></content><author><name>da-call-up</name></author><category term="da-call-up" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">AEW Dynamite Live Reaction, Review 🚨 | October 12 , 2022</title><link href="/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/AEW-Dynamite-Live-Reaction-Review-October-12-2022/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="AEW Dynamite Live Reaction, Review 🚨 | October 12 , 2022" /><published>2022-10-13T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-10-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/AEW%20Dynamite%20%20Live%20Reaction%20Review%20%20%20%20October%2012%20%202022</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/AEW-Dynamite-Live-Reaction-Review-October-12-2022/"></content><author><name>jofo-in-the-ring</name></author><category term="jofo-in-the-ring" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Jungle Boy Jack Perry entrance AEW DYNAMITE Toronto</title><link href="/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/Jungle-Boy-Jack-Perry-entrance-AEW-DYNAMITE-Toronto/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Jungle Boy Jack Perry entrance AEW DYNAMITE Toronto" /><published>2022-10-13T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-10-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/Jungle%20Boy%20Jack%20Perry%20entrance%20AEW%20DYNAMITE%20Toronto</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/Jungle-Boy-Jack-Perry-entrance-AEW-DYNAMITE-Toronto/"></content><author><name>jofo-in-the-ring</name></author><category term="jofo-in-the-ring" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">SERENA DEEB IS GREAT!</title><link href="/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/SERENA-DEEB-IS-GREAT/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="SERENA DEEB IS GREAT!" /><published>2022-10-13T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-10-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/SERENA%20DEEB%20IS%20GREAT</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jofo-in-the-ring/videos/SERENA-DEEB-IS-GREAT/"></content><author><name>jofo-in-the-ring</name></author><category term="jofo-in-the-ring" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Issue 39 Shows of September 24-30, 2022</title><link href="/articles/Issue-39-Shows-of-September-24-30,-2022/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Issue 39 Shows of September 24-30, 2022" /><published>2022-10-13T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-10-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/Issue%2039%20Shows%20of%20September%2024-30,%202022</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/Issue-39-Shows-of-September-24-30,-2022/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png&quot; alt=&quot;pro darin&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;safety-first&quot;&gt;Safety First&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before getting to the shows, I hope that everyone on the east coast in the United States stayed safe during Hurricane Ian. This issue is dedicated those that were affected by the wrath of the hurricane.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;progress-chapter-138-the-deadly-viper-tourcodename-cottonmouth&quot;&gt;Progress Chapter 138: The Deadly Viper Tour—Codename: Cottonmouth&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ll kick things off with a belated recap as promised.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 138th chapter of Progress Wrestling took place on August 14, 2022 at the Boiler Shop in Newcastle, England in the United Kingdom; it served as part 2 of the Deadly Viper Tour. From what I saw on Peacock, the ring in the venue had fans on three sides, with the fourth side consisting of glass doors and windows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like in the last chapter that kicked off the Deadly Viper Tour, this chapter had eight matches on the card; it consisted of two championship matches, one match where the winner would qualify for this year’s Natural Progression tournament, and five exhibition matches that did or didn’t have champions competing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-10-13/cottonmouth.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;PROGRESS cottonmmouth&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To me, all eight matches ranged from fair to excellent. My favorite regular match of the chapter would go to Konosuke Takeshita’s second Progress match that saw him go toe-to-toe with veteran Dean Allmark. It was a great back and forth bout between the two, even with moments that occurred at ringside besides in the ring prior to near falls being made after signature maneuvers—including finishers—were exchanged left and right. In the end, it was Takeshita picking up his second straight Progress victory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for the championship matches that took place, we saw both the Progress Tag Team Championship and the Progress Women’s Championship on the line. Out of the two bouts that occurred, my favorite would go to the women’s championship match between Kanji and Rhio. Not only was it good to see Rhio back in Progress action, but also what she had in store for Kanji especially in this title bout. In the end, it was Kanji who retained the belt after overcoming moments such as getting one of her ankles worked on—instead of her left arm which has been targeted several times even, going back to last year, before taking time away due to injury—besides not being preoccupied with her current rival Laura di Matteo who appeared after the match came to a close. SoCal Val—who joined Olie Spring on commentary in this chapter—was not kidding when she said that the women’s division in Progress is, like the tag team division, “scorching hot”; this championship match definitely proved it that day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the match results from Newcastle…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-the-sunshine-machine-defeated-lykos-gym-to-retain-the-progress-tag-team-championship&quot;&gt;Match #1: The Sunshine Machine defeated Lykos Gym to retain the Progress Tag Team Championship.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before the match started, Kid Lykos and Kid Lykos II blindsided TK Cooper and Chuck Mambo until the champions fought back. Early in the match, the Sunshine Machine took turns holding up Lykos II in a delayed vertical suplex position both in and out of the ring, leading to SoCal Val making a Coldplay reference on commentary (i.e.: “Talk about a rush of blood to the head…”). Also, during the match, Lykos knocked Mambo off the apron and fought him out of the building and locked him out; Mambo would return to the doors that were—as I mentioned in the beginning of this recap—at one side of the ring seconds before tagging in and cleaning house.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Near the end, Lykos sent Cooper head first into a post while Lykos II took a tray out of their satchel and hit Mambo with it before crotching him and hitting him with a brainbuster; Cooper recovered in time to break up the pin afterwards. Then, the Sunshine Machine made a comeback and—after Cooper hit Lykos with a shooting star press from the apron—hit Lykos II with Captain Midnight’s Revenge (Death Valley driver/double knee gutbuster combo) for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-liam-slater-defeated-screwface-ahmed-and-shreddy-in-a-triple-threat-match-to-qualify-for-the-natural-progression-tournament&quot;&gt;Match #2: Liam Slater defeated Screwface Ahmed and Shreddy in a triple threat match to qualify for the Natural Progression tournament.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(NOTE: Liam Slater is not to be confused with Leon Slater who also competed on this chapter as you’ll see shortly.) Before the match started, Shreddy said that he dislikes fighting “skinny fat ass Johnnies” like Slater and Ahmed, and then poked fun of the fans and their chants before calling them “disgusting sweat hogs.” Earlier, Slater had Ahmed in a cloverleaf before—while holding onto Ahmed—putting Shreddy in an abdominal stretch until Shreddy powered out of the hold. Later, Slater had Shreddy in a half crab while Ahmed had the same wrestler in a crossface until Slater surprised Ahmed with a crucifix for two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Towards the end, Slater hit Ahmed with a cross bomb until Shreddy broke up the pin before Slater put him in a half crab; Ahmed fought back until Slater rolled him up with a seated La Magistral for the win. After the match, Tate Mayfairs came into the ring and said that he was helping Progress grow, then said that he didn’t need to be in a qualifying match like the three did because he’s a “certified superstar”; he then vowed to knockout Effy and then win the Natural Progression tournament and the Progress World Championship, and then had ring announcer Simon Miller hold up one of his shirts before leaving. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-3-raven-creed-defeated-eliza-alexander-both-women-went-at-it-seconds-before-the-bell-rang&quot;&gt;Match #3: Raven Creed defeated Eliza Alexander. Both women went at it seconds before the bell rang.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The match ended with Raven hitting Eliza with the Hellmouth for the win. Afterwards, Raven—while interviewed by Jayde—challenged Lana Austin to a straitjacket match. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-4-the-greedy-souls-defeated-the-smokin-aces&quot;&gt;Match #4: The Greedy Souls defeated the Smokin’ Aces.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After Brendan White and Danny Jones hit Nick Riley with back-to-back Claymores, Jones hit Charlie Sterling with a piledriver on the apron; then, the Greedy Souls hit Riley with a catapult/sidewalk slam combo for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-5-kanji-defeated-rhio-to-retain-the-progress-womens-championship&quot;&gt;Match #5: Kanji defeated Rhio to retain the Progress Women’s Championship.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rhio worked on Kanji’s left ankle during the match; Kanji would fight back by forearming and dropkicking her while she was tangled in the ropes, causing Rhio to bleed from the mouth. The match ended with Rhio going for an air raid crash until Kanji countered and won with a hard back elbow. After the match, Laura di Matteo ran in and attacked Kanji and Rhio—who was helping the champion during the beatdown—before working on the ankle while vowing to win the belt. Laura then stood over Kanji with the title until Rhio shoved her out of the ring before helping up Kanji. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-6-maggot-defeated-spike-trivet-by-disqualification&quot;&gt;Match #6: Maggot defeated Spike Trivet by disqualification.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before the match started, Trivet came to the ring and threw a kid’s cap elsewhere in the audience before telling him “Wait until your father tells you about Santa Claus.” Then, Trivet took the microphone from Simon Miller before the introductions were wrapped up, and poked fun of Maggot’s nickname “Son of Nothing”—saying “nothing is [f-bombing] right”—before calling him a “disgusting freak”, calling Newcastle a “shithole”, and saying that Maggot being nothing doesn’t make him special.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the match, Trivet attempted to use his key as a weapon, but slid it by his opponent to distract him and hit him with a cheap shot; he then worked on Maggot’s nose and tongue piercings until Maggot responded back with—to quote the cartoon “Ed, Edd n Eddy”—a purple nurple. Trivet would later pretend to be Cara Noir after hitting his opponent with a trifecta of Swan Woo dropkicks, and then hit him with a necktie neckbreaker until Maggot spat at him…and I have to admit it besides sound disgusting, but that was one big ass loogie…that aside, Maggot won by DQ after Trivet attacked him with the key before storming off and throwing the kid’s cap elsewhere again. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-7-konosuke-takeshita-defeated-dean-allmark&quot;&gt;Match #7: Konosuke Takeshita defeated Dean Allmark.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the match, after Takeshita hit Allmark with a piledriver (after Allmark did a headstand while in a headscissors) followed by a DDT on the apron, he fought his opponent into the audience—including having him sit on a fan’s lap—before hitting him with a running big boot into the chairs. Near the end, Allmark countered the running knee strike with a rollup for two, then backslid him while performing a headstand for another two until Takeshita came back with a running knee strike for a near fall followed by a sit out powerbomb for three. Both men shook hands and bowed to one another afterwards. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-hayata-luke-jacobs--big-damo-defeated-the-0121&quot;&gt;Main event: Hayata, Luke Jacobs &amp;amp; Big Damo defeated the 0121.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Leon Slater is now officially a member of the 0121. Combinations by both teams occurred during the bout including Slater, Man Like Dereiss and Dan Moloney hitting Damon with a powerbomb/double kick combo, the aforementioned Progress World Champion hitting Slater and Dereiss with a Samoan drop/fallaway slam combo,  and a neckbreaker/powerbomb/backcracker combo to Hayata by the 0121. Then, moments after Slater dove onto Damo and into the chairs in the audience, the opponents came back and beat down Dereiss and Moloney before Hayata, Jacobs and Damo won with Jacobs’ Burning Lariat, Hayata’s Headache and Damo’s Wasteland, senton and Belfast Blitz to Slater. The winning team showed respect to the 0121 afterwards. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;icw-fight-club&quot;&gt;ICW Fight Club&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We now head to the GPWA in Glasgow, Scotland for an episode of ICW Fight Club.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After getting Whit’s Occurrin’?! out of the way, it was time for ICW to refocus on Fear &amp;amp; Loathing XIV come November.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will indeed see a match for the ICW World Heavyweight Championship, but we don’t know how many opponents the champion Kez Evans will have come F&amp;amp;L XIV.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This week’s episode started off with Craig Anthony coming into the ring and said that, while out of action due to an arm injury he suffered last year, thoughts of the current champion—including his recent actions such as sneaking his way to the top of ICW like a snake (after calling Evans “poison”)—were eating him and then announced that he was fighting Evans for the title at Fear &amp;amp; Loathing XIV. Evans came out and said that Anthony need to earn a title shot, and then noted that no one came close to defeating him for the belt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This led to “The Outlaw” Stevie James coming into the ring and reminded Evans that he—James—came close to winning the title months ago on an episode of Fight Club (where weapons brought in by the fans were used if you remember), and then said that he deserved a shot while Anthony needed to wait his turn. Then, Leyton Buzzard—Square Go! briefcase and all—appeared and despite understanding that Anthony and James had a score to settle with the champion, he—after saying that he’s nothing like Evans who “beats a man while he’s down”—announced that he would cash in the briefcase at F&amp;amp;L. Then, after Buzzard got under Anthony’s skin by telling him “save me a spot in Zero-G”, Anthony and Buzzard brawled until Evans put Anthony in the Blood Clot Clutch before James hit the champion with a super kick. Normally, I try not to jump to conclusions, but I got a feeling that—regardless of who is next in line as well as who needs to earn what—we’re going to see a four-way dance for the title at F&amp;amp;L.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-10-13/icw_fight_club.png&quot; alt=&quot;icw_fight_club&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Three matches took place this week and weren’t too bad, although I saw one match that was better than the other two. My favorite match of the episode once again involved BT Gunn, and this time, his opponent was Levi who was looking to get back on track after his match with Aaron Echo at Shug’s Hoose Party 7. Not only did it involve Levi attempting to make a comeback, but it also involved—both during and after the match—Gunn finally cementing his heel turn after tactics that had wrestlers, fans, officials and others ticked off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the match results from Glasgow…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-jason-reed-w-coach-trip-defeated-vaughn-vertigo&quot;&gt;Match #1: Jason Reed (w/ Coach Trip) defeated Vaughn Vertigo.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After Vertigo hit Reed with back-to-back half nelson suplexes, he then hit Reed with a Bryan Danielson knee for a near fall. Vertigo then went for the Coup de Grace to the back, but Reed dodged it and hit him with a clothesline before winning with the Club Deck powerbomb. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-bt-gunn-defeated-levi&quot;&gt;Match #2: BT Gunn defeated Levi.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Levi’s right shoulder had kinesio tape. As soon as the match began, Gunn offered Levi a handshake, and Levi was hesitant at first before finally giving Gunn the handshake until Gunn suckered him with a kick to the gut. Gunn would later on attempt to chop Levi at ringside, but missed and hit the post, leading to Levi slamming it on the apron a few times before the action was brought back into the ring. Gunn worked on Levi’s shoulder later on, and this made Levi unable to perform a springboard maneuver due to the pain in his shoulder; Levi then attempted to go for a top rope maneuver instead of a springboard maneuver until Gunn took him down with a chop followed by the Kill Shot (buzzsaw kick) for a near fall. Then, towards the end, Levi shoved Gunn away and hit him with a shining wizard for two, then went for a top rope maneuver before missing, allowing Gunn to win with a roundhouse kick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the match, Gunn beat down Levi and put him in a crab; guards and referees came in and attempted to stop Gunn until Gunn punched two guards down before working on Levi’s shoulder and putting him back in the crab. Then, Jack Jester ran in and settled Gunn down until Gunn blindsided Jester—who was helping up Levi—and then headbutted another guard on his way out. Jester chased him to the back, and then looked for him backstage until—inside Mark Dallas’ office—Gunn appeared from the closet in the office and attacked him with a nightstick before referees came in and separated the two. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.25/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-glasgow-grindhouse-defeated-ian-skinner--charlie-vyce-to-retain-the-icw-tag-team-championship&quot;&gt;Main event: Glasgow Grindhouse defeated Ian Skinner &amp;amp; Charlie Vyce to retain the ICW Tag Team Championship.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As noted not too long ago, Skinner and Vyce are no longer members of Thatcher’s Cabinet. Near the end, Lou King Sharp hit Vyce with the 0141 (or 619 if you’re Rey Mysterio), Krieger hit him with a sidewalk slam, and Sharp hit him with the Tadpole Splash until Skinner broke up the pin. Then, Thatcher Wright appeared and slid the book in for Skinner and Vyce until the two kicked it out of the ring; the distraction led to the Glasgow Grindhouse winning after a wheelbarrow slam/top rope cutter combo to Vyce. Afterwards, Thatcher came into the ring and wanted Skinner and Vyce to rejoin him until the two ignored him and headed to the back; Thatcher then got down on his knees and asked himself why. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;nxt&quot;&gt;NXT&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We now head to Orlando, Florida in the United States for an episode of NXT.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only will there be a ladder match for the currently vacant NXT North American Championship, but there will also be a match for the NXT Championship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last week, we saw JD McDonagh win a shot at the title by defeating Tyler Bate; then, as soon as the match concluded, and the champion Bron Breakker stood face to face with McDonagh, Ilja Dragunov—returning from an ankle injury he suffered on an episode of NXT UK—came in and encountered the two in the ring.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This week, the “Czar” Dragunov came into the ring and talked about conquering “unbeatable machines” such as Walter (now Gunther) for the NXT United Kingdom Championship at NXT TakeOver 36 last year before vowing to do the same thing to Bron Breakker for the NXT Championship. Then, McDonagh came into the ring and said that he wasn’t surprised that Dragunov followed him to America before Dragunov reminded him of their “loser leaves NXT UK” match; McDonagh then vowed to reinjure Dragunov and end his career until Breakker came into the ring. McDonagh originally wanted to face Breakker for the title again at Halloween Havoc until Breakker had an idea of his own, using the “Steiner math” by saying that McDonagh had a 33 1/3% chance of winning; at Halloween Havoc, Breakker will defend the title against McDonagh and Dragunov. Dragunov does indeed make a great wildcard for what was originally going to be a rematch between Breakker and McDonagh for the title; I definitely look forward to seeing what both NXT UK have up in their sleeves for the NXT Champion come later in October.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eight matches took place on this week’s episode. Aside a slew of short matches (and yes, I am aware that I’m being fussy over short matches…lol…), there were two matches that I enjoyed; one match had an ending that I didn’t expect (and neither did Wes Lee as you’ll see shortly), and the other became my favorite match of the episode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-10-13/NXT.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;nxt&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That match was the main event between Josh Briggs &amp;amp; Brooks Jensen and Gallus members Mark Coffey &amp;amp; Wolfgang in a Pub Rules match. This match was a street fight that was made to look like both teams were in a bar, with kegs at the entryway and a standing table with a mug and glasses among other items that both teams used as weapons. Many shows love to have no-DQ matches as main events, and this no-DQ match didn’t disappoint me one bit; this battle between two teams of heavy hitters definitely ended this week’s episode on a high note.
Here are the NXT results from Orlando…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-mandy-rose-w-gigi-dolin-and-jacy-jayne-defeated-fallon-henley-in-a-non-title-match&quot;&gt;Match #1: Mandy Rose (w/ Gigi Dolin and Jacy Jayne) defeated Fallon Henley in a non-title match.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fallon didn’t have Josh Briggs &amp;amp; Brooks Jensen at ringside because they brawled with Gallus backstage. Mandy won with the Kiss By the Rose. After the match, Mandy said that she knows that Alba Fyre was jealous of her unifying both the NXT Women’s Championship and NXT UK Women’s Championship at Worlds Collide until Alba appeared on the screen; Alba said that she’s more of a visual woman before setting a message on fire—reading “#ANDNEW”—on the ground. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-wes-lee-w-quinn-the-king-crusher-molitor-defeated-tony-dangelo-w-stacks-by-referee-stoppage-to-qualify-for-the-nxt-north-american-championship-match-at-halloween-havoc&quot;&gt;Match #2: Wes Lee (w/ Quinn “The King Crusher” Molitor) defeated Tony D’Angelo (w/ Stacks) by referee stoppage to qualify for the NXT North American Championship match at Halloween Havoc.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Molitor is a Connor’s Cure patient. Also, Carmelo Hayes and Trick Williams watched the match backstage. During the match, Stacks blocked Lee’s attempt of hitting D’Angelo with a tope until Lee hit him with the dive; this made Stacks livid and refusing to calm down for D’Angelo, and then trip Lee at ringside before being ejected to the back. The match came to a screeching halt after Lee hit D’Angelo with a drop toehold into a corner, and then D’Angelo being unable to get up with a leg injury; Lee, who looked concerned, ended up as the winner. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-3-sol-ruca-defeated-amari-miller-in-almost-five-minutes-with-a-flipping-boom-drop-ala-kofi-kingston&quot;&gt;Match #3: Sol Ruca defeated Amari Miller in almost five minutes with a flipping Boom Drop (ala Kofi Kingston).&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both women shook hands and hugged afterwards. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-4-joe-gacy-w-the-dyad-defeated-cameron-grimes-in-three-minutes&quot;&gt;Match #4: Joe Gacy (w/ the Dyad) defeated Cameron Grimes in three minutes.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the match, Jagger Reid and Rip Fowler blocked Grimes from diving onto Gacy at ringside, but he jumped over the two and dove onto his opponent with a cannonball anyway. The match ended with Fowler getting on the apron and Grimes knocking him off before Reid clipped him, and then Gacy winning with the handspring clothesline (now known as the Upside-Down World). &lt;strong&gt;My score: 0.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-5-nikkita-lyons-w-zoey-stark-defeated-kayden-carter-w-katana-chance-in-almost-five-minutes-with-a-jumping-heel-kick-followed-by-a-leg-split-leg-drop&quot;&gt;Match #5: Nikkita Lyons (w/ Zoey Stark) defeated Kayden Carter (w/ Katana Chance) in almost five minutes with a jumping heel kick followed by a leg split leg drop.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My score: 2/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-6-ilja-dragunov-defeated-xyon-quinn-in-almost-five-minutes-with-the-torpedo&quot;&gt;Match #6: Ilja Dragunov defeated Xyon Quinn in almost five minutes with the Torpedo.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My score: 1.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-7-brutus-creed-defeated-damon-kemp-by-disqualification-in-three-minutes&quot;&gt;Match #7: Brutus Creed defeated Damon Kemp by disqualification in three minutes.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Creed fought Kemp at the entryway and into the ring before the match began. Creed fought Kemp out of the ring until Kemp grabbed a steel chair and hit him with it, giving Creed a win by DQ. Kemp continued to attack Creed with the chair afterwards until referees separated the two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-josh-briggs--brooks-jensen-defeated-mark-coffey--wolfgang-in-a-pub-rules-match&quot;&gt;Main event: Josh Briggs &amp;amp; Brooks Jensen defeated Mark Coffey &amp;amp; Wolfgang in a Pub Rules match.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Briggs came into the ring with a bull rope. Trashcans, trashcan lids, tables, chairs, Briggs and Jensen’s belts, and beer glasses were also used as weapons in this bout. Towards the end, Briggs and Jensen put Mark in a trashcan, and then saw Joe Coffey appear until the two knocked him off and through a table at ringside. Then, Wolfgang charged at the two until he was tossed into another table that was set up in a corner. Finally, the two hit Mark—who was still in the trashcan—with a clothesline/chop block combo for the win.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the match, Briggs and Jensen celebrated their win with Fallon Henley while security was backing Gallus away; one guard got knocked down, and the referees came to do the same thing until one referee was knocked down. Then, police came and had all three members of Gallus handcuffed and escorted out of the arena. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;nxt-lvl-up&quot;&gt;NXT: LVL UP&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Staying in Orlando, we wrap things up with NXT: LVL UP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was afraid that this week’s episode was going to be like the last two episodes I watched (and made me fear that it was going to be like the Philadelphia Phillies struggling in the final handful of games and trying to qualify to be in the MLB postseason tournament), but I was proven wrong as soon as I saw the episode get better match wise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-10-13/NXT_LVL_UP.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;nxt_lvl_up&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Out of the three matches that took place, the tag team main event was my favorite; it was the team of Malik Blade &amp;amp; Edris Enofé, who is building a winning streak on NXT: LVL UP, taking on Guru Raaj &amp;amp; Ikemen Jiro. Just like Blade and Enofé who have been on a roll as of late, this new team of Raaj and Jiro also showed tag team chemistry as well as ways to metaphorically cut the ring in half. In the end, it was Blade and Enofé chalking up another win.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the NXT: LVL UP results from Orlando…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-javier-bernal-defeated-ru-feng&quot;&gt;Match #1: Javier Bernal defeated Ru Feng.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After suplexing and kicking Bernal, Feng ended up crashing into a corner, leading to Bernal winning with a jumping flatliner. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-thea-hail-w-andre-chase-and-bodhi-hayward-defeated-valentina-feroz-in-four-and-a-half-minutes&quot;&gt;Match #2: Thea Hail (w/ Andre Chase and Bodhi Hayward) defeated Valentina Feroz in four and a half minutes.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Valentina countered Thea’s discus punch with a spear for two, then put her in a sleeper hold until Thea turned it into a rollup for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-malik-blade--edris-enofé-defeated-guru-raaj--ikemen-jiro&quot;&gt;Main event: Malik Blade &amp;amp; Edris Enofé defeated Guru Raaj &amp;amp; Ikemen Jiro.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jiro hit Enofé with a Swanton for two, then went for the Ikemen Slash, but missed; Blade tagged in and he and Enofé hit Jiro with a Samoan drop/neckbreaker combo (now known as the Climax) for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;next-time&quot;&gt;Next time…&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Again, my currently usual trifecta of shows and probably one or two belated recaps…as well as a bonus!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For my newsletters as well as any articles that are on the Wrestling With Johners website, the website is wrestlingwithjohners.com/articles&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For just my newsletters along on the WWJ website, it is wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/pro-darin/&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading! Feel free to comment! I’ll see you next time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Photos shown in the newsletter are from WWE, Progress and ICW.)&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>pro-darin</name></author><category term="articles" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Issue 40 Shows of October 1-7, 2022</title><link href="/articles/Issue-40-Shows-of-October-1-7,-2022/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Issue 40 Shows of October 1-7, 2022" /><published>2022-10-13T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-10-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/Issue%2040%20Shows%20of%20October%201-7,%202022</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/Issue-40-Shows-of-October-1-7,-2022/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png&quot; alt=&quot;pro darin&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;pro-wrestling-noah-grand-ship-2022&quot;&gt;Pro Wrestling Noah Grand Ship 2022&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s kick off the 40th issue (yep, you read correctly!) of Pro-Darin with a bonus, shall we?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bonus event I chose for this issue is Pro Wrestling Noah Grand Ship 2022; I watched this event days before we lost Japanese pro wrestler, martial artist, politician and New Japan Pro Wrestling founder Antonio Inoki, and also days before our very own Johners went to see New Japan Pro Wrestling’s Royal Quest II in his home country of the United Kingdom. (P.S.: I’m glad to see that he had fun that night including praising the tag team main event in night 1, FTR vs. Aussie Open for the IWGP Tag Team Championship.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-10-13/pro_wrestling_noah.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;pro_wrestling_noah&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grand Ship 2022 took place on September 25, 2022 at the AICHI Dolphins Arena in Nagoya, Japan; it was shown on Wrestling Universe and Fite TV. On the card that day were ten matches; four of them had GHC titles on the line. One of the wrestlers taking part of this event was Keiji Muto, best known as the Great Muta; on June 12, 2022 at Pro Wrestling Noah’s CyberFight Festival 2022, he announced that he was retiring in 2023. Part of his retirement tour are five matches; this match, his second on that tour, was a tag team match that took place at Grand Ship 2022. Muto is expected to retire on February 21, 2023 at the Tokyo Dome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Out of the matches that didn’t have gold on the line, my favorite match would go to the tag team match that I mentioned just now; in this match, Keiji Muto teamed with Kazuyuki Fujita to take on Katsuhiko Nakajima and Masakatsu Funaki. Even though this was one of the final five matches Muto participated in, Muto showed his opponents what he’s capable of; you could definitely tell—metaphorically—how much gas he had in his tank that day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for the championship matches, my favorite of the four that took place—and also my favorite of Grand Ship 2022—would go to the GHC Heavyweight Championship bout that served as the main event; in this match, Kenoh defended the belt against the “Supernova” Kaito Kiyomiya. The storyline in this match was Kiyomiya getting sick and tired of struggling to win that title, and was proving himself—and to the fans—that he could defeat Kenoh for it. This main event from start to finish didn’t disappoint me one bit, and they definitely gave each other hell—tooth and nail—with gold on the line.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the match results from Nagoya…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-manabu-soya-defeated-taishi-ozawa&quot;&gt;Match #1: Manabu Soya defeated Taishi Ozawa.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Soya is a member of the group Kongo. Soya won after making Ozawa, who was pulled away from the ropes, submit to a Boston crab. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-eita--nosawa-rongai-defeated-kai-fujimura--yasutaka-yano-in-four-minutes&quot;&gt;Match #2: Eita &amp;amp; Nosawa Rongai defeated Kai Fujimura &amp;amp; Yasutaka Yano in four minutes.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eita and Rongai are members of Perros del Mal de Japon; they came to the ring with the Perros del Mal merchandise (a shirt, a towel and a tote bag to be more specific). Rongai offered a handshake until Fujimura and Yano dropkicked him and Eita seconds before the bell rang. The team of Eita and Rongai came back and won after a camel clutch/sliding dropkick combo to Fujimura. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-3-yoshiki-inamura--masa-kitamiya-defeated-the-funky-express&quot;&gt;Match #3: Yoshiki Inamura &amp;amp; Masa Kitamiya defeated the Funky Express.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inamura and Kitamiya are members of the Tough. Funky Express consists of Akitoshi Saito and Mohammed Yone, or “Aki” and Yone for short). The Tough members won after Inamura hit Yone with the Muso uranage. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-4-alejandro-xtreme-tiger--ninja-mack-defeated-hiroki-ohara--tadasuke-by-disqualification&quot;&gt;Match #4: Alejandro, Xtreme Tiger &amp;amp; Ninja Mack defeated Hiroki, Ohara &amp;amp; Tadasuke by disqualification.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hiroki (a.k.a. “Hi69”), Ohara and Tadasuke are members of Kongo. Also, this was Ninja Mack’s return to Pro Wrestling Noah. Towards the end, Xtreme Tiger hit the Kongo members Hiroki and Ohara with a springboard corkscrew moonsault, and then Mack hit the two with the Ninja Special. Back in the ring, Alejandro and Tadasuke went at it until Tadasuke unmasked him, giving Alejandro and his teammates the win by DQ. After the match, Tadasuke gave Alejandro back his mask until Alejandro—with his tag team partners in tow—chased him to the back. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.25/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-5-jack-morris-hijo-del-dr-wagner-jr--naomichi-marufuji-defeated-daiki-inaba-masaaki-mochizuki--masato-tanaka&quot;&gt;Match #5: Jack Morris, Hijo del Dr. Wagner Jr. &amp;amp; Naomichi Marufuji defeated Daiki Inaba, Masaaki Mochizuki &amp;amp; Masato Tanaka.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inaba, Mochizuki and Tanaka are members of Zero 1. Also, for those of you that follow ICW of Scotland like I do, Morris is indeed the same wrestler that serves as ½ of the Nine9. (Speaking of the Nine9, I wonder where Dickie Divers is nowadays…) With Hijo del Dr. Wagner Jr. and Marufuji dealing with Mochizuki and Tanaka at ringside, Morris hit Inaba with a Bryan Danielson knee followed by a falcon arrow for two before winning with a shooting star press. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-6-seiki-yoshioka--atsushi-kotoge-defeated-chris-ridgeway--yoshinari-ogawa-to-become-the-new-ghc-junior-heavyweight-tag-team-champions&quot;&gt;Match #6: Seiki Yoshioka &amp;amp; Atsushi Kotoge defeated Chris Ridgeway &amp;amp; Yoshinari Ogawa to become the new GHC Junior Heavyweight Tag Team Champions.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ridgeway had taped ribs, probably due to his match with Big Damo at Progress Chapter 137 that took place one month prior. The Stinger members went after Yoshioka and Kotoge seconds before the bell rang until the challengers fought back. Kotoge’s left arm was worked on, ditto Yoshioka’s left leg during the match. Also, after Ridgeway hit Kotoge with a brainbuster for two followed by a running punt to the chest for another two, both men traded strikes until Ridgeway got the upper hand; Kotoge popped up and hit him with a headbutt before Ridgeway responded back with a punt, and the two ended up in a bloody mess (with Kotoge getting the worst of it) due to the headbutt. Towards the end, Ogawa put Yoshioka in a reverse half crab (known as the Ridgeway Clutch) and then put him in a Figure Four until Yoshioka was able to get out of it; Yoshioka then fought back before winning with a buzzsaw kick. After the match, Yoshioka and Kotoge celebrated their victory until Tadasuke and Hiroki ran in and blindsided the new champions, with Tadasuke hitting Kotoge with a steel chair (that would break after one or two chair shots) and Hiroki working on Yoshioka’s leg; the Kongo members then vowed to defeat Yoshioka and Kotoge for the belts. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-7-satoshi-kojima--takashi-sugiura-defeated-timothy-thatcher--hideki-suzuki-to-become-the-new-ghc-tag-team-champions&quot;&gt;Match #7: Satoshi Kojima &amp;amp; Takashi Sugiura defeated Timothy Thatcher &amp;amp; Hideki Suzuki to become the new GHC Tag Team Champions.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thatcher and Suzuki came to the ring with the same theme song used by Die Familie on NXT UK (except it was played at a slow pace unlike the original Die Familie theme). During the match, Kojima went for the Western Lariat but missed and ended up getting his right arm worked on. Also, Sugiura accidentally booted his tag team partner instead of Thatcher even though he was able to hit the other opponent Suzuki minutes later. The end of the match saw Kojima hitting Thatcher with the Western Lariat and then hit Suzuki with a brainbuster followed by the Western Lariat, then Sugiura hitting Suzuki with an Olympic slam for the win. After the match, Suzuki beat down a crewman while heading to the back. Then, Kojima said “We did it” before shaking Sugiura’s hand (instead of giving him a finger shake like he did before the match began) and then telling the “assholes” on the roster that they’re a dangerous tag team. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-8-hayata-defeated-yo-hey-to-retain-the-ghc-junior-heavyweight-championship&quot;&gt;Match #8: Hayata defeated Yo-Hey to retain the GHC Junior Heavyweight Championship.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the match, Yo-Hey went for a Meteora from the apron until Hayata countered with a powerbomb on the floor; Hayata came back in at 13, ditto Yo-Hey at 19. Yo-Hey hit Hayata with the Gamengin (running double knees) for two, and then a Codebreaker and second Gamengin for another two until Hayata came back with the 403 Impact (jumping lifting DDT) for two. After Yo-Hey came back with a top rope Gamengin for another two, Hayata fought back and won with the Headache. After the match, Ninja Mack came into the ring and told Hayata to hold the belt tight, challenging him for the title. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4.25/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-9-kazuyuki-fujiya--keiji-muto-defeated-katsuhiko-nakajima--masakatsu-funaki&quot;&gt;Match #9: Kazuyuki Fujiya &amp;amp; Keiji Muto defeated Katsuhiko Nakajima &amp;amp; Masakatsu Funaki.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nakajima and Funaki are members of Kongo. A double Figure Four was done by Fujiya and Muto during the match until their opponents were able to get out of the holds. Also, near the end, Nakajima hit Muto with—one of Muto’s maneuvers—the Space Rolling Elbow until Muto came back and won with a shining wizard. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4.25/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-kaito-kiyomiya-defeated-kenoh-to-become-the-new-ghc-heavyweight-champion&quot;&gt;Main event: Kaito Kiyomiya defeated Kenoh to become the new GHC Heavyweight Champion.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kenoh is a member of Kongo. (P.S.: Did any of you get tired after seeing me mention who is in Kongo yet? Just asking…lol…) After Kenoh hit Kiyomita with a dragon superplex followed by the PFS (or Coup de Grace if your name is Finn Bálor) for a near fall, Kiyomita came back and won with two shining wizards. After the match, Kiyomita thanked the fans and then challenged Kazuyuki Fujita to a match for the belt. Fujita, who was drinking a can of beer, came into the ring and Kiyomiya raised his title in front of him until Fujita hugged him and then jokingly poured beer on his head; Kiyomiya took offense and punched Fujita, then as Fujita left, the champion said that he didn’t like beer despite still issuing a challenge to Fujita. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;progress-chapter-139-warriors-come-out-to-play&quot;&gt;Progress Chapter 139: Warriors Come Out To Play&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-10-13/warriors.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;progress_warriors&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, onto a belated recap…and no, I didn’t need to go to a search engine for the chapter title. The dead giveaway…I still remember watching “The Warriors” on TNT back when I was in my early double-digit years, and it is indeed a damn good movie if you like action packed thriller films like this. (Yes, you read correctly…it was on TNT that night I watched it; the f-bombs and the word “shit” were edited out if I remember correctly.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, this chapter of Progress took place at the Electric Ballroom in London, England in the United Kingdom on August 28, 2022. All four Progress championship belts were on the line that day, and there were also four exhibition matches—including one involving a straitjacket—that occurred.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I enjoyed three of the nine matches that took place that day. The opener was one of the three matches, and it was for the Progress Atlas Championship. This championship match, between Jacobs and Dereiss, was scheduled to take place two chapters ago until Mark Davis of Aussie Power was added to the bout. Just like the three-way dance for that belt, this match for the Atlas Championship was a great battle as well. Both wrestlers came close to picking up the win and title even while going back and forth with their signature maneuvers from Jacobs’ Burning Lariat to Dereiss’ Four Fiddy; in the end, it was the North West Strong member Jacobs who retained the belt. Both Jacobs and Dereiss did indeed have a good battle not just in the three-way dance, but also in this one-on-one bout.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second of the three matches I enjoyed involved wXw wrestler Maggot and, returning to Progress after his time in the now defunct NXT UK, Eddie Dennis. After being away from pro wrestling for approximately a month, Dennis returned to action as well as Progress where he was the Progress World Champion in the past before relinquishing the belt due to injury. Dennis showed his opponent Maggot what he’s still capable of, as did Maggot that day; in the end, it was the returning Dennis who emerged victorious. I definitely look forward to seeing what else Dennis has in store for Progress now that he’s back in the company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The third of the three matches that I enjoyed was what would have been the main event (and you’ll see why I said “would have been” in the results shortly). This match saw Big Damo defending the Progress World Championship against Dan Moloney of the 0121, and it was indeed a great battle between the two heavy hitters with gold on the line. The title didn’t change hands in this bout however, mainly because of the match’s ending that had the fans ticked off. Regardless of the result, I still enjoyed that championship match.
Here are the match results from London…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-luke-jacobs-defeated-man-like-dereiss-to-retain-the-progress-atlas-championship&quot;&gt;Match #1: Luke Jacobs defeated Man Like Dereiss to retain the Progress Atlas Championship.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both shook hands as the match began. After dodging a Four Fiddy from Dereiss, Jacobs hit him with the Burning Lariat for two, and then put him in a sleeper until Dereiss bridged him for two. The back-and-forth bout continued with Dereiss hitting Jacobs with a powerbomb and a Four Fiddy for back-to-back two counts until the action spilled out of the ring near the end of the match; Jacobs hit him with a Death Valley driver into the chairs, then hit him with a coast-to-coast dropkick and a second Burning Lariat for two before winning by making him submit to a sleeper. After the match, Jacobs helped up Dereiss and hugged him. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4.25/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-tate-mayfairs-defeated-gene-munny&quot;&gt;Match #2: Tate Mayfairs defeated Gene Munny.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mayfairs coerced Simon Miller to introduce him as “The greatest professional wrestler ever to walk planet Earth.” Early in the match, Munny did a victory lap—even with his Gene Munny Championship belt in his hands—and posed on the top rope until Mayfairs shoved him off and into the ring crew at ringside. Later on, Munny hit Mayfairs with the James Blunt Force Trauma (sit out powerbomb) for two, and then his opponent got out of the ring before the Ainsley Lariat was attempted, leading to Munny hitting him with a tope into the chairs followed by a Cactus Jack elbow drop from the apron while Mayfairs was laying on a couple chairs at ringside. Suddenly, as soon as both wrestlers were back in the ring, an SMPTE color bar test card appeared on the screen until Matt Cardona appeared on the screen as well, challenging Munny—who was setting up Mayfairs for the Ainsley Lariat—to a match; as soon as Cardona was no longer on the screen, Mayfairs missed on attempting to hit Munny with brass knuckles, then—behind the referee’s back—hit Munny with his own title for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-3-lana-austin-defeated-raven-creed-in-a-straitjacket-match&quot;&gt;Match #3: Lana Austin defeated Raven Creed in a straitjacket match.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The only way to win was to put the opponent in a straitjacket and strap it closed. Before the match started, Simon Miller announced that Lana was “unavailable” until Raven decided to look for her backstage; Raven, after asking Jayde where Lana was, then left the venue and found her at a sushi bar before attacking and chasing her back into the Electric Ballroom. (Plus, we learned that Raven isn’t a fan of sushi as she came back with a plate with it and didn’t like it after taking one piece of it…lol…) Raven followed Lana outside as well as under the ring early in the match, and then after beating her down, she grabbed the straitjacket (from a mannequin that read “DIE LANA DIE” on the torso) until Lana hotshot her on the top rope before fighting back. Both women fought with the straitjacket until Raven headbutted Lana after a tug-of-war with it and then hit her with the Hellbound and put her in a sleeper; she then grabbed the straitjacket until all of the sudden, Skye Smitson ran in and attacked Raven before putting the jacket on her and having Lana finish the job for the win. Afterwards, Lana told Jayde—who interviewed her—that Skye is a member of “The Lana Austin Experience.” &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-4-eddie-dennis-defeated-maggot&quot;&gt;Match #4: Eddie Dennis defeated Maggot.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those of you that watched it on Peacock or WWE Network (or for those of you that live in Australia, Binge come 2023), Dennis’ theme song—“Party Hard” by Andrew W.K.—was replaced with the FSU theme. After Maggot countered the Gunslinger (sit out sidewalk slam) with the Crucifixion for two and then hit Dennis with a snap suplex and spear for another two, he went for a top rope crossbody—after a pendulum kick—until Dennis countered with the Gunslinger for a near fall of his own. Then, Maggot and Dennis exchanged rollups after Dennis went for the Severed Bridge until Dennis was able to hit him with the Severed Bridge before winning with the Neckstop Driver (lifting reverse DDT). Post-match, Dennis said that he planned to come back “in this [f-bombing] room” and wrestle someone making a name for himself such as Maggot, and then vowed to win back—what he relinquished due to injury a couple years ago—the Progress World Championship. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4.25/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-5-the-sunshine-machine-defeated-danny-black--joe-lando-to-retain-the-progress-tag-team-championship&quot;&gt;Match #5: The Sunshine Machine defeated Danny Black &amp;amp; Joe Lando to retain the Progress Tag Team Championship.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the match, TK Cooper attempted to punch Lando until Black distracted him; Cooper then went for a sunset flip powerbomb from the apron until Chuck Mambo flipped Cooper back to the apron, leading to Cooper hitting the CPF member with a reverse piledriver on the apron. The end of the match saw Mambo hit Black with a springboard crossbody into the chairs at ringside before coming back into the ring where he and Mambo hit Lando with Captain Midnight’s Revenge for the win. Post-match, Lykos Gym talked about defeating the Greedy Souls for a shot at the tag team belts and then defeating the Sunshine Machine for those titles until the tag team champions appeared; Mambo and Cooper were talking about their win until Kid Lykos spat water in his face, with Mambo trying to settle him down after telling Lykos that it was uncalled for. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.75/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-6-anthony-ogogo-defeated-callum-newman&quot;&gt;Match #6: Anthony Ogogo defeated Callum Newman.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the match, Newman booted Ogogo into a chair until Ogogo hit him with a back body drop into the chairs in the crowd; Newman would dart back into the ring at nine afterwards. Then, after Newman powered out of a triangle choke with a powerbomb, Ogogo won with the Tower of London. After the match, Ogogo shook hands and hugged Newman before his arm was raised, and the Kosta Konstantino came into the ring and talked about working with him in the past before Ogogo became a “disrespectful piece of shit”; Konstantino said that Ogogo was a “rookie” instead of “the guv’nor” in pro wrestling like in boxing until Ogogo started poking fun of him for working for his father’s chip factory. Ogogo then said that he was looking forward to fighting Malik until Konstantino told him to get a box to lie next to his dead father; this made Ogogo furious and go after Konstantino until Malik blindsided him and beat him down prior to the two placing the Union Jack on Ogogo and leaving. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-7-kanji-defeated-laura-di-matteo-to-retain-the-progress-womens-championship&quot;&gt;Match #7: Kanji defeated Laura di Matteo to retain the Progress Women’s Championship.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If Kanji lost by disqualification, Laura would become the new champion. Laura blindsided Kanji before the match until the ring crew separated the two; both women continued to fight at ringside before getting back in the ring. The two wrestlers were then held by the ring crew as Simon Miller did the intros, and then got the hell out of dodge as the two went at it a second after the bell rang. Laura tried to get Kanji DQ’d on purpose including using the referee as a shield as Kanji charged at her. Near the end, Laura countered a slingshot spear with a super kick before hitting her with a swinging neckbreaker for two, and then got out of the ring and threw six steel chairs into the ring (including those she stole from fans). Kanji attempted to hit her with a running leg drop until she noticed that Laura tried to get her DQ’d with one of the chairs; Laura then attempted to hit Kanji with the chair until Kanji took it away from her, thought about hitting her with it, and then threw it down. Then, Laura went for a backslide until Kanji countered with a full nelson before bridging it, elbowing her down, and making her submit to a triangle choke. After the match, Laura took the title away from the referee, but then approached Kanji, whispered something in her ear, and gave the title back before heading to the back. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-8-dan-moloney-defeated-big-damo-by-disqualification-damo-retained-the-progress-world-championship&quot;&gt;Match #8: Dan Moloney defeated Big Damo by disqualification; Damo retained the Progress World Championship.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both bumped fists before the match. As soon as the bell rang, Moloney hit Damo with a spear for two until the action spilled out of the ring; Damo came back and stood on Moloney like a surfboard before hitting him with a senton on the floor. Later on, Moloney hit Damo with a deadlift slam followed by a German suplex for two. Towards the end, after Damo hit Moloney with a uranage from the apron followed by a hilo for two, Moloney made a comeback until Damo hit him with a clothesline, Wasteland, a senton and the Belfast Blitz for a near fall; Moloney came back with a second spear followed by the Drilla until all of the sudden, Spike Trivet ran in and hit Moloney in the head with a bottle, giving the “Drilla” a win by DQ. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4.25/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-spike-trivet-defeated-big-damo-in-five-seconds-to-become-the-new-progress-world-champion&quot;&gt;Main event: Spike Trivet defeated Big Damo in five seconds to become the new Progress World Champion.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After attacking Moloney, Trivet beat down Damo with a steel chair several times and then used his key to open the championship opportunity. Then, as soon as the bell rang, Trivet pinned Damo for the win; he would then taunt the irate fans at ringside before leaving with the belt afterwards. &lt;em&gt;*No score.&lt;/em&gt;8&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;icw-fight-club&quot;&gt;ICW Fight Club&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, onto my currently usual three, starting things off by going to the GPWA—now known simply as “The Asylum”—in Glasgow, Scotland for ICW Fight Club.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only did the buildup to Fear &amp;amp; Loathing XIV occur this week, but so did the fallout from Shug’s Hoose Party 7. This week’s episode began with Dylan Thorn coming from the crowd and into the ring, demanding answers from the Manifesto’s leader ADM. ADM came into the ring and Thorn asked him why he attacked him after losing to Daz Black at SHP7, and ADM said that he was tired of seeing Thorn fail again and again until Thorn noted other “failures” that the Manifesto had in matches such as one-on-one matches with Che Monet and Jack Jester prior to that event before ADM blamed Thorn for embarrassing the Manifesto. Thorn then talked about what happened during his match with Black at SHP7 including what Black did when the rest of the Manifesto interfered and then said that Black deserved the win until ADM called Thorn “pathetic” before getting under his skin by—comparing himself to Thorn’s deceased father—saying “I want nothing to do with you.” I got a feeling that Thorn, who appears to be no longer part of the Manifesto, will be reaching his breaking point by fighting the team’s leader ADM at Fear &amp;amp; Loathing XIV in November; I have to admit, the Manifesto has been a force to be reckoned with even before ending up with a handful of losses heading into SHP7, but if Thorn vs. ADM does indeed occur at F&amp;amp;L XIV, then I could expect the other members—Grant McIvor and Eddie Castle—take part of this bout whether it helps ADM more than Thorn or vice versa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back to F&amp;amp;L XIV, we saw that there is another match that has been made for that event. After Chris Bungard rescued Levi from getting beaten down by Aaron Echo, we learned there will be a match between the mixed martial artist/wrestler Bungard and ICW veteran Echo at that event in November. Before he does so, Bungard will face Theo Doros next week on an episode of ICW Fight Club. I believe giving Bungard some matches—including one against Doros—prior to F&amp;amp;L XIV is indeed a good thing, mainly because it helps build his pro wrestling skills even with any plans of using his MMA-related fighting abilities in his bouts; this looks like something WWE should take notes on before having Logan Paul fight Roman Reigns for the Undisputed WWE Universal Championship at Crown Jewel (even though Paul was impressive in his first two matches per se). That’s just my opinion, so…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-10-13/icw_fight_club2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;icw_fight_club&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Me being opinionated (and probably biased as well) aside, we saw three matches on this week’s episode of Fight Club. My favorite of the three would go to the Zero-G Championship match between Daz Black and Sheikh El Sham. With size and strength coming into play, El Sham showed Black what he had in store even before Black made a comeback and won. Black is so far having a good run as a champion, and El Sham is indeed proving to us that he can be championship worthy even after coming close to winning that belt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the match results from Glasgow…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-angel-hayze-defeated-lana-austin-lana-is-nowadays-like-on-progress-since-late-2021-competing-as-a-heel&quot;&gt;Match #1: Angel Hayze defeated Lana Austin. Lana is nowadays, like on Progress since late 2021, competing as a heel.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As soon as the match began, Angel offered Lana a handshake until Lana slapped it away. Both wrestlers fought into the audience, including Lana slapping a drink out of a fan’s hand and Angel punching her opponent into the seats and fans. Near the end, Angel hit Lana with a superkick and then put her in a guillotine until Lana backed her into a corner and—after kicked her off the top tope—came back with a Codebreaker for two. Lana then went for a discus forearm, but Angel dodged it and won with a bridging La Magistral. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-andy-wild-defeated-coach-trip-w-jason-reed&quot;&gt;Match #2: Andy Wild defeated Coach Trip (w/ Jason Reed).&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before the match started, Wild went after Trip until Reed joined in the battle; Reed even attacked Wild with a steel chair, giving Trip the upper hand before the bell rang. Reed also helped Trip who had Wild in an abdominal stretch until the referee caught him; Reed attempted to interfere again until he was ejected from ringside. Trip begged for mercy and then went for a low blow until Wild blocked the attempt prior to hitting the coach with a clothesline and the Dad Bomb for the win. Afterwards, Reed and Trip attempted to escape through the crowd until Wild blamed Reed for riding the coach’s coattails while wrestling and not having a connection with fans; Wild then said that it will be 2 vs. 1 with fans before telling Reed and Trip “We’re going to [f-bomb] you up at Fear &amp;amp; Loathing!” &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-daz-black-defeated-sheikh-el-sham-to-retain-the-icw-zero-g-championship&quot;&gt;Main event: Daz Black defeated Sheikh El Sham to retain the ICW Zero-G Championship.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both bumped fists before the match began. After Black missed with a moonsault, El Sham hit him with a spear for a near fall, and then had him in a camel clutch until Black backed him into a corner. Black came back with a shining wizard-like kick followed by the Curbstomp for the win afterwards. After the match, El Sham looked like he was going to attack Black, but instead he shook hands with the champion. Then, Theo Doros appeared and said that despite Black epitomizing the Zero-G division, he vowed to win the title at Fear &amp;amp; Loathing XIV and change the Zero-G division. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 4.25/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;nxt&quot;&gt;NXT&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We now head to Orlando, Florida in the United States for an episode of NXT.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-10-13/NXT2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;nxt&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NXT has been rebranded once again. This rebrand looks like a cross between the NXT of the black-and-gold era and the NXT of the short-lived multicolored “2.0” era. Besides keeping the same décor used for the last era, the black wrestling mat was brought back and also had black barricades covering up the glass barricades that were used for a year. Like I said, it looks like two past eras wrapped into one; I might call it either the white-and-gold brand or the black, white and gold brand mainly because of the changes made to the logo as well as the arena, but on the other hand, I’m definitely looking forward to what else this new era of NXT has in store.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two more matches were made for Halloween Havoc. One was the long-awaited rematch between friends turned enemies Cora Jade and Roxanne Perez. This match was announced on an episode of a new show “The Grayson Waller Effect” where Waller had both wrestlers as his guests. Roxanne vowed to come into the match without emotions instead of mixed emotions like the last time she did before fighting Cora who claimed that her opponent was telling a “sob story” and said that she’s nothing but “internet hype”; Cora then said that she tried to be nice to the fans before “The Generation of Jade” was born until Roxanne said that no one bought Cora’s “nice girl act” and said that she was “full of shit.” Waller then added a stipulation to their match with the Halloween Havoc wheel; as soon as he spun the wheel, it landed on “Weapons wild match.” That is indeed one way of having the two women clash once again, especially for an event such as Halloween Havoc; I look forward to seeing what they have in store including Roxanne promising to go after Cora without a single iota of emotion. By the way, shouldn’t the wheel be used during Halloween Havoc instead of before? Maybe they’ll use it for other matches that may be added to that event come in a few weeks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other match made for Halloween Havoc was Julius Creed taking on Damon Kemp. After Kemp battered and bruised Brutus Creed with a steel chair last week, Julius vowed to go after the now former Diamond Mine member even with Brutus wanting to go after the turncoat. Kemp decided to challenge Julius to a match at Halloween Havoc, and Julius made it an ambulance match. Kemp then added a stipulation to that bout. If Julius wins, Brutus will have his rematch against Kemp; if Kemp wins, Brutus is gone from NXT. I have been a fan of Diamond Mine as of late, especially the Creed Brothers and I doubt that we’ll see Kemp have one Creed stay and the other part ways with the NXT roster.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seven matches took place, with two tag team matches that were better than the rest that were—once again—short lived including one that lasted for less than a minute. Not only was the main event tag team match between—from SmackDown—Ridge Holland &amp;amp; Butch of the Brawling Brutes and Pretty Deadly for the NXT Tag Team Championship, but so was the women’s tag team match that took place in the middle of the episode; the women’s tag team match ended up being my favorite match of the episode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this tag team bout, we saw the team of Nikkita Lyons and Zoey Stark take on Toxic Attraction members Gigi Dolin and Jacy Jayne; the winning team would become #1 contenders for the NXT Women’s Tag Team Championship. Originally, this match was supposed to be a six-woman tag team match with Alba Fyre together with Nikkita and Zoey taking on all three members of Toxic Attraction until the match was changed courtesy of Alba as you’ll see shortly. Even though it was a last-minute change that occurred prior to the episode taking place, it still a good tag team bout that involved the wrestlers in NXT’s women’s division; in the end, it was Nikkita and Zoey that was victorious, and even though this team is fairly new, you can tell that those two women work like a well-oiled machine, chemistry and all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the NXT results from Orlando…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-carmelo-hayes-w-trick-williams-defeated-oro-mensah&quot;&gt;Match #1: Carmelo Hayes (w/ Trick Williams) defeated Oro Mensah.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Near the end, Williams—who distracted Mensah during the bout—pulled Hayes out of the way before being hit by Mensah’s running heel kick in the corner; this led to Hayes hitting Mensah with a Codebreaker followed by the Nothing But Net for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-von-wagner-w-mr-stone-defeated-andre-chase-w-bodhi-hayward-and-thea-hail-in-three-and-a-half-minutes-to-qualify-for-the-nxt-north-american-championship-ladder-match-at-halloween-havoc&quot;&gt;Match #2: Von Wagner (w/ Mr. Stone) defeated Andre Chase (w/ Bodhi Hayward and Thea Hail) in three and a half minutes to qualify for the NXT North American Championship ladder match at Halloween Havoc.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Carmelo Hayes joined Sudu Shah, Byron Saxton and Wade Barrett on commentary. Mr. Stone distracted Chase until Thea picked him up on her shoulders before—after Mr. Stone threw the Chase U flag on the floor—slamming him on the floor. Then, Wagner defeated Chase with a Death Valley bomb. Suddenly, after the match, Wes Lee jumped from the crowd and attacked Hayes until two referees came and separated them. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 0.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-3-wendy-choo-defeated-lash-legend-in-almost-four-minutes&quot;&gt;Match #3: Wendy Choo defeated Lash Legend in almost four minutes.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lash fired up Wendy by throwing her own body pillow at her before the match. Wendy won after hitting Lash with a reverse splash. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 0.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-4-nikkita-lyons--zoey-stark-defeated-gigi-dolin--jacy-jayne-for-a-shot-at-the-nxt-womens-tag-team-championship&quot;&gt;Match #4: Nikkita Lyons &amp;amp; Zoey Stark defeated Gigi Dolin &amp;amp; Jacy Jayne for a shot at the NXT Women’s Tag Team Championship.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was originally scheduled to be Alba Fyre, Nikkita Lyons &amp;amp; Zoey Stark vs. Toxic Attraction until—before the episode took place—Alba attacked Gigi and Jacy in the parking lot before hightailing in Mandy Rose’s SUV; Gigi ended up with taped ribs as a result. Also, Kayden Karter &amp;amp; Katana Chance watched the match backstage. Zoey and Nikkita won after hitting Gigi with, respectively, the Z360 and a leg split leg drop. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-5-julius-creed-defeated-duke-hudson-in-52-seconds&quot;&gt;Match #5: Julius Creed defeated Duke Hudson in 52 seconds.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This match was made after Hudson taunted the Creed Brothers and Ivy Nile over Damon Kemp turning on their backs and Brutus being unable to compete due to injury. Julius won with a basement clothesline to Hudson. Post-match, Brutus ran in and attacked Hudson until Kemp appeared on the stage. Kemp vowed to defeat Julius at Halloween Havoc, and Julius made it an ambulance match; Kemp then said that Brutus will have his rematch with him if Julius wins, or else—if Kemp wins—will be kicked out of NXT. &lt;strong&gt;No score.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-6-xyon-quinn-defeated-hank-walker-in-two-minutes&quot;&gt;Match #6: Xyon Quinn defeated Hank Walker in two minutes.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Walker is using his southern rock-like theme song, that we’ve heard during his appearances on NXT: LVL UP, as his theme song once again. Quinn dodged a running boot and then won with a running jumping forearm. Post-match, Quinn attempted to attack Walker until Quincy Elliott came in and chased him out. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-pretty-deadly-defeated-ridge-holland--butch-to-retain-the-nxt-tag-team-championship&quot;&gt;Main event: Pretty Deadly defeated Ridge Holland &amp;amp; Butch to retain the NXT Tag Team Championship.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This match was made after Kit Wilson and Elton Prince in their “address of NXT commonwealth” announced that they will be champions forever due to a lack of competition until the Brawling Brutes members came and challenged them for the belts. Near the end, Pretty Deadly attempted to hit Butch with Spilled Milk until Holland clotheslined Prince out of the ring, leading to Butch putting Wilson in a cross armbreaker. Prince came back in and broke up the hold before Butch hit him with the Bitter End seconds later until Wilson put his tag team partner’s foot on the bottom rope. Then, Holland hit Wilson with Northern Grit until all of the sudden, Giovanni Vinci and Ludwig Kaiser appeared; this distraction led to Pretty Deadly winning with Spilled Milk. Afterwards, Holland and Butch fought the Imperium members out of the arena while Edris Enofé &amp;amp; Malik Blade appeared at the entryway ditto Josh Briggs &amp;amp; Brooks Jensen on the stage; both teams stared at Pretty Deadly, gesturing for shots at the belts. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 3/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;nxt-lvl-up&quot;&gt;NXT: LVL UP&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Staying in Orlando, we wrap things up with NXT: LVL UP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2022-10-13/NXT_LVL_UP2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;nxt_lvl_up&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Out of the three matches that took place this week, I enjoyed the second bout between Myles Borne and Guru Raaj. Not only was it a flashback from June of this year, but it was also a good back and forth bout between the two. It was slightly better, in my opinion, than their June encounter; in the end, it was Borne who was finally able to pick up his career first win. Besides a good showing from the two competitors, it was also good to see Borne finally chalk up a win in his WWE tenure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the NXT: LVL UP results from Orlando…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-1-indi-hartwell-defeated-sloane-jacobs-in-three-minutes&quot;&gt;Match #1: Indi Hartwell defeated Sloane Jacobs in three minutes.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After Sloane hit Indi with a middle rope crossbody, Indi won with a spinebuster. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 1.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;match-2-myles-borne-defeated-guru-raaj&quot;&gt;Match #2: Myles Borne defeated Guru Raaj.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Raaj booted Borne in a corner, and then went for a top rope maneuver until Borne caught him with a flatliner for the win. Both men shook hands afterwards. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2.5/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-event-fallon-henley--sol-ruca-defeated-kiana-james--arianna-grace&quot;&gt;Main event: Fallon Henley &amp;amp; Sol Ruca defeated Kiana James &amp;amp; Arianna Grace.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sol kicked Kiana off the apron, and Fallon hit Arianna with a shining wizard for the win. &lt;strong&gt;My score: 2/5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;next-time&quot;&gt;Next time…&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Besides my currently usual three, I will also take a look back at Extreme Rules. Plus, not yet set in stone, I might throw in a belated recap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For my newsletters as well as any articles that are on the Wrestling With Johners website, the website is wrestlingwithjohners.com/articles&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For just my newsletters along on the WWJ website, it is wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/pro-darin/&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading! Feel free to comment! I’ll see you next time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Photos shown in the newsletter are from WWE, Pro Wrestling Noah, Progress and ICW.)&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>pro-darin</name></author><category term="articles" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A top guy, getting shoutouts from the top guys! #subscribe #aew #fyp #viral #ftr #wrestling #doit</title><link href="/straight-talk-wrestling/videos/A-top-guy-getting-shoutouts-from-the-top-guys-subscribe-aew-fyp-viral-ftr-wrestling-doit/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A top guy, getting shoutouts from the top guys! #subscribe #aew #fyp #viral #ftr #wrestling #doit" /><published>2022-10-13T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-10-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/straight-talk-wrestling/videos/A%20top%20guy%20getting%20shoutouts%20from%20the%20top%20guys%20subscribe%20aew%20fyp%20viral%20ftr%20wrestling%20doit</id><content type="html" xml:base="/straight-talk-wrestling/videos/A-top-guy-getting-shoutouts-from-the-top-guys-subscribe-aew-fyp-viral-ftr-wrestling-doit/"></content><author><name>george-mckay</name></author><category term="straight-talk-wrestling" /><category term="videos" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Bucklebomb Live Presents The Chop Shop 10/10/22</title><link href="/bucklebomb-entertainment/Bucklebomb-Live-Presents-The-Chop-Shop-101022/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bucklebomb Live Presents The Chop Shop 10/10/22" /><published>2022-10-12T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-10-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/bucklebomb-entertainment/Bucklebomb%20Live%20Presents%20The%20Chop%20Shop%20101022</id><content type="html" xml:base="/bucklebomb-entertainment/Bucklebomb-Live-Presents-The-Chop-Shop-101022/"></content><author><name>bucklebomb-entertainment</name></author><category term="bucklebomb-entertainment" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>