<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-12-19T18:36:18+00:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Wrestling With Johners</title><subtitle>Pro Wrestling podcast with news, reviews and debate from WWE, NXT, NXT:UK, AEW, NJPW, Indy Wrestling and so much more. Listen to Wrestling With Johners on Apple Podcasts, Google Podcasts, Spotify, Podbean, Podcast Addict, Castbox, YouTube or wherever you get your podcasts.</subtitle><author><name>John Scott</name></author><entry><title type="html">I Have An Addiction</title><link href="/articles/I-Have-An-Addiction/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I Have An Addiction" /><published>2019-12-18T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-12-18T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/I%20Have%20An%20Addiction</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/I-Have-An-Addiction/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;ladies-and-gentlemen-my-name-is-lexi-helms-and-i-have-an-addiction&quot;&gt;Ladies and Gentlemen: My name is Lexi Helms and I have an addiction…&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This addiction is something that affects my daily habits, actions in situations and the world, drains my money, is a habit that started as a child and is something I cannot live without. Sometimes, it hangs in my wardrobe, influencing my style and sometimes causes random strangers to come and speak to me. Most recently, it has influenced my hair style and Christmas Tree decorations. My addiction can take me on the highest high and send me into a blubbering mess. It also frequents my laptop, phone, social media stream and my DVD collection - not to mention my TV. It’s something my mother hates, something I watch mainly with males and something my significant other actively encourages… Ladies and Gentlemen, my name is Lexi Helms and my addiction is pro-wrestling [tell me you did NOT read that with Paul Hayman’s voice!].&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was two when this addiction started -my brother was watching it and I became hooked. I, to this day, cannot tell you why I liked it and for a while it was all I spoke about and wanted to play. Having two brothers who actively encouraged me to be Superfly Jimmy Snuka and jump off the sofa onto one of them only deepened my love for it. At one point I wanted to BE the Ultimate Warrior at the age of 3 [and yes, I cried when he was inducted into the HOF, cried when he died and yes, I cry at documentaries because I’m still not over it!] and was not ashamed to admit it to anyone that would listen. I have stuck with it for over 29 years.  It is a sad fact to admit that in this world, it’s often rare to come across a female pro-wrestling fan. I didn’t get into it simply to look at males in skimpy outfits. Case and point: I once got into a very public argument with a girl over Randy Orton because she insisted his name was a good marketing ploy merely based on his good looks. This coming from a girl who hated wrestling before seeing Orton…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have always loved WWF - until 1996… When, by coincidence, I stumbled across a little-known programme called “Nitro”. Back in the day, Cartoon Network changed to TNT at 9pm, and as a result, Nitro was shown on a Friday night. I was hooked - because I recognised Scott Hall. It was so different to what WWF was offering at the time, and with the absence of Sky Sports in the Sky Package, WCW gave me a guaranteed 2-hour wrestling fix on a Friday night. I remember watching WCW back on ITV in ’92 / 93, but 1996 WCW was different. At one point, on a family holiday to America, I my brothers and I traded rooms to catch the episodes of RAW for Nitro, briefly filling in the blanks during ad breaks. My desire to have wrestling in my life was so great that I used to listen to episodes of Livewire on the old Sky Sports 3 because you could still get sound from the channel, despite having no picture - much to my mother’s annoyance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a Teenager, wrestling was more accessible, and I had caught a few ECW matches here or there - but my confused brain both loved and hated ECW. Part of me loved it, because it was wrestling and especially because RVD blew my mind with what he could do. Part of me hated it, because I had a genuine fear for the safety of the performers in the company. Bear in mind, we were edging towards the tail end of the Attitude Era - Hardcore wrestling in WWF was much tamer than ECW and was the only “hardcore” wrestling I had seen up until this point. I remember only briefly watching ECW mainly because, finally, both mum and I agreed that it was TOO violent. Only now, with the benefit of hindsight, and with an adult mind (to fully understand who Jenna Jameson is, for example) can I fully appreciate ECW and the utter genius that is Paul Hayman. Despite Hayman’s’ brilliance, I must admit that parts of ECW and death matches in other promotions presently still make me uncomfortable – to me, that is not the wrestling that I love, but I understand their appeal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By this point in my addiction (circa 1999), I had also stopped watching Nitro after the decision was made to end Goldbergs’ streak and fell in love with Smack Down!, After Burn and Bottom Line. This was more than enough for the wrestling fix I craved… Until the Invasion storyline. We had gone from a guaranteed 9 hours of wrestling a week (RAW, SmackDown! Nitro and Thunder) to just 4 hours of main shows. So, I again by sheer chance, I stumbled across the “Wrestling Channel” on Sky. This exposed me to the likes of AJ Styles, Christopher Daniels, Jushin Liger and Frankie Kazarian. Their work was good, and it was reassuring that I came across them in other promotions.  During this time, my brother had pointed out that you could now purchase WWF attire over in this country, and, as a result, my brother and I proudly own a Shane O’Mac Baseball shirt - still my pride and joy to this day! From this, I quickly developed a collection of Wrestling-related t-shirts that I still wear to this day:  including Stone Cold, The Rock, John Cena [bring on the hate eh?], Evolution, Batista [more heat for me!], Wade Barrett, Charlotte Flair, AJ Styles, Shinskue Nakamura, DIY, Shane McMahon, Moustache Mountain,  Eddie Gurrereo and William Regal [to name but a few!].&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once the “Invasion” angle finished, wrestling fans were introduced to the “Brand Split”, which was fantastic. The idea that only the Champion would be on both shows was intriguing, making that person feel special and the split made you choose a brand and be loyal to it. I also loved the Raw and SmackDown! Sets respectively but favoured the SmackDown! Fist and, if truth be told, I long for its return.  The storylines were engaging, and both shows pushed and developed young talent. I loved the Nitro element of SmackDown! With the Lucha Libre style and quick paced matches and the fact that RAW had the comforting reassurance of Triple H, Shawn Michaels and… Dare I say it…? Chris Benoit (granted he was on SmackDown! initially). All these only furthered my need for my fix of wrestling - I would pull the all-nighters to watch the PPVs, at the sacrifice of schooling and potential friendships if matches didn’t go the way I wanted to the next day. Then Wrestlemania 21 happened. It was no X7 but it was good enough, and it was clear that some of the old guard were slowing down and the new boys were taking over. It was a fresh start and paved the way for new storylines and rivalries to happen. This era of peace was not going to replicate the Monday Night Wars, but would come close, especially with the addition of the draft picks and Team RAW vs Team SmackDown! matches at Survivor Series.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amongst all this, darker days came… Eddie Gurrereo passed away… then Chris Benoit. The feel of WWE changed, dramatically. But I still watched it. I still loved it. I still invested in it. The impact of the passing of these two greats (and no, I do NOT condone what Benoit did, but you cannot deny his talent pre-June 2007), made people more aware of the “violence” in pro-wrestling (living in America at the time, the news was full of reports on this tragedy, with most of the reports containing false allegations). Seemingly overnight the following happened: Chair shots?  Gone. Blood? Vanished. Weapons? Not used. Target Demographic? Altered, and it was clear I wasn’t in it. Then I noticed TNA Wrestling. And Aces and Eights. This hooked me in again - THIS is what pro-wrestling should be… but then TNA started to make their mistakes and quickly lost my interest, as they had done before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, I went crawling back to WWE, and I am not sorry. Over 4 years ago, I subscribed to the Network I discovered NXT and my word, does the future look bright. NXT Blackpool in 2015 was one of the greatest sporting events I have ever attended - moments still make me giggle and smile several years later. NXT Liverpool in 2016 was also a brilliant show too, but Blackpool just pips it! Then, in December 2016 I got a voicemail telling me I was getting a bonus Christmas present, tickets to see UK Championship Tournament in Blackpool. That night in January 2017 an epiphany happened, and I fell in love with the UK Wrestling scene. I cried when Tyler Bate won the title. I cried when he lost it to Pete Dunne. I cried because Pete Dunne was the UK Champion. I cried when Moustache Mountain won the NXT Tag Team Titles and was bereft when they lost them. I am so excited by other British promotions, and NXT UK. I was at the Liverpool tapings for NXT UK in 2018 (front row, I might add!) and began 2019 with another trip to Blackpool for NXT UK Takeover: Blackpool and the aftermath tapings. Let me tell you, there is nothing like being part of thousands of people calling out Vince McMahon and getting him to respond. Only the UK Fans have the balls to do this with the confidence and pride that you heard at Blackpool and Cardiff. It was deafening at Blackpool and, although I wasn’t there, I have a feeling it was the same in Cardiff. My only hope is that the NXT UK Roster follows the same and to the point format of its American father, seemingly knowing who to push and who to develop, with engaging storylines and there is a huge sense of competition between talent the future of wrestling is brighter than ever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the more refreshing aspects of NXT was their one hour shows, meaning you can go weeks without seeing a superstar, meaning I value their matches more. I’m still undecided if the 2-hour format works. I hope that the development of characters continues to be better than the main roster, seemingly because they’re not shoved down your throats. This environment reminds me of the fabled Attitude Era and how good it was. Because of NXT I have been exposed to the likes of Shinsuke Nakamura, Ricochet, Hedeo Itami, No Way Hose, Cien Almas, Finn Balor, Ember Moon, Alistair Black, Tomaso Ciampa and Johnny Gargano… I could go on and list more. But, more importantly, because of NXT, I have gone on to seek out and watch the likes of ROH and NJPW to see the earlier work of the talent mentioned. So much so, I consider Wrestle Kingdom 11 to be one of the best PPVs’ I’ve ever witnessed! This newfound discovery has created dream scenarios’ where I see Kenny Omega signing to NXT. Because of NXT, I am excited to be a wrestling fan again. I cannot wait for Wednesdays to come around, so I can watch NXT, not to mention how excited I get for NXT: Takeovers and how jealous I was that I couldn’t see NXT at Download this year. My one criticism… If only creative could continue this work with the talents when they’re called up to the main rosters… Let me leave this here, Tyler Breeze, Nakamura and Alistair Black STILL deserve better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also have a changing wrestling scene with the addition of AEW. This offers yet another alternative to the WWE product. I can’t say I’ve watched it religiously (i.e stayed up late to catch it in ‘real time’), but I have watched Dynamite on a regular basis. Despite it being early days, I do see so much potential in the promotion – not just because of the likes of the Young Bucks (they’ll always be Generation Me!), Omega, Cody and Dustin. The product, overall, feels more authentic and revives the sense of ‘anything can happen’. Something that WWE programming has been lacking for a while now (NXT Excluded, of course!). Not to mention the commentary team. Whilst WWE has Mauro, Graves and McGuinness (some of the best around in my opinion), it is comforting to hear Tony Schiavone and JR’s voice on commentary. Another reason why I tune in. Call me nostalgic, but I adore the two of them on commentary, although I must also give credit to Excalibur too. The ‘Wednesday Night War’ is another reason why I am excited to be a wrestling fan again – maybe, just maybe, this is what WWE needs to change its stale ways. This is what can happen when you allow talent to be themselves – Jon Moxley, PAK, Jericho, Sean Spears have become exciting to see again, because you never know what can happen when they’re around. Be it Jericho trolling the fans by calling out their chants, PAKs mean streak or Jon Moxley talking directly down the camera. It makes AEW must see TV. Lets just hope this continues…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I started this piece, I announced that Pro-Wrestling is my addiction. There is no escape from it, it simply is. I have used this piece to introduce myself to new websites that I write for to allow the depth of my addiction to shine through, especially as I know that others feel the same. We know that it is pre-determined and scripted. We know that people will tell us that its fake and will mock us for this admission. On a personal level, I know that people will dislike the fact that my main source of wrestling is WWE, and not independents’ like Progress, ROH or NJPW. I know that WWE make mistakes; If I had a quid (£1) for every time I’ve said “this is bull sh*t! I am Done with this!” I would be more than comfortable! I get why certain talents are pushed and others not. I understand that not every wrestling fan will see eye-to-eye on things like who is the greatest of all time? Who should be pushed now? Why aren’t such and such in the Hall of Fame yet? But this is one of the reasons why I adore the wrestling scene - not everyone agrees, but on that rare occasion when the stars align, and we see greatness (such as Eddie Gurrereo), our belief is suspended, and we unite as one, caught up in the moment, jaws slack, standing in awe. There are no words to describe the feeling of standing in a crowd of people, all sharing a passion and joy in what we’re seeing, chanting so loud it stops a match (American Alpha vs. Blake and Murphy at NXT Blackpool) or that it makes me lose my voice due to a throat infection that followed (I blame Finn and Nakamura at NXT Liverpool and AJ Styles winning the World Title in Manchester in 2017). It is these moments that fuels the addiction, makes me proud to admit that I adore professional wrestling; I crave more; my life is empty without it… and I hope this piece encourages others to admit their addiction too.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>lexi-helms</name></author><summary type="html">Ladies and Gentlemen: My name is Lexi Helms and I have an addiction…</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep87 - WWE TLC Review (John Scott &amp;amp; Jason Lee Wood)</title><link href="/podcasts/EP87/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep87 - WWE TLC Review (John Scott &amp; Jason Lee Wood)" /><published>2019-12-17T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-12-17T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP87</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP87/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep86 – Moxley to join Inner Circle! NXT Triple Threat Main Event WWE TLC Preview</title><link href="/podcasts/EP86/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep86 – Moxley to join Inner Circle!  NXT Triple Threat Main Event  WWE TLC Preview" /><published>2019-12-16T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-12-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP86</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP86/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep85 - 2 Min BRAINBUSTER Quiz (Bonus Ep w/ Kieron Reed)</title><link href="/podcasts/EP85/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep85 - 2 Min BRAINBUSTER Quiz (Bonus Ep w/ Kieron Reed)" /><published>2019-12-10T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-12-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP85</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP85/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep84 - Interview with CJ CARTER (Pro Wrestling CLASH &amp;amp; Turnbuckle TV)</title><link href="/podcasts/EP84/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep84 - Interview with CJ CARTER (Pro Wrestling CLASH &amp; Turnbuckle TV)" /><published>2019-12-05T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-12-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP84</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP84/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Welcome to the Wrestling with Johners website!</title><link href="/articles/Matt-Based-Wrestling/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to the Wrestling with Johners website!" /><published>2019-12-03T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-12-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/Matt%20Based%20Wrestling</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/Matt-Based-Wrestling/">&lt;p&gt;First up I am really looking forward to working with Johners to create content for this website, which I am sure is going to be a great experience. I have loved seeing, well hearing the progress and development of the Wrestling With Johners podcast over the last year or so as well as the growth of the community especially on Facebook!
I have previously written reviews and articles over on The Indy Corner as well as providing some content for the podcast too covering a load of British wrestling including Progress and Kamikaze Pro. A few years back I trained for a while with Kamikaze Pro which meant getting trained by Pete Dunne – although my time there was short lived, mostly due to lack of fitness and an injury plus boring stuff like work!
I was fortunate enough to meet Johners through work, it’s always good to make a friend with shared interests and we’ve been able to attend a variety of shows together including Attack!, 4FW and Progress.
I have been a wrestling fan for close to 30 years now – originally through WWF where the first match I saw was a Bret vs Owen bout and was hooked instantly! I started following British Wrestling much later on and have been to many promotions around the country and been fortunate to see so many talents up close who are now on global TV on a weekly basis, and also had some amazing experiences including camel clutches from Sabu and Uhaa Nation/Apollo Crews, commentating on a Juventud Guerera match as well as a multi person elimination match featuring Joe Coffey, Kay Lee Ray, Kenny Williams, Dan Moloney, Pete Dunne, Robbie X and Tyler Bate and of course I can’t leave out  harassing Eddie Dennis with an inflatable sheep for months with a little help from Uhaa Nation and Tomasso Ciampa!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have also been fortunate enough to meet some big names over the years including Bret Hart, Scott Hall, Sunny, Ted Dibiase, DDP and even the living legend Virgil who I actually had a really good chat with! Although my personal highlight would be meeting the Hardcore Legend Mick Foley on two occasions and in particularly getting a hug from my hero!
Where do I stand on the WWE/AEW battle? I have said from the start that AEW needs time, they need to do their thing but they will only be successful if they can do it over a long period of time and keep the quality high. WWE is far from perfect, although NXT is arguably the closest thing to it in the whole of wrestling at the moment. I actually think AEW is tracking better than I expected them to be at this stage – some of what they are doing so far is phenomenal especially with some of Jericho’s promo work and what they have achieved so far with their tag division.
I am always keen to find the positives in wrestling, anyone who steps inside the ring is there to entertain and put their bodies on the line to do so – are some better than others? Of course, but I don’t see the point in trying to slate people. Similarly I understand everyone is entitled to their opinion and always happy to listen and discuss different views. That’s part of what makes wrestling fandom amazing
I am on Twitter where I have a new profile – Matt Based Wrestling - just to focus on all things wrestling related; you can follow me at @mattbasedwres01&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>matt-bayliss</name></author><summary type="html">First up I am really looking forward to working with Johners to create content for this website, which I am sure is going to be a great experience. I have loved seeing, well hearing the progress and development of the Wrestling With Johners podcast over the last year or so as well as the growth of the community especially on Facebook! I have previously written reviews and articles over on The Indy Corner as well as providing some content for the podcast too covering a load of British wrestling including Progress and Kamikaze Pro. A few years back I trained for a while with Kamikaze Pro which meant getting trained by Pete Dunne – although my time there was short lived, mostly due to lack of fitness and an injury plus boring stuff like work! I was fortunate enough to meet Johners through work, it’s always good to make a friend with shared interests and we’ve been able to attend a variety of shows together including Attack!, 4FW and Progress. I have been a wrestling fan for close to 30 years now – originally through WWF where the first match I saw was a Bret vs Owen bout and was hooked instantly! I started following British Wrestling much later on and have been to many promotions around the country and been fortunate to see so many talents up close who are now on global TV on a weekly basis, and also had some amazing experiences including camel clutches from Sabu and Uhaa Nation/Apollo Crews, commentating on a Juventud Guerera match as well as a multi person elimination match featuring Joe Coffey, Kay Lee Ray, Kenny Williams, Dan Moloney, Pete Dunne, Robbie X and Tyler Bate and of course I can’t leave out harassing Eddie Dennis with an inflatable sheep for months with a little help from Uhaa Nation and Tomasso Ciampa!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Underground Report</title><link href="/articles/Underground-Report/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Underground Report" /><published>2019-12-03T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-12-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/articles/Underground%20Report</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/Underground-Report/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; src=&quot;/assets/posts/2019-11-23/image2.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Date: 30/8/2019&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Venue: Logan Square Auditorium Chicago Illinois&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Matches&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#colt-cobana-vs-josh-alexander--quarter-final-tournament-match&quot;&gt;Colt Cobana vs Josh Alexander Quarter Final Tournament Match&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#myron-reed-vs-laredo-kid-second-quarter-final-match&quot;&gt;Myron Reed vs Laredo Kid Quarter Final Tournament Match&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#curt-stallion-vs-eddie-kingston-third-quarter-final-match&quot;&gt;Curt Stallion vs Eddie Kingston Quarter Final Tournament Match&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#ace-romero-vs-paco-4th-quarter-final-match&quot;&gt;Ace Romero vs Paco Quarter Final Tournament Match&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#5-way-scramble-match-for-the-aaw-heritage-championship&quot;&gt;AAW Heritage Championship: Ace Austin vs Clayton Gainz vs Willie Mack vs Jake Atlas vs Jake Something ( 5 way Scramble Match)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#josh-alexander-vs-myron-reed-first-semi-final-tournament-match&quot;&gt;Semi Final Tournament Match 1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#ace-romero-vs-eddie-kingston-second-semi-final-tournament-match&quot;&gt;Semi Final Tournament Match 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#santana--ortiz-lax-at-the-time-vs-lucha-bros--fenix-and-pentagon-jr&quot;&gt;Santana and Ortiz (LAX) vs Lucha Bros (Rey Fenix and Pentagon Jr)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#jessicka-havok-and-the-besties-in-the-world-davey-vega-and-matt-fitchett-vs-the-rascalz-desmond-xavier-trey-miguel-and-zachery-wentz&quot;&gt;Besties In the World (Matt Fitchett and Davey Vega) &amp;amp; Jessicka Havok vs The Rascals (Trey Miguel, Zachary Wentz and Desmond Xavier)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#aaw-heavyweight-championship-match-sami-callahan-wjt-davidson-vs-kris-statlander&quot;&gt;AAW Championship Sami Callahan vs Kris Statlander&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#jim-lynam-memorial-tournament-final-josh-alexander-vs-eddie-kingston&quot;&gt;Tournament Final&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;pre-show&quot;&gt;Pre Show&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before the show starts Danny Lynam comes to ringside with his son to say how much this show means to him and his family. He says Jim is with everyone in the arena in spirit. Jim was a Chicago radio broadcaster and it was his idea to help start AAW and he would be so proud.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;show&quot;&gt;Show&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sarah Shackey interview with Colt Cobana, Colt Cobana, Colt says to be in this tournament is a privilege and an honour. Colt knew Jim and spent a lot of hours talking to him. Colt has been at AAW since the start but he has never had the privilege of representing AAW as champion, he has held the AAW Heritage title but never the AAW Heavyweight title, Colt says he knows Josh wants the Colt Cobana of old and Colt will bring out his serious side and Josh is going to regret ever asking for it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jimmy Jacobs comes to the ring dressed in evening clothes and cuts a promo saying he has to take control of the Mance Warner situation. Mance lost a loser leaves AAW match he says thanks to him you will never see Mance Warner again. Then music hits and Good Brother Number 3 comes out who again is obviously Warner in a mask with a kendo stick in his hand. Jimmy picks up a steel chair both swing and miss before Jimmy get’s the advantage GBN3 ducks a chairshot and hits Jimmy round the back of the head with the kendo stick. Jimmy powders outside drags GBN3 outside and they brawl round the outside. Back in the ring security pull both guys apart, the crowd shout “let them fight”.  GBN3 takes his frustrations out on the security&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2019-12-03/unnamed.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;colt-cobana-vs-josh-alexander--quarter-final-tournament-match&quot;&gt;Colt Cobana vs Josh Alexander – Quarter Final Tournament Match&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They both lock up, Waistlock Takedowns from both to start, Josh works over the arm followed by basic chain wrestling, Josh rolls Cobana up for a 2 count. Cobana whips Alexander into the corner but doesn’t follow up. More chain wrestling Cobana does the Johnny Saint corner reversal for a 2 count. Foream exchanges follow which Colt wins. Alexander straight back to his feet hit’s a hard knee strike to Colt’s body Colt hits the ropes and hits a Satellite Headscissors on Alexander who powders out of the ring, Cot follows and they both brawl around the ring. Back in the ring Alexander hits a Fireman’s Carry roll through (Omega style) goes up to the middle rope and hits a diving Knee drop for a 2 count. Forearms and Chops from Alexander follow but Colt reverses not for long as Josh putsd Colt into a reverse Chinlock. Colt fights out hits the ropes floats over Alexander and hits a beautiful Russian Leg Sweep followed by a submission move (which looks a lot like Pac’s Brutaliser) Colt fights out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trade off of Forearms follow which Alexander wins, Josh Chops Colt back into the corner Josh runs for an Avelanch Splash but eats turnbuckle, Colt then hits signature Dusty Rhodes punches goes for a Bionic Elbow but Josh punches Colt to the face before Colt eventually hits the Bionic Elbow to crowd applause. Josh feeds into the corner Colt goes for a Flying Hip Attack Alexander catches him and German Suplex’s Cobana into the corner. Alexander then hits a huge splash into the corner but gets cut off on the second one, Colt goes up to middle turnbuckle . Alexander runs at him hits a Forearm, Alexander climbs up top Colt pushes him down, Colt hits a a Canadian Destroyer onto Alexander gets a 2 count, Cobana looks frustrated but Forearms Alexander who backs into the corner, Cobana hits the flying Hip-Attack and places Alexander on the top turnbuckle , and goes for a Back Suplex . Alexander fights out sends Colt down to the canvas, goes for a top rope Moonsault but Colt moves. Colt goes up top for a top rope Moonsault gets a two count. He picks Alexander’s legs up goes for the Billy Goats Curse Alexander reverses it into an Anklelock. Colt reverses and rolls through and goes for the Billy Goats Curse again but Alexander sends him flying out on to the ring apron. Josh hits the Roaring Elbow but Colt sends him to the outside. Alexander hits Colt with a hard strike goes up top Cobana cuts him off. Cobana picks him up for a Fireman’s Carry drops Alexander’s body first on the top turnbuckle. Colt goes for the Superman pinning combination. Alexander grabs Cobana’s ankle and Colt taps&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Winner and advancing to the Semi Finals : Josh Alexander&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time: 12 minutes 31 seconds&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Match Rating: 4 out of 5 * Great match felt a lot longer than 12 minutes though hard-fought battle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;myron-reed-vs-laredo-kid-second-quarter-final-match&quot;&gt;Myron Reed vs Laredo Kid Second Quarter Final Match&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reed opening strike to Kid who fakes to the outside Gammanguri kicks and Springboard rolls through to the inside. Myron goes for a Clothesline misses but hits a nice Hurricarana. Laredo ducks a Clothesline and hits a beautiful Headscissors standoff centre of the ring.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A couple of more lightning fast reversals follow with Kid rolling up Myron for a 2 count. Kid goes for a reverse Texas Cloverleaf Laredo Kid lets go but starts working on Myron’s left knee and continue to ‘Charley Horse’ it. Kid picks up reed for a Suplex but Reed reverses mid air into a Stunner. Kid goes for a roundhouse kick but Myron Matrix fakes out Kid and hits a nice Enziguri which leads to a double down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reed runs at Kid but Backsplashes nothing but turnbuckle, Kid hits a jumping Forearm and a Michanoku Driver, Laredo goes for a bottom rope Moonsault which he hits. Kid goes for a springboard second rope Moonsault but Reed gets his knees into Kids bread basket. Reed hits the rope and Springboard Cutters Kid for a two count. Myron is slow because of his leg being worked on Kid cuts off Myron who backs Elbow’s kid sending him to backflip to his feet to avoid crashing into the mat.  Myron jumps off the top turnbuckle but eats a Dropkick from Kid. Kid goes for a Suplex again which Reed has scouted and hits the Stunner reversal for the second time Reed then hits a Canadian Destroyer onto Kid for the 3 count.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Winner and advancing to the Semi Finals: Myron Reed&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rating: 3.5 out of 5* Finish came out of nowhere it was a fantastic match till then&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sarah Shackey interviews Paco who says he will take any advantage he can.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;curt-stallion-vs-eddie-kingston-third-quarter-final-match&quot;&gt;Curt Stallion vs Eddie Kingston Third Quarter Final Match&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eddie Kingston walks to the ring with purpose. Match starts and they go straight into a Hockey fight straight rights and lefts thrown by both guys. Trade off of Forearms follow which Stallion wins,  Stallion follows with a German Suplex which Eddie no sells there then follows German Suplex after German Suplex from both guys who no sell and get straight back up until eventually Stallion gets up slow and goes to Clothesline Kingston ducks and Stallion German Suplexs him again !!! that must be about 6 German Suplex’s in about 2 minutes. Kingston back up Clotheslines Stallion out of his boots for a big double down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back up exchange of hard Chops which makes Stallions chest bleed! A flurry of European Uppercuts by Stallion leads to Forearms and an STO by Kingston. He gets a count of 1. Kingston then hits a beautiful Urinagi Slam onto Stallion for a 2 count. Kingston hits a big sit out Powerbomb for a 2 count.  Kingston then hits more hard Chops this time to the back of Stallion who fights back sending Kingston into the corner this has been brutal so far. Curt Stallion hits an Air Raid Crash before kicking Kingston to the shoulder which gets a count of 2.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trade offof unprotected Headbutt’s follow by both and both guys feed into opposite corners. Stallion hit’s a Mafia Kick sending Kingston down and then follows up with with a hard Knee Strike followed by a Hesitation Dropkick to Kingston’s face. Kingston fights back and Clotheslines and hits Stallion with a variety of strikes followed by a Spinning Back Fist for the 3 count.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Winner and advancing to the Semi-Finals: Eddie Kingston&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time: 7 Minutes 2 Seconds&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rating 3.5 out of 5* Brutal hard hitting match the Headbutts were sickening&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;ace-romero-vs-paco-4th-quarter-final-match&quot;&gt;Ace Romero vs Paco 4th Quarter Final Match&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 4th Quarter Final match sees huge underdog Paco against big Acey Baby Ace Romero
Both square off Centre of the ring. Lockup Ace powers Paco down into the corner twice. Paco sends Ace to the corner with a Satellite Headscissors. Paco goes to the second turnbuckle Ace cuts him off, Paco jumps off for a High Cross Body straight onto Romero who catches Paco and powers him down with a Slam. Paco avoids a charge from Romero sending him to the outside. Paco hits a succession of Suicide Dives onto Romero before Romero catches him on the third and sends Paco down back first onto the apron . Back in the ring and Ace hits a big Pounce for a 2 count. Huge babyface heat from the crowd “Paco” chants. Paco gets placed on the top rope by Romero. Paco fights him off and Sunset Flips Romero off the Second Rope for a 2 count for a 2 count. Paco hits 3 Superkicks followed by a Tornado DDT. Paco goes up top for a huge Frogsplash hits it for a 2 count.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Paco hits a barrage of Roundhouse kicks (Miz style) to Romero’s chest before Ace catches his foot more strikes follow before Ace hits the big Clothesline from Hell for the 3 count&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Winner and advancing to the Semi Finals: Ace Romero&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time: 7 Minutes and 25 Seconds&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rating 4 out of 5* - Best match of the night so far, great David and Goliath story told here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;5-way-scramble-match-for-the-aaw-heritage-championship&quot;&gt;5 Way Scramble Match For The AAW Heritage Championship&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ace Austin vs Clayton Gainz vs Jake Atlas vs Willie Mack vs Jake Something 
5 Way scramble’s are very difficult to follow but I’m going to try my best. Gainz and Austin hit double Roundhouse Kicks on Mack and Atlas. Austin drop toe holds Something down then kicks him to the back of the head, Austin and Gainz continue to work on Something until a double team Irish Whip fails as Something hits a running Hip Attack on to Austin and a huge one handed slam onto Gainz. Atlas on the outside hits a Gamunguri on Something followed by a springboard Armdrag into the ring followed by a jump up Enziguri and a change of direction following by floating over Something’s back before posing. Something goes for an Elbow but Atlas moves and Atlas hits a Springboard Hurricarana on Something sending him outside. Atlas follows with a Tope over the top rope Austin goes for a PK Atlas blocks it Ace gets himself free hitting a Thrust kick, sending Atlas down&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mack in the ring gets Shoulder Blocked by Austin who goes for a Springboard Kick Mack catches him and sends Austin into the corner with a Fallaway Slam. Mack hits a diving Forearm onto Austin, Gains runs into a Elbow followed by a hard Kick and a Pump Kick sending Gainz into the other corner as well as a Senton to Gainz. Mack runs at Austin but eats a Boot, Ace hits the ropes Mack catches him and hits him with a Somoan Drop , Mack kips up before Moonsaulting onto Austin. Something runs into a big German Suplex from Mack and a T-Bone Exploder, Mack runs at Something but Something moves Something hits Atlas with a Sit Out Powerbomb for a 2 count. The pin is broken by Ace. With heavy Kicks to Something and unleashes some big Forearms. Ace goes for a Spinning Kick Something moves and Something hits Austin with a big Spear. Austin goes to the ropes before kicking Something to the head. Something rolls to the outside Gainz and Austin go for simultaneous Clotheslines on Mack and Atlas but both step aside sending Gainz and Austin outside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mack goes for a Kick on Atlas who catches his foot and hits a reverse Roundhouse Kick to Mack’s chin. Mack hits a Thrust Kick back and Atlas hits a Jumping Knee to Mack’s face followed by a Handstand into a Tornado DDT very inventive offense onto Mack. Gainz in hit’s a TKO onto Atlas and Austin double stomp variation sends Atlas down. Atlas kicks out at 2, Ace Austin drags Mack back in the ring and hits a few Forearms before hitting the ropes and Mack lifts him up and forearms Austin out of the air following up with a Powerbomb of his own. Gainz breaks up the pin, Gainz exchange of Chops with Mack before Mack sends him into the corner Gainz reverses a nd Powerslams Mack followed by a Vader Bomb. Austin hits a Springboard change of direction Splash but Something breaks up the pin. Something sends Ace and Gainz down with Forearms. Something goes for a Spear Ace avoids and hits a Caprana Kick Gainz goes to Spear Something who moves and he ends up accidently spearing Austin in the corner. Something hits a big sit out Slam on Gainz for the 3 count.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Winner and still AAW Heritage Champion Jake Something&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time: 8 Minutes and 12 Seconds&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rating 4 out of 5* typical good Spotfest&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sarah Shackey interviews Ace Romero who says nobody can stop him its his time. Ace says Eddie Kingston is an Independent legend but tonight it’s Aces tournament to win.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;josh-alexander-vs-myron-reed-first-semi-final-tournament-match&quot;&gt;Josh Alexander vs Myron Reed First Semi Final Tournament Match&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Josh charges at Myron who moves, Reed Dropkick’s to the back of Alexander who powders to the outside. Reed hits an explosive Tope Con Hilo over the Turnbuckles onto to Alexander, Reed sends Alexander back in the ring and hits a perfect springboard 450 into the ring onto Josh Alexander for a 2 count. Alexander feeds to the corner, Reed hits a big corner Dropkick and floats in and out of the ring aiming to end in a Tornado DDT on Alexander who powers Reed down with a vicious Powerbomb to the knee followed by a Gory Guerreo Special Reed doesn’t submit. Alexander kicks Reed to the back and goes for the Gory Special again Reed this time floats over Josh Chops him back down. Myron back up hit’s a Superkick and goes for a Pump Kick Alexander catches his leg and hit’s Reed with another huge Backbreaker. Josh goes for a big Suplex but Reverses into the Stunner and Reed goes for a springboard, but Alexander catches him mid air into a Torture Rack before powering him down. Alexander gets a count of 2. Josh stomps on Reed before putting him in an Anklelock, Reed fights off with Kicks. Reed back up hits a Springboard Ace Crusher and gets a 2 count&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reed goes for a Pump Kick Alexander catches it but Reed Backflips out Reed goes for a Tope but Alexander catches him and slams him back first onto the apron Alexander then hits the ropes Lope’s out and takes out Reed who was leaning on the bottom rope that looked nasty. They both Brawl round the outside, back in Alexander climbs to the top turnbuckle Reed catches him climbs up and hits a big one-man Spanish Fly for a 2 count.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Big double down follows, both back up Trade-off of Forearms Alexander keeps hitting clubbing blows to Reeds back. Josh goes for a big chop on to Reed who Matrix’s out, Reed goes for an Enziguri but misses Alexander picks him back up and goes for a Ripcord Clothesline which Reed ducks and Reed goes for the fake out fake in Codebreaker but Alexander has it scouted sends Reed into the corner Reed out of nowhere with a quick roll up count of 2. Alexander goes for a Backslide 2 count.  Reed back up hits a Canadian Destroyer for a 2 count and he follows with an an attempted 450 Splash which he rolls through as Josh moved. Reed runs straight into a Big Boot from Josh in the corner. Alexander goes for a German Suplex into the corner Reed rolls through into a pin for a 2 count. Alexander hits a Ripcord Forearm to the face. Alexander powers to the second rope with Reed on his shoulders. Reed forearms out and Alexander drops Reed onto the apron. Reed goes for a Springboard Hurricarana, but Alexander was waiting catches him in a big sit out Powerbomb followed by a Jay Driller for the 3 count.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Winner and advancing to the final: Josh Alexander&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time: 11 Minutes 54 Seconds&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Match Rating 4.5 out of 5*. Great Match Myron Reed is something special for the future&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jake Something and Curt Stallion are outside the building talking about where the hell David Starr is who is there leader, Jake says David Starr should stop doing his battles on Twitter&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;ace-romero-vs-eddie-kingston-second-semi-final-tournament-match&quot;&gt;Ace Romero vs Eddie Kingston Second Semi Final Tournament Match&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two big super heavyweights go to war here. Ace tries Powering Kingston over doesn’t work. Eddie then tries Drop Toe Holding Ace down but Ace jumps down with all his weight into an Elbow Drop onto Kingston’s injured ribs. Kingston feeds into the corner Romero hit’s an Avalanche Splash on Kingston. Ace picks up Kingston who fights back with a Chop before the start trading Chops, Romero hits a big Dropkick for a Two Count, Ace goes up for a second rope Vaderbomb Kingston moves and both Double Down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back up Kingston hits Romero with a couple of Hard Chops, Kingston hits the ropes and Ace powers him down with a big Clothesline, Kingston kicks out of a 2 count. Ace sends Kingston into the ropes hit’s a big Sit Out Powerbomb for a 2 count. Both trade off of Forearms Kingston hits the Spinning Backfist from nowhere onto Romero followed by a Saito Suplex for a 3 count.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Winner and advancing to the final: Eddie Kingston&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time: 4 minutes and 37 seconds&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Match Rating: 3 out of 5&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Very short match and the ending caught me off guard&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;santana--ortiz-lax-at-the-time-vs-lucha-bros--fenix-and-pentagon-jr&quot;&gt;Santana &amp;amp; Ortiz (LAX at the time) vs Lucha Bros ( Fenix and Pentagon Jr)&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This starts with a big time brawl round the outside at one stage Pentagon gets launched into the front row! Santana piledrives Fenix into a stood-up chair.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Match officially underway Ortiz sets up Pentagon on the top turnbuckle and tries to rip his mask off. All 4 guys brawl back into the crowd Santana DDT’s Fenix on the stage. More brawling to the ring back in double Superkicks from the Lucha Bros before Santana and Ortiz hit Superkicks of their own. Before both being sent into opposite corners both Fenix and Pentagon hit double Forearms and double Wheel Kicks onto LAX. Out of the corner Lucha Bros hit double Superkicks. Fenix and Santana brawl to the outside Fenix places Santana onto the guard rail before walking the guardrail and hitting a double Stomp. Both teams again brawl into the crowd.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pentagon trades chops with Ortiz on the stage. Fenix Dropkicks a dustbin into Santana. Back in Fenix whips Santana into a dustbin Fenix Powerbomb onto Santana whilst Pentagon hits a top rope Low Blow, Lucha Bros double team Ortiz. Pentagon with a Codebreaker Fenix with a Double Stomp.  Both guys back up Ortiz hits a Michanouko Driver whilst Santana hits an Alley Oop sending Fenix into Pentagon for a Double Count of 2. Santana slams Fenix down before more double teaming as Ortiz hits a Senton and Santana Moonsault’s off Ortiz back. Ortiz hits the comical no hands Splash for a 2 count. LAX continue the double teaming on Fenix who rolls out of a Washing Machine attempt Pentagon back in hit’s a Superkick on Ortiz but get’s Pump Kicked back before Pentagon grabs two chairs throws one to Ortiz and both guys hit big chair shots to each other over the head. All four men then start Chopping each other leaving Fenix and Santana the only ones left standing before all 4 men kick each other leading to a 4 way double down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Santana and Pentagon feed into each opposite corner before Santana runs at Pentagon who floats over him and Pentagon kicks his legs out. Santana goes crashing down Pentagon goes up top fly’s at Santana iinto a big Cross-body Pentagon throws a Clothesline Santana ducks and removes Pentagon’s mask!!!. Pentagon rolls to the outside.  Santana runs at Fenix Springboards into a Low Blow from Fenix who rolls him up before Ortiz pulls the ref outside Pentagon appears again with mask back on stereo Superkicks to Ortiz Santana fights off both Lucha Bros  before hitting the ropes gets Back Kicked from Pentagon and double teamed Double Stomp Package Piledriver combo before Pentagon rolls up Santana for the 3 count.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Winners: The Lucha Bros&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time: 13 minutes 4 seconds&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Match Rating: 3 out of 5 *&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Big brawl most of the match not really my thing but still entertaining however&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the match huge ovation for both teams both teams go to shake hands before the dastardly heels LAX remove the Lucha Bros masks and leave the ring,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Airwolf goes to the ring only to be attacked by Killer Kross and Scarlett Bordeaux. Killer Kross then cuts a promo saying he will kill anyone who will confront him. Scarlett says she has never had a title shot and Scarlett would kick Jessica Havok’s ass all over Chicago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Havok then comes to the ring with backup of the Besties in the world. The Rascalz jump Havok and the Besties from behind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Match Starts&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;jessicka-havok-and-the-besties-in-the-world-davey-vega-and-matt-fitchett-vs-the-rascalz-desmond-xavier-trey-miguel-and-zachery-wentz&quot;&gt;Jessicka Havok and The Besties In The World (Davey Vega and Matt Fitchett) vs The Rascalz (Desmond Xavier, Trey Miguel and Zachery Wentz)&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wentz hits a Headlock Driver on Vega on the outside to start, Xavier and Fitchett in the ring Fitchett Forearms Xavier into the corner, goes to the ropes, Xavier hits a beautiful Dropkick. Xavier then starts taunting the crowd before Punching the ribs of Fitchett, Xavier tags in Wentz who Lucha rolls onto Fitchett before Miguel follows before Xavier hits his trapped leg version.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Miguel tags in hooks Fitchett in the Tree Of Woe before Choking him in the corner. Miguel gets the ref distracted before low blowing Fitchett. Miguel tags Wentz in who European Uppercuts Fitchett and tags in Xavier. Xavier picks up Fitchett who floats down his back and hits a big Enziguri before hot tagging Davey Vega in. Davey runs through a Xavier clothesline and attacks Miguel and Wentz. Vega Kicks Xavier’s leg before Dragon Screw Leg Whipping and wiping him off with a big Roundhouse Kick. Vega change of direction and Forearms Miguel before hitting a Death Valley Driver on him. Wentz back in hits a Handstand Knee Strike on Vega. Xavier tags in Wentz who wears Vega down with a Reverse Chinlock. Vega fights out but eats a Dropkick from Wentz and pins him for a Two Count. The Rascals taunt the crowd Miguel runs and eats a boot from Vega who fights off all the Rascalz and hits a Gamunguri on Miguel, before hitting a big High-Cross Body and hot tags Havok in. Havok fired up Double Clotheslines and Chokeslams to Xavier and Wentz before eating a Boot in the corner from Xavier. She picks up both Xavier and Wentz and hits a double Samoan Drop on both that was impressive. Havok hits the ropes and eats a Superkick from Miguel before Miguel goes for a Suicide Dive misses everyone and hits nothing but guardrail ouch! Havok takes out Wentz and Xavier with a Suicide Dive back in Chokeslams Miguel but Xavier breaks up the pin. Havok with a big knee hits Xavier then tags in Fitchett but all 3 come in the ring so we have a 3 on 2 standoff. Wentz takes out Havok to the outside Xavier hits Vega with a Superkick and a Double Stomp (Coup De Gras style) Vega sends Miguel into the pile breaking up the pin attempt. Havok picks up Miguel Forearms him exchange of Forearms Havok wins the exchange. She hits the ropes but eats a Superkick she follows with a Roundhouse Kick. Xavier and Wentz hit perfect Superkicks onto her before a Combo of Kicks and Stomps sends her down. Vega double kicked both Wentz and and Xavier and cuts Miguel off at the top. The Rascalz back in Miguel traps Vega’s head and hits a Cheeky Nando’s Kick followed by a Tiger Feint Kick from Xavier and a Double Stomp off Wentz shoulders, sending Vega crashing down. Fitchett back in double Pele onto Wentz and Miguel before hitting a Pele onto Xavier on the apron.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fitchett hits a beautiful Hurricarana off the second rope sending Miguel into the corner. Miguel Casadora pin and gets the 3 count for the Rascalz&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Winners: The Rascalz&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time: 9 Minutes 52 Seconds&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Match Rating 4.5 out of 5 *&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Great spot fest. Very enjoyable match&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sami Callahan comes to the ring with JT Davidson. Sami cuts a promo says he issued a challenge on Twitter for anyone who has the guts to face them, they need to come up and face #TheDraw&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;aaw-heavyweight-championship-match-sami-callahan-wjt-davidson-vs-kris-statlander&quot;&gt;AAW Heavyweight Championship Match Sami Callahan w/JT Davidson vs Kris Statlander&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Statlander tries playing mind games with Callahan who pie faces her down. Match starts off with Callahan working a side headlock right on Statlander who breaks free hits the ropes Sami forearms her straight on the chin. Statlander kips straight up and Matrix’s into a Crab, avoiding a Callahan Clothesline and Statlander hits a Pele sending Callahan to the outside. Statlander goes for a Hurricarana off the apron but Callahan catches her and Powerbombs her to the apron he does it again but catches her head mainly on the apron, that looked vicious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Callahan sends her straight into the guard rail. Statlander back in the ring, Callahan puts an Indian Deathlock on her  Statlander reaches for the ropes. Sami continues working on her leg and Dragon Screw Leg Whips Statlander down. Sami then puts a Figure Four Leglock on her which Statlander reverses and Callahan reaches for the ropes causing a break. Sami continues to taunt the audience working Kris’s ankle on the ropes. Statlander pushes Sami over the ropes. Sami back in goes for a Stomp Statlander feeds into the corner but Callahan eats a Big Boot from Kris followed by a Slam and a Chop. Kris hits a flurry of Punches and Chops, Statlander picks Callahan up on her shoulder’s rolls through and second rope Moonsaults on to him (Omega Style) but gets a 2 count.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Statlander goes for a Fisherman Suplex but Callahan reverses and sits out into a Ligerbomb followed by a Calf Stretch. Callahan picks up a chair chucks it in the ring picks Statlander up for an Exploder Kris fights out hit’s the ropes and Callahan hits a T-Bone Exploder on her through a chair for a 2 count.  Callahan gets more chairs thrown in from Davidson, both back in Callahan hits the ropes but eats a Superkick and another one followed by a Low Blow from Statlander. She then hits a Michanoko Driver onto Callahan through the chairs for a 2 count. Statlander climbs up top but Callahan catches her Kris fights him off with Forearms and Biting sending Callahan to the mat, Statlander goes to jump but JT Davidson climbs on top of Callahan to protect him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Statlander hit’s a 450 Splash onto both Callahan and Davidson. Statlander hit’s an Axe Kick on Callahan and goes for the pin 1,2 and Davidson drags the ref outside, Statlander takes out Davidson with a Baseball Slide, She climbs up top again hits another 450 Splash and gets a 2 count, She then goes for a third 450 but Davidson grabs her ankle Callahan hits a Pump Kick followed by a Piledriver off the second rope that looked dangerous for the 3 count.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Winner and still AAW Heavyweight Champion: Sami Callahan&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time: 17 minutes 45 seconds&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rating: 4.5 out of 5*&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Very very enjoyable match, Statlander gave her all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jimmy Jacobs says he has been more successful behind the curtain that pulls the strings. He says he is done but he will give $10,000 to anyone who will rip Good Brother Number 3’s mask off and reveal him as Mance Warner&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;jim-lynam-memorial-tournament-final-josh-alexander-vs-eddie-kingston&quot;&gt;Jim Lynam Memorial Tournament Final Josh Alexander vs Eddie Kingston&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Match starts off with a Collar and Elbow which they end up doing to the ground. Alexander works on Kingston’s shoulder. Kingston is clearly injured here. Test of Strength follows which Kingston wins at first before Alexander powers back, Kingston takes him down with an Headlock Takeover but Alexander powers back up shoots Kingston off the ropes but no one moves, exchange of Chops but Kingston goes for the Spinning Backfist Alexander moves and forearms Kingston. Alexander hits the ropes but Kingston Shoulderblocks him down. Alexander powders to the outside. Kingston hits a Suicide Dive but smashes his hand on the guard rail. Alexander works over Kingston’s arm wrapping it round the post, back in the ring Alexander kicks him in the arm and stomps on it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hard Knees to Kingston’s head follow and Alexander hits a Trapped Arm Back Suplex on to Kingston. Alexander put’s Kingston’s arm in a Fujiwara Armbar but Kingston grabs the ropes. Alexander goes for another Armbar, but Kingston grabs the ropes. Alexander forearms and Chops to Kingston who fights back with Chops with his only good arm. Alexander and Kingston trade Forearms centre of the ring. Kingston goes for a Clothesline, but Alexander blocks the first before Kingston sends him down with the second. Kingston goes for a Saito Suplex but Alexander elbows out. Alexander goes to Powerbomb but Kingston backdrops him out it Kingston goes for a running Avalanche Splash Alexander moves. Kingston kicks Josh to the head Alexander Chops back places Kingston on the second turnbuckle exchange of Chops between both guys . Kingston sends him down with Headbutts, Kingston climbs on top but Alexander holds on and hits a huge Suplex for a 2 count. Both guys slow to get up Alexander hit’s hard Knee strikes to Kingston and Alexander goes to pick up Kingston but doesn’t have the leverage. Kingston hits a twisting Fisherman’s Buster for a 2 count. He then follows with a normal Fisherman’s Suplex a double down follows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both guys up at 8 Kingston goes for the Spinning Backfist Alexander German Suplex’s him. Alexander Powerbombs Kingston before Powerbombing him to his Knee and gets a 2 count. Alexander hit’s a top rope Moonsault before putting Kingston in an Anklelock followed by a Crossface Kingston reaches the ropes. Trade off of Forearms and Chops both guys almost out on their feet. Kingston hits the Backfist Alexander fights back with a Forearm Alexander hits the Ripcord Forearm but Kingston fights back with another Spinning Backfist. Another Forearm Backfist exchange Kingston goes for another Backfist but Alexander blocks and hits a Tombstone for a 2 count. Alexander goes for another Piledriver Kingston reverses into a Saito Suplex and hits the Big Backfist for a 2 count.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both guys slow to get up Kingston sets up Alexander for a Burning Hammer but Alexander floats down the back. Big Forearm to Kingston’s back hits a huge Forearm to Kingston’s jaw before hitting the Jay Driller for the 3 count.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Winner Of The Jim Lynam Memorial 2019 Tournament “The Walking Weapon” Josh Alexander&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time: 20 minutes 8 seconds&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Match Rating: 4.5 out of 5*&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Absolute brutal Strongstyle match to end the Tournament Josh Alexander the rightful winner&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fantastic event from start to finish thoroughly enjoyable, Both guys get a standing ovation&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Watch full event here https://www.highspotswrestlingnetwork.com/media/83019-jim-lynam-memorial-tournament-night-2-aaw-pro/91524/feature&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img title=&quot;Josh Alexander With The AAW Jim Lynam Memorial Trophy Copyright AAW Wrestling&quot; class=&quot;restrict-width&quot; src=&quot;/assets/posts/2019-12-03/image3.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>jc</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep83 – Jericho vs Sky | Ciampa vs Bálor | 2 Min BRAINBIUSTER Quiz | NXT vs AEW wk.9</title><link href="/podcasts/EP83/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep83 – Jericho vs Sky | Ciampa vs Bálor | 2 Min BRAINBIUSTER Quiz | NXT vs AEW wk.9" /><published>2019-12-02T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-12-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP83</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP83/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Ricky J Reports - PCW SPLIT DESCIONS 2019 REVIEW</title><link href="/article/The-Ricky-J-Reports-PCW-Split-Decision/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Ricky J Reports - PCW SPLIT DESCIONS 2019 REVIEW" /><published>2019-12-02T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-12-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/article/The%20Ricky%20J%20Reports%20-%20PCW%20Split%20Decision</id><content type="html" xml:base="/article/The-Ricky-J-Reports-PCW-Split-Decision/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;pcw-split-descions-2019-review&quot;&gt;PCW SPLIT DESCIONS 2019 REVIEW&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Show starts with sheik the sham calling out Steven Fludder. Steven beat up Sheik They will have a match on December 7th.  If Steven loses he has to leave Preston.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;first-match--danny-hope-vs-mj-maxx&quot;&gt;First match.  DANNY HOPE VS MJ MAXX&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ok match here.  Not to much else to say.  Ok opening match.  Winner of the match Danny Hope.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;next-match-up-rossy-rascal-vs-bruce-wheeler&quot;&gt;Next match up ROSSY RASCAL VS BRUCE WHEELER&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alright match.  Back and fourth action.  Once again not much else to say.  Winner of the match Rossy Rascal Onto the next match.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;mark-alexander-price-vs-ac-striker&quot;&gt;MARK ALEXANDER PRICE VS AC STRIKER&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another alright match.  AC in control for most of the match.  AC has gone from number one contender to facing mark Alexander price.  A surprising win in this one.  Winner of the match Mark Alexander Price. Time for another match.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;paradox-vs-devastating-dan-whyte-and-ryan-lloyd&quot;&gt;PARADOX VS DEVASTATING DAN WHYTE AND RYAN LLOYD&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ryan was actually alright.  I believe this was Andy Knoxs evogue debut.  Ok tag match.  I do like paradox they are good. Winner of the match Paradox Next match on its way.&lt;br /&gt;
CJ BANKS VS SERBIUS CJ getting heat before the match with a heel promo.  Serbius has got alot better.  I was impressed by him.  Good back and fourth action.  Typical heel vs face match.  Winner of the match CJ Banks. It’s now white collar wrestling.  And the match is…..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;joey-hayes-vs-erebus&quot;&gt;JOEY HAYES VS EREBUS&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An ok match.  Erebus was good.  This was a non title match.  Many pin falls attempts Winner of the match Joey Hayes We have the next match.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;rossy-rascal-vs-ward-the-butcher&quot;&gt;ROSSY RASCAL VS WARD THE BUTCHER&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was impressed by the butcher.  Good gimmick  Good back and fourth action.  I liked this one.  Winner of the match Rossy Rascal Next match&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;joey-hayes-vs-danny-hope-vs-big-t-justice-in-a-triple-threat-match-for-the-pcw-championship&quot;&gt;JOEY HAYES VS DANNY HOPE VS BIG T JUSTICE IN A TRIPLE THREAT MATCH FOR THE PCW CHAMPIONSHIP&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Good triple threat match.  Danny and Big T beat up Joey.  I thought this would have been the main event but I guess not.  I was expecting a new champion here.  Winner of the match and still PCW champion Joey Hayes Next match is women’s action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;lizzy-styles-vs-laura-rose-for-thr-pcw-womens-title&quot;&gt;LIZZY STYLES VS LAURA ROSE FOR THR PCW WOMENS TITLE&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Laura was alright.  Lizzy is a good heel.  Good to see a women’s match.  Laura impressed me.  She came close to winning the title.  Winner of the match and still PCW women’s champion Lizzy styles NOW ITS THE MAIN EVENT.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;cj-banks-and-danny-hope-vs-pl-dotson-and-lordy&quot;&gt;CJ BANKS AND DANNY HOPE VS PL DOTSON AND LORDY&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was surprised this way the main event.  Dotson was super over.  He was good Lordy was ok.  CJ is very good at getting heat.  Typical tag team match Winners of the match PL Dotson and Lordy It was an alright show and i give It 5 out 10.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately I feel this is the beginning of the end for PCW.  Only 50 people in attendance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t forget to go check out my YouTube channel the people’s wwe channel and like and subscribe IF YOU SMELL WHAT RICK THE ROCK IS COOKIN&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>ricky-j</name></author><summary type="html">PCW SPLIT DESCIONS 2019 REVIEW Show starts with sheik the sham calling out Steven Fludder. Steven beat up Sheik They will have a match on December 7th. If Steven loses he has to leave Preston.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ep82 – WWE Survivor Series Review (feat. The Queen of NE Pod)</title><link href="/podcasts/EP82/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ep82 – WWE Survivor Series Review (feat. The Queen of NE Pod)" /><published>2019-11-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-11-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/podcasts/EP82</id><content type="html" xml:base="/podcasts/EP82/"></content><author><name>john</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>