<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Johners Podcasting Network</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/</link><description>Recent content on Johners Podcasting Network</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><atom:link href="https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/aiwf-network/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/aiwf-network/</guid><description>AIWF Wrestling is the largest global network of pro wrestling promotions with 128 promotions in 44 countries, fighting champions around the globe and we&amp;rsquo;ve been in operation since 1992.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/bear-chocky-wrestling-recap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/bear-chocky-wrestling-recap/</guid><description>Join “The Bear” and “Chocky T” as we recap what’s going on in AEW and Impact! Wrestling.
Don’t forget to like, share &amp;amp; subscribe.
Part of the wrestling with Johnners Network.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/bob-culture/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/bob-culture/</guid><description>The Bob Culture Podcast is hosted by drummer, writer, indy commentator and nerd, Bobman discussing what’s new in the world of Pop Culture, Sports, WWE, AEW and the Local Music Scene along with special guests. Guests include the likes of Jim Ross, Jake Roberts, Road Warrior Animal, Kris Statlander, Tommy Dreamer, Ernie Hudson (Ghostbusters), Summer Rae, Anthony Bowens, and more!! The BCP loves to put the spotlight on up and coming local bands and indy wrestling talents.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/bucklebomb-entertainment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/bucklebomb-entertainment/</guid><description>Pro Wrestling Podcast, news and more topics to come! AEW, WWE, NWA, NJPW, NXT, Puro, indie promotions like GCW, GSW, New South, ICW and dozens more!</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/bwnl-courtside-chronicles/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/bwnl-courtside-chronicles/</guid><description>Hosted by the Basketball Wales National League Lead Reporter, Omer Hagomer. This podcast will give Basketball fans great access to the minds of incredible Players, Coaches and Executives.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/champs-out-last/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/champs-out-last/</guid><description>Two Friends chatting with no logic or end point about the crazy world of professional wrestling. Reviewing Old WWE PPV&amp;rsquo;s/Network specials one story arc at a time.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/chaos-theory/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/chaos-theory/</guid><description>This is the channel for the Chaos Theory podcast. I am a LIFELONG wrestling fan and US Army Veteran. This podcast is way more than just your average wrestling podcast. All things are open for discussion. Join me every week on a journey into pro wrestling from the major league to the Indy scene.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/chicagoland-championship-wrestling/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/chicagoland-championship-wrestling/</guid><description>Chicagoland Championship Wrestling features the best of Illinois, Indiana, Wisconsin and Michigan.
For details on upcoming shows, visit us at: https://chicagolandchampionshipwrestling.com/</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/chokeslam-wrestling-report/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/chokeslam-wrestling-report/</guid><description>Hi my name is Henry Valentin aka &amp;lsquo;The Ultimate One&amp;rsquo;.
This channel was made to give wrestling fans the latest news &amp;amp; results from the top wrestling promotions. This includes WWE, NJPW ROH, TNA and last but not least AEW. I have been watching wrestling since 1974.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been through the Bruno Sammartino and Harley Race Era. To Hulkamania and The Four Horsemen Days. I have plenty of knowledge. I hope you guys click on the subscribe button to the channel.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/da-call-up/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/da-call-up/</guid><description>What’s Da Call Up it’s a place where your inner nerd can run free without judgment where life takes a back seat and we can just relax and enjoy the goodtimes</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/dan-sinasac/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/dan-sinasac/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/death-match-russell/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/death-match-russell/</guid><description>I Interview the best Indy Pro Wrestling Wrestlers Female Wrestlers Managers Announcers Wrestling Promoters Companies I cover CZW IWA GCW JPCW H2O OPW VOW EHF and more!</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/dkw-academy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/dkw-academy/</guid><description>DKW has a rich history of being one of the longest running training schools in the entire UK, producing the likes of current SmackDown superstar Elton Prince, current SmackDown General Manager, Nick Aldis and current WWE Commentator and former Intercontinental and Tag Team Champion, Wade Barrett.
Started in 1998, DKW has recently celebrated its 25th Anniversary. The academy is at the forefront of everything they do, and their live shows are great fun for all the family.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/doa-bookerman-podcast/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/doa-bookerman-podcast/</guid><description>From the Bookerman of DOA Wrestling, featuring interviews with wrestling personalities, discussion, historical reviews and the Bookerman attempts to re-book some of wrestling&amp;rsquo;s best and worst moments!</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/ewokk-jb-show/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/ewokk-jb-show/</guid><description>‘Ewokk and JB’ Show is two wrestling personalities, sharing stories amongst guest and dropping knowledge to better the business they are in.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/george-mckay/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/george-mckay/</guid><description>#TheHost George Mckay gives you the very best that Straight Talk Wrestling Podcast has to offer EVERY Thursday NIGHT @ 7:30 EST that is always available for listen and download on #Podbean, #Stitcher, #Spotify, #IHeartRadio, #ITunes &amp;amp; #GooglePlayMusic. Also, be sure to smash that like, follow, retweet or subscribe button on all the rest of my social media platforms including #Facebook, #Instagram &amp;amp; #Twitter!
We speak the truth about all things wrestling coming from the hardnosed perspective of long time wrestling fans!</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/half-decent/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/half-decent/</guid><description>Rapper, Producer, Thought Provoking Party Starter!!! For Bookings, Features, Instrumentals Or Remix&amp;rsquo;s Email info@halfdecentmusic.com</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/hidden-gem-hunters/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/hidden-gem-hunters/</guid><description>&amp;lsquo;Hidden Gem Hunters: The Search for Wrestling&amp;rsquo;s Forgotten Classics&amp;rsquo; is a brand new podcast where former British professional wrestler Peter Nixon and promoter of DOA Wrestling Alec Burnitt will look back on historical Pay Per View events in an attempt to uncover the best matches that have been lost in time.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/jofo-in-the-ring/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/jofo-in-the-ring/</guid><description>Frank Jofo &amp;amp; Kyle Morin &amp;amp; Jeremy Prophet Speak About All Wrestling, All The Time. Every TUESDAY 7PM on the JOFO IN THE RING YOUTUBE CHANNEL SUBSCRIBE LIKE AND FOLLOW ON YOUTUBE-TWITTER-INSTAGRAM-TIK TOK ETC
Linktree</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/john-scott/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/john-scott/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been a massive fan of Professional Wrestling since the early 90&amp;rsquo;s. However I remember watching British Wrestling on ITV&amp;rsquo;s The World of Sports with my Nan, every Saturday afternoon in the mid to late 80&amp;rsquo;s.
If I were to be put on the spot I would have to say that Ric Flair and Daniel Bryan are my favourite wrestlers ever. I was inspired to start the Wrestling With Johners Podcast after my trip to WrestleMania 34 in New Orleans, with the first episode going out in November 2018.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/justin-guilmette/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/justin-guilmette/</guid><description>Guilmy Talks is a podcast talking to interesting people and having fun while doing it.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/keepin-it-kayfabe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/keepin-it-kayfabe/</guid><description>‘Keepin’ it Kayfabe’ a 4CNRS Pro Wrestling Podcast, with exclusive interviews, UK Independent show reviews, Gossip from around the mainstream promotions, PPV highs &amp;amp; lows from AEW &amp;amp; WWE. Plus, a deep dive into turning a negative into a positive. Along with the occasional Big Screen movie review… this is your spoiler warning</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/kj-pro-wrestling/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/kj-pro-wrestling/</guid><description>For all your WWE/AEW wrestling news reviews and fantasy booking so for everything wrestling stay tuned and check out https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/knights-of-the-squared-circle/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/knights-of-the-squared-circle/</guid><description>Knights of the Squared Circle is a weekly radio show and podcast hosted by Ryan and Ariena Knight featuring interviews with Canada&amp;rsquo;s most talented independent wrestlers and a variety of wrestling figures. Available live every Sunday at 12 pm est on Coyote 103 and our website www.knightsofthesc.com with replays on Facebook, and Spotify.
Knights of the Squared Circle also host VIP sessions before live events featuring tapings of Knights with talent working that event, Q&amp;amp;A for the fans, giveaways and more!</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/kurt-johansson/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/kurt-johansson/</guid><description>The Kurt Johansson Show
Bringing you wrestling interviews from all around the world. Host of Fierce Females Focus. Various wrestling related topics.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/kwo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/kwo/</guid><description>Welcome to a new world of Wrestling Podcasts,the kWo! Hosted by Wrestling Rainman Dill Kimbo and his brother and one of the hosts of TrainPop Culture, Matt Kimbo, enjoy their rants and raves in the world of WWE, AEW and Impact Wrestling!</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/kyles-wrestling/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/kyles-wrestling/</guid><description>My name is Kyle and I am the host of Kyle&amp;rsquo;s Wrestling channel. I&amp;rsquo;m a huge fan of Professional Wrestling and love to interview wrestlers and people within the industry.
I also love to watch and review pro wrestling from around the world &amp;amp; you can hear my thoughts on some of my favourite wrestling matches, promotions and shows right here, on the Johners Podcasting Network.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/lewis-carlan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/lewis-carlan/</guid><description>I run the Alliance Pro Wrestling Network, host Shooting Up North on The Impact Lounge and Co host MLW Rewind.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/lexi-helms/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/lexi-helms/</guid><description>Come and join the Prin of the With Johners Family for some good old fashioned hospitality, as the drinks machine is fired up, snacks are laid out and the comfy chairs are available as Lexi Helms invites you in for a chat and a catch up over a brew. Grappuchino Thoughts discusses everything and nothing to do with the crazy world of wrestling, with the odd detour into life, football and the daily grind.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/lucha-libre-and-laughs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/lucha-libre-and-laughs/</guid><description>Lucha Libre &amp;amp; Laughs brings pro-wrestling and stand up comedy together for one great show in Denver, Colorado!</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/matt-bayliss/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/matt-bayliss/</guid><description>Harrassed Eddie Dennis with an inflatable sheep, trained with Pete Dunne, spine adjusted by Sabu, Chris Hero nearly ate my baby and hugged the hardcore legend&amp;hellip; And now appearing on the Wrestling With Johners website.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/michael-jolly/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/michael-jolly/</guid><description>I’ve been a huge wrestling fan since the mid 80s with ITV’s The World of Sport then thanks to Sky TV I was introduced to WWF/WWE &amp;amp; WCW. Now in my 40s I’m loving what is now available to watch from around the world.
I’ve had the privilege to watch some fantastic British Wrestling over the past 10 years which has led to me working with some incredible wrestlers as well as dabbling in commentary, being a backstage runner &amp;amp; writing the shows.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/my-britwres-journey/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/my-britwres-journey/</guid><description>Chris Lappin is joined by stars of the British Wrestling scene to discuss their wrestling journey from fan to their 1st match, the evolution of their gimmicks and created Fantasy Cards using only wrestlers they&amp;rsquo;ve worked with.
Featuring stars of NXT UK, Progress Wrestling, NGW, Britannia Wrestling Promotions, FutureShock Wrestling, North Wrestling, TNT Extreme Wrestling, Sacrifice Wrestling, Odyssey Pro Wrestling and Wrestle Island.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/nik-towers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/nik-towers/</guid><description>Hosted by Nik Towers. You don&amp;rsquo;t know where you&amp;rsquo;re going till you know where you&amp;rsquo;ve been. Looking through the history of British and American wrestling.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/off-the-top-rope/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/off-the-top-rope/</guid><description>Watch Johners Podcasting Network&amp;rsquo;s Off The Top Rope with everybody&amp;rsquo;s boy, Ty Asbury. As he brings all the slams, with some of the top interviews in pro wrestling.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/passion-universe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/passion-universe/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;It is in the presence of others that we discover who we are.&amp;rdquo; Passion Universe is a platform that is all about the power of human connection. Values such as inclusion, diversity, and representation are at the forefront of the mission statement.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/power-hour/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/power-hour/</guid><description>The Power Hour with C Red and Steve Ahrendt.
A Weekly Episodic Wrestling talk show featuring The Urban Sensation C.Red and The One and only Steve Ahrendt. Join us each week for great interviews, comedic banter and some of the best storytelling on any Wrestling Podcast format. Available exclusively on The Johners Podcasting Network!!!</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/pro-darin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/pro-darin/</guid><description>I hail from Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. I have been watching pro wrestling since the mid-1990s, and started watching WWE more often in the late 1990s when the &amp;ldquo;Attitude Era&amp;rdquo; was still going on. I would then check out indie wrestling shows, as well as shows affiliated with companies such as the National Wrestling Alliance as soon as we stepped foot into the 21st century. When it comes to reading articles, I might throw in some references to shows I&amp;rsquo;ve watched in the past (whether it is or isn&amp;rsquo;t from a WWE show).</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/refin-it-up-with-brian-hebner/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/refin-it-up-with-brian-hebner/</guid><description>Every Wednesday at 9AM EST Current IMPACT WRESTLING referee @babyhebner and @_ringsiderant cover your favourite wrestlers in a unique way #12.3 Follow @RefinItUp on Twitter as well #123</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/rewind-recap-relive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/rewind-recap-relive/</guid><description>Welcome everyone to Rewind Recap Relive! Where Legends and Rising Stars Meet each week to discuss their careers, road stories, advice on breaking into the pro wrestling business, and so much more!</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/ringside-rant/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/ringside-rant/</guid><description>Ringside Rant is The ELITE in all wrestling nostalgic podcasting!!! EVERY FRIDAY at 9am EST on all podcast platforms and now The Johners Podcasting Network. RJ and Justin rant about the good old days and some not so good days in the world of professional wrestling.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/rope-break/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/rope-break/</guid><description>Rope Break is the number one outlet to the world of Professional Wrestling covering WWE, AEW, Impact. Subscribe to YouTube. #theoriginalropebreak</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/scottish-wrestling-network/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/scottish-wrestling-network/</guid><description>The Scottish Wrestling Network Podcast hosted by Billy Strachan.
Interviewing the new faces and veterans of the Scottish wrestling scene with some bonuses thrown in for good measure.
Linktree</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/scumbags-of-wrestling/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/scumbags-of-wrestling/</guid><description>We are a group of wrestling fans who enjoy going to local independent wrestling shows. We support Smash Wrestling primarily. Our podcast focuses on the independent wrestling scene in Ontario, plus mainstream organizations such as WWE, Impact Wrestling, Ring of Honor and New Japan.
We have a very active group page on Facebook. Our podcast is available on over 10 outlets including; Spotify, Stitcher, iTunes and Google Podcasts</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/shootin-sht/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/shootin-sht/</guid><description>Join DDJ, “The Premiere” Joey K, and “Da Hot One” Jay Menacho as they “shoot” on random wrestling topics, such as “Who Is Mr Summerslam?” and “Was the CM Punk pop the biggest pop ever?” New episodes come out every week.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/sky-creates/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/sky-creates/</guid><description>I’m Sky I’m 20 years old. I got into wrestling about two years ago.
On my channel you can find Vlogs of shows I’ve been to, reviews, predictions and interviews spotlighting talent all across the world as well as much more.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/snap-crackle-and-cheap-pops/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/snap-crackle-and-cheap-pops/</guid><description>Pro Wrestling 4U owner Phil Woodvine gets together with his wrestling pals to give you some great stories, insider info, backstage goss, s***s and giggles. Enjoy the show !!
Check out our back catalogue of wrestling shows over at PW4UOnDemand.co.uk</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/steven-brads-talk-n-wrestling/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/steven-brads-talk-n-wrestling/</guid><description>Pro Wrestling fun for all ages! A 45-year old (Brad Marcus) and a 10 year-old (Steven Spice) discuss pro wrestling, review wrestling-related cartoons/shows/movies and a whole lot of hijinx!</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/such-good-shoot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/such-good-shoot/</guid><description>We are a group of dudes watching and talking about wrestling old, new, bad, and even occasionally good. Join us every Thursday at 10:05pm to see what we are up to!</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/tea-and-tights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/tea-and-tights/</guid><description>Dan and Andy round up all the latest from the British Wrestling scene, with show reviews, previews and all the latest news, from the likes of Rev Pro Wrestling, Progress Wrestling, ICW, TNT Extreme Wrestling and many more. Weekly episodes plus the occasional specials with interviews from British wrestling talents, promoters and more.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/the-everett-lee-show/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/the-everett-lee-show/</guid><description>The Everett Lee Show delivers a “Shot Of Entertainment,” with candid conversations from Independent Wrestlers, Independent Film Makers and people in the entertainment industry.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/the-soul-sessions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/the-soul-sessions/</guid><description>Everyone has a story and every story has a beginning, come witness the stories of wrestlers, companies and more around the world, with your host who is always suited up: Soul. So, grab a drink and get ready for The Soul Sessions.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/time-to-fight/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/time-to-fight/</guid><description>A wrestling podcast, hosted by award winning ring announcer Matthew Terry. We try to be different and we try to keep everything highbrow. Try &amp;hellip; Posted every Tuesday.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/toilet-side-wrestling-talk/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/toilet-side-wrestling-talk/</guid><description>Interviews with top wrestling stars on the independent wrestling circuit&amp;hellip;and some stars from larger promotions&amp;hellip;with a humorous twist!</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/tom-talks-rubbish/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/tom-talks-rubbish/</guid><description>Conversations with people involved in the media about how they keep their fandom for wrestling alive through their work.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/tornado-tag/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/tornado-tag/</guid><description>A wrestling podcast that talks about wrestling history and stories and shows love to the indy scene. No tag rope needed.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/tree-hill-wrestling-federation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/tree-hill-wrestling-federation/</guid><description>Where the world&amp;rsquo;s of One Tree Hill and Wrestling collide&amp;hellip; Welcome to the FIRST EVER podcast that combines One Tree Hill and Professional Wrestling BROTHER!
Join us weekly on Mondays as we watch through the WWE Attitude Era and every single episode of One Tree Hill, and try to appreciate each other&amp;rsquo;s most loved shows!</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/turnbuckle-arms-podcast/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/turnbuckle-arms-podcast/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new Bar in town!
Welcome to the turnbuckle arms, where the banter flows like wine and the topics are as fresh as an ice cold pint. So pull up a chair, grab yourself a glass and welcome your hosts&amp;hellip;. “The Brew’d.&amp;quot;
Part of the Wrestling With Johners Podcast family, with a group of friends talking wrestling, the latest news from #WWE #AEW #NXT &amp;amp; reliving the yesteryears of the sport.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/turning-heel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/turning-heel/</guid><description>Chris, Griz and Robert talk about all kinds of topics in this wacky, weird world that is Pro Wrestling.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/united-wrestling/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/united-wrestling/</guid><description>Professional Wrestling promotion founded in 2019 and based in Oxford, Oxfordshire. We pride ourselves on being all inclusive! Labels mean nothing when you step through a United door. It is all about the best story telling, with the best wrestling featuring the very best the UK has to offer. While providing a platform for newer talent to showcase what they can do. We run out of home at the Tap Social Movement&amp;rsquo;s Taproom in North Hinksey.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/untitled-wrestling-podcast/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/untitled-wrestling-podcast/</guid><description>The Untitled Wrestling Podcast is a no holds barred pro wrestling podcast, presented by a group of friends from the far reaches of the UK. Weekly shows covering WWE, AEW, NJPW, Impact, NWA and more. Recorded and live special episodes, live streams, gaming communities and watch along parties are all available throughout various social media outlets.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/whaddya-say-with-ddj/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/whaddya-say-with-ddj/</guid><description>Whaddya Say With DDJ is a long form interview style show where I interview pro wrestlers and those associated with pro wrestling. Most of my interviews are with those who wrestle in the Chicagoland area. Former guests include John Bullard, Tim Storm, C Red, Paragon, amongst others.
I’ve been a pro wrestling fan for over 30 years. My all time favorites include: Ric Flair, Ricky Steamboat, Randy Savage, Steve Austin, and Kurt Angle.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/what-do-you-call-it/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/what-do-you-call-it/</guid><description>What Do You Call It? Podcast! is run by a fan who&amp;rsquo;s loved the world of pro wrestling for over 20 years.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/where-is-my-mind/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/where-is-my-mind/</guid><description>A deep dive into the life and mind of Curtis Rich, over the last 9 years as Ontario Gumby and content producer for Professional Wrestling. This podcast is my way of reconnecting with people I’ve met along the way. Getting to know them on a more personal level &amp;amp; updating his fans on life.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/wombtravel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/wombtravel/</guid><description>Hi! I’m Jordan. On my channel you will find wrestling related content and travel videos, from my time traveling the world
My channel will also offer Interviews with some of the biggest and best names from the world of Professional Wrestling. Including names from the WWE, IMPACT Wrestling, AEW and the Independent scene
You will also find videos from my times at wrestling events
I hope that you enjoy my channel on the Johners Podcasting Network</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/world-elite/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/world-elite/</guid><description>World Elite Podcast is hosted by die-hard wrestling fans Dylan Hebert, Marcus Hay and Jordan Johnson. As they strive to deliver quality wrestling content, every single week.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/wrestle-rage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/authors/wrestle-rage/</guid><description>The &amp;ldquo;Rich Cannon&amp;rdquo; Curtis Rich-Cannon, &amp;ldquo;The Wizard Of West Texas&amp;rdquo; JMB, &amp;amp; Charlie &amp;ldquo;Blueprint&amp;rdquo; Bruno weekly as they rundown the best &amp;amp; worst of Professional Wrestling!!</description></item></channel></rss>