<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Johners Podcasting Network</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/</link><description>Recent content on Johners Podcasting Network</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Championship Matches At The Royal Rumble</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/dan-sinasac/2023-01-14-championship-matches-at-the-royal-rumble/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/dan-sinasac/2023-01-14-championship-matches-at-the-royal-rumble/</guid><description>Championship Matches At The Royal Rumble The Royal Rumble is one of the greatest brain children of WWE. The creativity and pure chaos of the match made it an instant hit. It has led to the Royal Rumble beginning the road to Wrestlemania and becoming a staple of WWE programming.
The prize of winning a WWE Championship match is what all in the Rumble match aspire to. It is what drives the competitors, but that dream is one that can come early for some.</description></item><item><title>Issue 53 Shows of December 31, 2022 January 6, 2023</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2023-01-08-issue-53-shows-of-december-31-2022january-6-2023/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2023-01-08-issue-53-shows-of-december-31-2022january-6-2023/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
So This Is the New Year… Happy New Year! Now that we have stepped foot into 2023, are you ready for what’s in store for the pro wrestling world this year? I’m definitely ready as you can see with the dead giveaway being that I’m starting off the second year of Pro-Darin. Let’s take a look back at the action that I checked out this week, shall we?</description></item><item><title>Issue 52 Shows of December 24-30, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2023-01-06-issue-52-shows-of-december-24-30-2022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2023-01-06-issue-52-shows-of-december-24-30-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
RIP Don West ![don west](/assets/posts/2023-01-06/don west.jpg){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Not too long ago, I noted that Jim Ross and Jerry “The King” Lawler were my favorite commentating duo in pro wrestling. Those two aren’t the only ones that are my favorites when it comes to announcers and commentators in pro wrestling.
Another one of my favorites is from TNA (nowadays Impact Wrestling), and his name is Don West. West not only worked as a commentator on Impact, but—outside the pro wrestling world—he also worked a host for Shop At Home, as well as sports talk show host in Nashville, Tennessee and the director of sales and marketing for an ice hockey team in Wenatchee, Washington.</description></item><item><title>Royal Rumble Surprises</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/dan-sinasac/2023-01-06-royal-rumble-surprises/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/dan-sinasac/2023-01-06-royal-rumble-surprises/</guid><description>Royal Rumble Surprises The holidays are over. The time with family and friends is over and now we can all get into full Royal Rumble mode. It is only a few weeks away and the wrestling world is already buzzing.
One of the reasons for this buzz is the potential surprises for the Rumble match. Every year there are spots earmarked, in both matches, for some surprise entrants. It is a huge selling point of the Royal Rumble and one that causes much speculation.</description></item><item><title>Issue 48 Shows of November 26-December 2, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-12-27-issue-48-shows-of-november-26-december-2-2022/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-12-27-issue-48-shows-of-november-26-december-2-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Progress Chapter 143: The Deadly Viper Tour – Codename: Sidewinder We’re kicking things off with a belated Progress recap. Plus, even though a sidewinder is a type of snake, I—for some reason—think of “Rogue Trip: Vacation 2012” (a comedic parody of the “Twisted Metal” franchise) where one of the vehicles is named Sidewinder.
Videogame nostalgia aside, the 143rd chapter of Progress took place on October 9, 2022 at the O2 Arena in Manchester, England in the United Kingdom; it also served as the fourth part of the Deadly Viper Tour.</description></item><item><title>Issue 49 Shows of December 3-9, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-12-27-issue-49-shows-of-december-3-9-2022/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-12-27-issue-49-shows-of-december-3-9-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Progress Chapter 144: The Deadly Viper Tour – Codename: Snake Charmer Let’s kick things off with a belated Progress recap!
The 144th chapter of Progress took place at the Tramshed in Cardiff, Wales in the United Kingdom; it also served as the tail end of the Deadly Viper Tour. Hosting the event was Session Moth Martina who took over for Simon Miller that day, and she did very well doing the ring announcing duties as well as have fun, drinking games and all.</description></item><item><title>Issue 50 Shows of December 10-16, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-12-27-issue-50-shows-of-december-10-16-2022/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-12-27-issue-50-shows-of-december-10-16-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Fifty-Fifty Share Alike Yes, this is my 50th issue of Pro-Darin. I’m so glad to have my issues on Wrestling With Johners, and I thank you readers—including “Johners” himself John Scott for having my articles on his website—for joining me from when it began as a ten-issue sampler on my Facebook page all the way to Wrestling With Johners including the podcast’s FB group page where I often post them before they end up in the articles section of his website.</description></item><item><title>Issue 51 Shows of December 17-23, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-12-27-issue-51-shows-of-december-17-23-2022/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-12-27-issue-51-shows-of-december-17-23-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
ICW Fear &amp;amp; Loathing XIV I was unable to do any belated recaps this week (mainly because, as the saying goes, “‘tis the season”), but I am going to kick off this week’s issue with ICW Fear &amp;amp; Loathing XIV. F&amp;amp;L took place at the Garage in Glasgow, Scotland in the United Kingdom on November 20. It was the second time, for me, to check out ICW’s F&amp;amp;L with the exception that this year’s event took place for one night only instead of two nights like last year’s F&amp;amp;L; I definitely enjoyed my first F&amp;amp;L last year, and I was hungry for this year’s F&amp;amp;L like dogs going after a Christmas turkey in “A Christmas Story.</description></item><item><title>Overrated/Underrated Stars of The New Generation</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/dan-sinasac/2022-12-04-overrated-underrated-stars-of-the-new-generation/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/dan-sinasac/2022-12-04-overrated-underrated-stars-of-the-new-generation/</guid><description>Overrated/Underrated Stars of The New Generation The early 1990s was a time of much trepidation in WWE. The stars of the Golden Era had been committing a mass exodus from the company, and newer, unproven talent took their place.
It was not known what would become of WWE and the ripple effect of that era is still being felt today.
During this era, we had every gimmick imaginable. This was the time of every worker having a job.</description></item><item><title>Issue 45 Shows of November 5-11, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-11-27-issue-45-shows-of-november-5-11-2022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-11-27-issue-45-shows-of-november-5-11-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Pro Wrestling Noah Ariake Triumph – The Return – Pro-Wrestling Love Forever 3 ~ Triumph ~ Even though I was unable to finish up a Progress chapter (I’ll recap it in the next issue by the way), I’m still kicking things off with another Pro Wrestling Noah bonus. Pro Wrestling Noah’s “The Return” (full name “Pro Wrestling Noah Ariake Triumph – The Return – Pro-Wrestling Love Forever 3 ~ Triumph ~”) took place on October 30 at the Ariake Arena in Tokyo, Japan; it was the same venue that hosted volleyball during the 2020 Summer Olympics and wheelchair basketball during the 2020 Summer Paralympics.</description></item><item><title>Issue 46 Shows of November 12-18, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-11-27-issue-46-shows-of-november-12-18-2022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-11-27-issue-46-shows-of-november-12-18-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Progress Chapter 142: The Deadly Viper Tour – Codename: California Mountain Snake As promised, I’m kicking things off with a belated Progress recap.
The 142nd chapter of Progress took place on September 25 at the O2 Academy in Birmingham, England in the United Kingdom; it was the third event that was part of the Deadly Viper Tour.
![deadly viper tour](/assets/posts/2022-11-27/deadly viper tour.jpg){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Nine matches were on the card that day with the last four being championship matches; not only did we see the champions in action, but we also saw competitors either visiting (such as those from other companies such as wXw and AEW) or returning to Progress—along with a long-awaited rivalry in the form of a tag team bout—as you’ll see shortly in the results.</description></item><item><title>Issue 47 Shows of November 19-25, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-11-27-issue-47-shows-of-november-19-25-2022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-11-27-issue-47-shows-of-november-19-25-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Progress: Return of the Fly Cue the CDK theme song because it’s time to kick things off with a Progress recap.
![return of the fly](/assets/posts/2022-11-27/return of the fly.jpg){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Return of the Fly took place on September 27 at the Dome in London, England in the United Kingdom, a few days after the 142nd chapter of Progress took place. You may notice that it doesn’t have a chapter number next to it, mainly because it’s a special event or “subchapter” if you will.</description></item><item><title>Great Solo Performances in Survivor Series History</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/dan-sinasac/2022-11-26-great-solo-performances-in-survivor-series-history/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/dan-sinasac/2022-11-26-great-solo-performances-in-survivor-series-history/</guid><description>Great Solo Performances in Survivor Series History The Survivor Series is one of the longest-standing traditions in WWE history. Every November team warfare enters our homes and the results have, usually, been great. The team dynamic is one that WWE doesn’t explore often and we are given some interesting pairings.
The Survivor Series has always been more about the team game than anything. The importance of working together is always highlighted going into the show but that doesn’t mean a solo performance can’t shine above.</description></item><item><title>Survivor Series Championship Matches</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/dan-sinasac/2022-11-26-survivor-series-championship-matches/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/dan-sinasac/2022-11-26-survivor-series-championship-matches/</guid><description>Survivor Series Championship Matches The American Thanksgiving tradition of the Survivor Series has been a staple of WWE programming for decades. Compiling teams of 4/5 wrestlers, teams go to war with each other to establish their dominance over the company. It was a great idea and one that has continued to this day.
The concept of the Survivor Series has generally remained the same. The importance of team warfare is always the driving force behind the PPV, but that doesn’t mean the show was a one-trick pony.</description></item><item><title>Issue 44 Shows of October 29-November 4, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-11-11-issue-44-shows-of-october-29-november-4-2022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-11-11-issue-44-shows-of-october-29-november-4-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Progress Chapter 141: Handshakes and Cheeseburgers We kick things off with a belated Progress recap. For some reason, the chapter title “Handshakes and Cheeseburgers” has me thinking of the “Lashing Out with Lash Legend” segment on an episode of NXT where Grayson Waller poked fun of the NXT veterans (such as Johnny Gargano and Tommaso Ciampa) for being rewarded a hotdog and a handshake during their indie wrestling tenures.</description></item><item><title>Issue 43 Shows of October 22-28, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-11-10-issue-43-shows-of-october-22-28-2022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-11-10-issue-43-shows-of-october-22-28-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
wXw Shortcut To the Top 2022 Kicking things off with a belated recap, let’s take a look back at wXw’s rendition of the Royal Rumble known as Shortcut To the Top!
wXw Shortcut To the Top 2022 took place on August 6, 2022 at the Turbinenhalle in Oberhausen, Germany. Not only did the 30-wrestler battle royal occur that night, but so did four other matches that took place prior; two of them were championship matches.</description></item><item><title>Who Can Topple Roman Reigns?</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/dan-sinasac/2022-11-09-who-can-topple-roman-reigns/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/dan-sinasac/2022-11-09-who-can-topple-roman-reigns/</guid><description>Who Can Topple Roman Reigns? Roman Reigns is approaching god-like status in WWE. He has held both World Championships for the better part of this year, and has carried the Universal strap for over two years! Add to that the fact that the last time he was pinned was in 2019 and he has cemented himself as the top dog in the world of wrestling.
With all of the opponents, Reigns has run through the championship contenders pool is running shallow.</description></item><item><title>North Wrestling “The World At Large”</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/michael-jolly/2022-11-03-north-wrestling-world-at-large/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/michael-jolly/2022-11-03-north-wrestling-world-at-large/</guid><description>{:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Since it’s birth on to the British wrestling scene back in 2016, North Wrestling has brought to us some of the best this business has to offer, whether that be home grown or international, there’s something for anyone which is why North has become a firm favourite to fans and wrestlers alike. Having been part of the incredible atmosphere, surrounded by these amazing people it’s no wonder why this company is a fantastic night out at the Anarchy Brewery Co, Newcastle and always SOLD OUT.</description></item><item><title>Issue 41/Shows of October 8-14, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-10-26-issue-41-shows-of-october-8-14-2022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-10-26-issue-41-shows-of-october-8-14-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
wXw We Love Wrestling 35 We’re kicking things off with a belated recap.
The 35th episode of wXw We Love Wrestling took place on July 16, 2022 at the Batschkapp in Frankfurt, Germany. It was the last episode prior to Dead End which would take place later that month.
Six matches were on the card including two six-man tag team matches that I enjoyed. The first half of the show, consisting of three one-on-one matches, was lukewarm until the second half of the show turned everything up a notch or two.</description></item><item><title>Issue 42 Shows of October 15-21, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-10-26-issue-42-shows-of-october-15-21-2022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-10-26-issue-42-shows-of-october-15-21-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Progress Chapter 140: Wrestling, Golf, Madrid In That Order We kick things off with a belated recap of Progress Chapter 140: Wrestling, Golf, Madrid In That Order. Personally, if it were me, my three things would be wrestling, NASCAR, and any of the Philadelphia sports teams in that order…lol…
![progress cardiff](/assets/posts/2022-10-26/progress wrestling golf madrid.jpg){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
The 140th chapter of Progress took place at the Tramshed in Cardiff, Wales in the United Kingdom, one night after Clash At the Castle and ICW Whit’s Occurrin’?</description></item><item><title>Tag Team Break-Ups</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/dan-sinasac/2022-10-26-tag-team-break-ups/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/dan-sinasac/2022-10-26-tag-team-break-ups/</guid><description>Tag Team Break-Ups Unless your name is Vince McMahon, tag team wrestling has always held a special place in your heart. Sure, the singles division is what drives most wrestling companies, but the tag team division has provided just as many memorable moments and great matches.
These tag teams can show some tremendous charisma and become one of the best parts of the roster. They are a great way to showcase younger talent and build experience in the greener athletes on the roster.</description></item><item><title>Great Moments From PPVs Outside The United States</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/dan-sinasac/2022-10-21-great-moments-from-ppvs-outside-the-united-states/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/dan-sinasac/2022-10-21-great-moments-from-ppvs-outside-the-united-states/</guid><description>Great Moments From PPVs Outside The United States WWE has always been a tradition in the United States. Starting as the Capitol Wrestling Corporation the company made its name in the North Eastern United States. Its popularity continued to grow into the worldwide leader in sports entertainment that we know and love/hate today.
As much as its roots have been set in the United States there have been some great moments that have taken place outside of it.</description></item><item><title>Issue 39 Shows of September 24-30, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-10-13-issue-39-shows-of-september-24-30-2022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-10-13-issue-39-shows-of-september-24-30-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Safety First Before getting to the shows, I hope that everyone on the east coast in the United States stayed safe during Hurricane Ian. This issue is dedicated those that were affected by the wrath of the hurricane.
Progress Chapter 138: The Deadly Viper Tour—Codename: Cottonmouth We’ll kick things off with a belated recap as promised.
The 138th chapter of Progress Wrestling took place on August 14, 2022 at the Boiler Shop in Newcastle, England in the United Kingdom; it served as part 2 of the Deadly Viper Tour.</description></item><item><title>Issue 40 Shows of October 1-7, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-10-13-issue-40-shows-of-october-1-7-2022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-10-13-issue-40-shows-of-october-1-7-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Pro Wrestling Noah Grand Ship 2022 Let’s kick off the 40th issue (yep, you read correctly!) of Pro-Darin with a bonus, shall we?
The bonus event I chose for this issue is Pro Wrestling Noah Grand Ship 2022; I watched this event days before we lost Japanese pro wrestler, martial artist, politician and New Japan Pro Wrestling founder Antonio Inoki, and also days before our very own Johners went to see New Japan Pro Wrestling’s Royal Quest II in his home country of the United Kingdom.</description></item><item><title>Best Canadian Wrestlers in Professional Wrestling</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/dan-sinasac/2022-10-07-best-canadian-wrestlers-in-professional-wrestling/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/dan-sinasac/2022-10-07-best-canadian-wrestlers-in-professional-wrestling/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Best Canadian Wrestlers in Professional Wrestling&amp;rdquo; The reputation of professional wrestling and Canada has been well documented. Known to have their own agenda, during PPVs, Canadian fans have produced some truly memorable moments. Anyone who is anyone can remember the tremendous reaction during the iconic Hulk Hogan and The Rock contest from Wrestlemania 18.
Canada has always had a special place in professional wrestling. The passion shown by its fans rivals no one in the wrestling world and The Great White North has produced some of the greatest to ever step between the ropes.</description></item><item><title>Overrated &amp; Underrated Stars of the Attitude Era</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/dan-sinasac/2022-10-04-over-underrated-stars-of-the-attitude-era/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/dan-sinasac/2022-10-04-over-underrated-stars-of-the-attitude-era/</guid><description>Overrated &amp;amp; Underrated Stars of the Attitude Era The Attitude Era was a watershed moment for WWE. Since the early 1980s, the company held a monopoly over professional wrestling. It was happenstance that pushed them into a lull and after a while began producing less than stellar wrestling. This allowed WCW to move up in the ratings and become the most popular organization in North America.
As a result of the rating losses, Vince was forced to evolve his product.</description></item><item><title>Issue 37 Shows of September 10-16, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-09-26-issue-37-shows-of-september-10-16-2022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-09-26-issue-37-shows-of-september-10-16-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
wXw We Love Wrestling 34 As promised, I’m kicking things off with two belated recaps.
The 34th episode of wXw We Love Wrestling took place on June 12, 2022 at the Turbinenhalle in Oberhausen, Germany, hours after the previous episode occurred.
{:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Besides the aftermath of Broken Rules which took place on both episode of We Love Wrestling at the same venue, this episode also had Ahura returning to wXw after being suspended due to his actions at wXw Anniversary XXI.</description></item><item><title>Issue 38 Shows of September 17-23, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-09-26-issue-38-shows-of-september-17-23-2022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-09-26-issue-38-shows-of-september-17-23-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Progress Chapter 137: The Deadly Viper Tour—Codename: Copperhead Again, I’m kicking things off with a belated recap.
The 137th chapter of Progress Wrestling took place at the O2 Academy in Sheffield, England in the United Kingdom; it served as the first event of the Deadly Viper Tour. Eight matches were on the card; half of them were championship matches, and the other half were exhibition matches.
{:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}</description></item><item><title>Issue 36 Shows of September 4-10, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-09-16-issue-36-shows-of-september-4-10-2022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-09-16-issue-36-shows-of-september-4-10-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
British Invasion This Labor Day weekend (P.S.: I hope you’re enjoying your Labor Day weekend in the United States as much as I am!), we saw the WWE head to the United Kingdom for a premium live event (or pay-per-view event if you’re old school like me) and then wrap things up with NXT clashing with NXT UK—as well as Raw and SmackDown—in the United States.
Before I continue, I want to note that Queen Elizabeth II died this week, ending her reign as Queen of the United Kingdom that lasted for 70 years and 214 days; all hearts and condolences go out to the royal family.</description></item><item><title>Issue 35 Shows of August 28-September 3, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-09-15-issue-35-shows-of-august-28-september-3-2022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-09-15-issue-35-shows-of-august-28-september-3-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
ICW Fight Club Forgoing the intro (remember not too long ago when I promised to skip intros in select issues?), our first stop is the GPWA in Glasgow, Scotland in the United Kingdom for an episode of ICW Fight Club.
The fallout from Shug’s Hoose Party 7 took place on this week’s episode of ICW Fight Club. It kicked things off with something that ADM may have planned in the future even with the Manifesto.</description></item><item><title>Issue 34 Shows of August 21-27, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-09-14-issue-34-shows-of-august-21-27-2022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-09-14-issue-34-shows-of-august-21-27-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Better Late Than Never As promised, I’m back with a belated look back at three shows—with “NXT” in their names—as well as night 2 of ICW Shug’s Hoose Party 7. Off we go!
ICW Shug’s Hoose Party 7—Night 2 Our first stop is the O2 Academy in Glasgow, Scotland in the United Kingdom for night #2 of ICW Shug’s Hoose Party 7!
{:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Night #2 of SHP7 took place on July 30, 2022; like night #1, night #2 also had eight matches on the card.</description></item><item><title>Issue 33 Shows of August 14-20, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-09-13-issue-33-shows-of-august-14-20-2022/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-09-13-issue-33-shows-of-august-14-20-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Swan Song Early this year, we said goodbye to 205 Live before it was replaced with NXT: LVL UP. Come September, another WWE brand will go on hiatus and be replaced—in the form of renaming I guess you can say—with a newer NXT brand.
{:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
That show I’m talking about is NXT UK. This brand that took place in the United Kingdom, along with a few shows in the United States during the 2019 Royal Rumble and WrestleMania weekends, began in late 2018 which was over a year after the inaugural NXT United Kingdom Champion—then WWE United Kingdom Champion—was crowned.</description></item><item><title>Issue 32 Shows of August 7-13, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-09-12-issue-32-shows-of-august-7-13-2022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-09-12-issue-32-shows-of-august-7-13-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Double Dose Keeping this intro short and sweet, let’s start with a double dose of belated wXw recaps, shall we?
wXw Broken Rules XX For those of you that are new to wXw, Broken Rules is a special event that’s kind of like WWE’s Extreme Rules, where most of the matches are under hardcore wrestling rules or where there are no count outs or disqualifications whatsoever.
{:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}</description></item><item><title>Issue 31 Shows of July 30-August 6, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-08-10-issue-31-shows-of-july-30-august-6-2022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-08-10-issue-31-shows-of-july-30-august-6-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Use Sparingly I may think about using introductions on occasion in later issues. The reason why I say that is because I couldn’t think of a good introduction to begin this issue. I hope it’s okay for you readers to see me put aside intros and focus on the recaps, and then use the intros for special occasions such as holidays, anniversaries of events, and such.
Before I recap the shows I watched, I sure hope John Scott of Wrestling With Johners had a good birthday this week!</description></item><item><title>Issue 30 - Shows of July 23-29, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-08-06-issue-30-shows-of-july-23-29-2022/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-08-06-issue-30-shows-of-july-23-29-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
In case you’re wondering, it has nothing to do with the TV show of the same name my mother watched back when I was a little kid. I wanted to come up with a title that had “thirty” in it since this is my 30th issue of Pro-Darin. I’m so glad to be continuing writing this newsletter not just on my home computer, but also on Wrestling With Johners’ website and Facebook group page.</description></item><item><title>Issue 29 Shows of July 16-22, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-08-05-issue-29-shows-of-july-16-22-2022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-08-05-issue-29-shows-of-july-16-22-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Fourteen {:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Somewhere in either May or June of 1999, I started watching WWE—back when it was a “Federation”—more often. It was during the Attitude Era, and it was during one of the final few weeks of the Corporate Ministry that was led by Vince and Shane McMahon and the Undertaker and would target top names including “Stone Cold” Steve Austin and the Rock. At that time, Monday Night Raw—back when it was Raw Is War and was two hours long—was rated TV-14.</description></item><item><title>Issue 28 Shows of July 9-15, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-08-04-issue-28-shows-of-july-9-15-2022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-08-04-issue-28-shows-of-july-9-15-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Better Late Than Never Once again, I’m kicking things off with a belated recap. This week, it’s a look back at Day 2 of Progress Chapter 135: Super Strong Style 16. Off we go!
Progress Chapter 135: Super Strong Style 16—Day 2 {:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Day 2 of the 135th chapter of Progress took place at the Electric Ballroom in London, England in the United Kingdom; it served as part two of the three day long Super Strong Style 16 weekend.</description></item><item><title>Issue 27 Shows of July 2-8, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-08-03-issue-27-shows-of-july-2-8-2022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-08-03-issue-27-shows-of-july-2-8-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Stars and Stripes For those of you that live in the United States like I do, I sure hope you had a great Independence Day weekend as well as a good Fourth of July!
Progress Chapter 135: Super Strong Style 16—Day 1 As promised in the last two issues, I would recap two of the shows that came to Peacock while I was away; it starts off with day 1 of the 135th chapter of Progress.</description></item><item><title>Issue 26 Shows of June 26-July 2, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-07-21-issue-26-shows-of-june-26-july-2-2022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-07-21-issue-26-shows-of-june-26-july-2-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Coming Soon… Once again, I’m talking about my usual four shows and saving all three parts of Progress’ Super Strong Style tournament—as well as the 31st wXw We Love Wrestling episode—for later issues. Yes, I still have some catching up to do on those additions to Peacock (or WWE Network if you live outside the United States).
ICW Fight Club Our first stop is the United Kingdom as we enter the GPWA in Glasgow, Scotland for an episode of ICW Fight Club.</description></item><item><title>Issue 25 Shows of June 19-25, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-07-20-issue-25-shows-of-june-19-25-2022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-07-20-issue-25-shows-of-june-19-25-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Sorry I’m Late! Like I mentioned in the last newsletter, I took time away for a week to relax. In this newsletter, I’m talking about my usual four shows; bear with me since all four of those shows will have brief recaps. I will recap shows that made it to Peacock—Progress, wXw, etc.—in later issues.
ICW Fight Club First, we go to the United Kingdom, heading to the GPWA in Glasgow, Scotland for an episode of ICW Fight Club.</description></item><item><title>Issue 24 Shows of June 12-18, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-07-19-issue-24-shows-of-june-12-18-2022/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-07-19-issue-24-shows-of-june-12-18-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Happy Father’s Day To every father out there including my father, I’m wishing you a Happy Father’s Day!
ICW Fight Club Our first stop is the GPWA in Glasgow, Scotland in the United Kingdom for an episode of ICW Fight Club.
The buildup to ICW Shug’s Hoose Party 7 rolled on this week. This time, another match has been made for that event.
On the last episode of Fight Club, we saw Saqib Ali take on Theo Doros with DCT—as “Jackie Polo”—working as the special guest referee; the match of course ended in a disqualification after Doros coerced Chris Toal to put his hands on him.</description></item><item><title>Issue 23 Shows of June 5-11, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-07-18-issue-23-shows-of-june-5-11-2022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-07-18-issue-23-shows-of-june-5-11-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Courage/Gutsy One of these events that I watched this week will mention those two words, and I’m pretty sure—unless you missed what happened in the pro wrestling work this week—that you’ll find out which event I’m talking about…as well as which competitor. (P.S.: The definitions for those two words are also included.)
NXT In Your House Our first stop is the former Capital Wrestling Center at the WWE Performance Center in Orlando, Florida.</description></item><item><title>Issue 22 Shows of May 28-June 4, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-06-12-issue-22-shows-of-may-28-june-4-2022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-06-12-issue-22-shows-of-may-28-june-4-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Nothing Much To Say I don’t really have much of an intro this week, so why don’t we kick it off with a recap of the shows I watched this week. Okay with that?
Progress Chapter 134: No Mountain High Enough If that title doesn’t have Marvin Gaye &amp;amp; Tammi Terrell’s “Ain’t No Mountain High Enough” playing in your head, I don’t know what would. (It is a nice catchy tune from before my time by the way.</description></item><item><title>Issue 21 - Shows of May 21-27, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-05-29-issue-21-shows-of-may-21-27-2022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-05-29-issue-21-shows-of-may-21-27-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Thoughts and Prayers When I think of grade school, I think about good things such as hanging around with friends, getting good grades (including passing classes) as well as a good education, and some good highlights that were part of my time as a student including going to a senior prom with one of my classmates.
What I try not to think about when it comes to grade school is something horrifying and tragic such as mass shootings, especially one that took place this week at Robb Elementary School in Uvalde, Texas.</description></item><item><title>Issue 20 - Shows of May 14-20, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-05-26-issue-20-shows-of-may-14-20-2022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-05-26-issue-20-shows-of-may-14-20-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
20…Your Move Mr. Bond Yep! It’s my 20th issue of the Pro-Darin newsletter! I hope you readers enjoy it just like you have from issues 1 to 19.
To answer the question “How does it feel to make 20 issues?”, the answer is this…it really feels good. Regardless of how much I’ve gone through such as cramming four or more shows into one issue, making issues lengthy or not really lengthy, and so forth, it still feels good to make that many issues of Pro-Darin.</description></item><item><title>Issue 19 - Shows of May 7-13, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-05-16-issue-19-shows-of-may-7-13-2022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-05-16-issue-19-shows-of-may-7-13-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Mishap Alert There were some mistakes I made in the last issue. First, chapter 132 of Progress took place on April 17 and not April 18 like I said. Second, in the “Next time…” section of the newsletter, I meant to write “wXw Ambition 13” instead of “wXw Ambition 11” and also forgot to credit wXw for the Inner Circle logo that I used for the newsletter.</description></item><item><title>Issue 18 - Shows of April 30-May 6, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-05-08-issue-18-shows-of-april-30-may-6-2022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-05-08-issue-18-shows-of-april-30-may-6-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Happy Mother’s Day! For those of you readers that are mothers, Happy Mother’s Day! Happy Mother’s Day to my mom as well! Progress Chapter 132: By the Beard of Zeus! The chapter title comes from the movie “Anchorman”, said by Will Ferrell’s character Ron Burgundy.
This Progress chapter took place at the Dome in London, England on April 18, 2022 and served as night #1 of the Atlas Tournament weekend.</description></item><item><title>Issue 17 - Shows of April 23-29, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-05-02-issue-17-shows-of-april-23-29-2022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-05-02-issue-17-shows-of-april-23-29-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Many Years and Counting I guess you can say that it’s a good thing that I moved my lookback at Progress’ 10th anniversary show—from March of this year—to this week. The reason why I say that is because it coincided the week that we celebrated 20 years of Randy Orton competing in the WWE.
{:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
One week before Raw and SmackDown turned from regular shows to two separate brands in 2002, I—along with my mom and dad—saw Randy Orton compete in a dark match prior to the Sunday Night Heat and SmackDown tapings at what’s nowadays the Wells Fargo Center in Philadelphia; in his dark match, he took on the late Mr.</description></item><item><title>Issue 16 - Shows of April 16-22, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-04-27-issue-16-shows-of-april-16-22-2022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-04-27-issue-16-shows-of-april-16-22-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Now Available! My newsletter, from the first to this one and beyond, is now available on the Wrestling With Johners website at wrestlingwithjohners.com; once you’re at the website, click on “Articles”, and then you’ll see my newsletters located in that section!
I would like to thank John Scott of Wrestling With Johners for giving me this opportunity to send my show reviews to his website as well as his WWJ Facebook page.</description></item><item><title>Issue 14 - Shows of April 2-8, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-04-18-issue-14-shows-of-april-2-8-2022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-04-18-issue-14-shows-of-april-2-8-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
So Much WWE, So Little Time In other words, this issue of Pro-Darin is looking back at WrestleMania weekend, as well as episodes of NXT, NXT UK, and NXT: LVL UP that were shown days after that weekend. Let’s take a look at those events, shall we?
NXT Stand &amp;amp; Deliver For the first three events that I’m going to talk about, we are going to be in the home of 2022 WrestleMania weekend which is Dallas, Texas.</description></item><item><title>Issue 15 - Shows of April 9-15, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-04-18-issue-15-shows-of-april-9-15-2022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-04-18-issue-15-shows-of-april-9-15-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Back In the Saddle It’s more than just a reference to a song by Aerosmith. I’m calling the intro “Back In the Saddle” because now that WrestleMania weekend 2022 came and went, I’m back to doing—for now—my usual four shows which are ICW Fight Club, NXT, NXT UK, and NXT: LVL UP. Here’s a look back at those four events.
ICW Fight Club Our first stop is the United Kingdom where we return to the GPWA in Glasgow, Scotland for an episode of ICW Fight Club.</description></item><item><title>Issue 13 - Shows of March 26-April 1, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-04-17-issue-13-shows-of-march-26-april-1-2022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-04-17-issue-13-shows-of-march-26-april-1-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Endgame On March 25, 2022, Triple H—on ESPN—announced that ever since he had a cardiac scare in August of last year, he decided to retire from in-ring competition.
{:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Triple H will forever be on my Mount Rushmore of the WWE Attitude Era along with the Rock, “Stone Cold” Steve Austin and the Undertaker. I remember seeing him not only as a singles competitor winning gold on Raw (even during the “Raw Is War” era) and SmackDown premium live events (or “pay-per-view” events as I still call them) such as WrestleMania as well as fighting as the “Cerebral Assassin” and “The Game” in the WWE, but also during his time with well-known teams D-Generation X, the Kliq, and Evolution.</description></item><item><title>Issue 12 - Shows of March 19-25, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-04-16-issue-12-shows-of-march-19-25-2022/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-04-16-issue-12-shows-of-march-19-25-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
I Apologize… Unfortunately in this newsletter, I did not watch wXw We Love Wrestling 27. The reason why I didn’t is because the wXw event did not make it to Peacock (where I normally watch those shows except for NXT which is on USA Network) as it was scheduled; it is however scheduled to appear on Peacock next week.
I will however recap my four usual shows—ICW Fight Club, NXT, NXT UK, and NXT: LVL UP—this week.</description></item><item><title>Issue 11 - Shows of March 12-18, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-04-15-issue-11-shows-of-march-12-18-2022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-04-15-issue-11-shows-of-march-12-18-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
RIP Scott Hall As I mentioned in the first newsletter, I started watching WWE in the late 1990s; at that time, WWE was still a “Federation” before replacing “Federation” with “Entertainment” (and also “F” with “E”), the Attitude Era was still going on, we had the “Corporation Ministry” running amok a couple months before WWE SmackDown was born…just to name a few. Plus, at that time, the Monday Night Wars was occurring between WWE and WCW…WWE with Raw Is War (now known simply as “Raw” of course), and WCW with Monday Nitro.</description></item><item><title>Issue 10 - Shows of March 5-11, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-04-14-issue-10-shows-of-march-5-11-2022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-04-14-issue-10-shows-of-march-5-11-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Bonus Alert! First of all, welcome to the tenth issue of the Pro-Darin pro wrestling fan newsletter!
Second, remember in the very first newsletter when I introduced myself and explained what shows I would be recapping? At the end of one of the paragraphs in my self-introduction, I said—in parentheses—that I would sneak in a show from a different company and talk about it.
The bonus event that I have selected is Impact Wrestling: Sacrifice.</description></item><item><title>Issue 9 - Shows of February 26-March 4, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-04-13-issue-9-shows-of-february-26-march-4-2022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-04-13-issue-9-shows-of-february-26-march-4-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Yes, Your Honor… {:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Ring of Honor is finally taken care of during the hiatus that is expected to conclude in April of this year. This past Wednesday night on an episode of AEW Dynamite, it was announced by AEW CEO Tony Khan that he agreed to buy Ring of Honor, including the library that dates back to 2002 which was the year that ROH was born.</description></item><item><title>Issue 8 - Shows of February 19-25, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-04-12-issue-8-shows-of-february-19-25-2022/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-04-12-issue-8-shows-of-february-19-25-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Cue “Roads” by Portishead WWE is now on a road to WrestleMania after going through Elimination Chamber (that took place outside the United States for the first time ever), ICW was on a road to Square Go! after going through empty arena episodes of Fight Club (the Peacock broadcast will be shown on March 5 by the way, hence saying “was” instead of “is”), and Progress is on a road to the 15th Anniversary show.</description></item><item><title>Issue 7 - Shows of February 12-18, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-04-11-issue-7-shows-of-february-12-18-2022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-04-11-issue-7-shows-of-february-12-18-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
That Was Unexpected… Those three words were what I thought after seeing an announcement this past Tuesday, less than an hour before watching this week’s episode of NXT after seeing an announcement that 205 Live was being replaced with a new NXT show entitled “NXT: LVL UP” (pronounced NXT Level Up of course). I also thought to myself “Saw that coming” ever since 205 Live turned from a cruiserweight show to what looked like NXT’s rendition of WWE Main Event or Sunday Night Heat.</description></item><item><title>Issue 5 - Shows of January 29-February 4, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-03-27-issue-5-shows-of-january-29-february-4-2022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-03-27-issue-5-shows-of-january-29-february-4-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
First of all… I would like to say thank you to all of my family and friends that not only congratulated me or wished me good luck on this newsletter, but—during what was also Royal Rumble weekend—wishing me a happy birthday. I really appreciate it.
Not only that, I would also like to thank author and host John Scott of Wrestling With Johners for allowing me to use the Wrestling With Johners Facebook group to have me post this newsletter.</description></item><item><title>Issue 6 - Shows of February 5-11, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-03-27-issue-6-shows-of-february-5-11-2022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-03-27-issue-6-shows-of-february-5-11-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Happy Together Not only am I quoting a song by the Turtles, but I am also congratulating a new couple.
![Keith Lee Mia Yim](/assets/posts/2022-03-27/Keith Lee 6.PNG){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
That couple I’m talking about is Keith Lee and Mia Yim, two wrestlers best known for their time on NXT (and appearances in other WWE shows such as Raw) as well as other companies…Keith Lee—nowadays on AEW after seeing him debut on AEW Dynamite this past Wednesday—also best known in Ring of Honor for being together with Shane Taylor as PBK or “Pretty Boy Killers” before he headed to other companies such as Evolve and PWG (Pro Wrestling Guerrilla), and Mia Yim also known for her time in Combat Zone Wrestling, Shine Wrestling, Shimmer Women Athletes, and—back when she competed as “Jade”—Impact Wrestling.</description></item><item><title>Issue 3 - Shows of January 15-21, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-03-26-issue-3-shows-of-january-15-21-2022/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-03-26-issue-3-shows-of-january-15-21-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Moving on… ![samantha irvin](/assets/posts/2022-03-26/samantha irvin.jpeg){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Good luck wishes go out to Samantha Irvin who is now the official ring announcer of SmackDown! She was best known for her time as the ring announcer, as well as occasional backstage interviewer, on both NXT and 205 Live. I’m hoping that she does well on SmackDown now that Mike Rome is focusing on just Raw after taking over for the released Greg Hamilton.</description></item><item><title>Issue 4 - Shows of January 22-28, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-03-26-issue-4-shows-of-january-22-28-2022/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-03-26-issue-4-shows-of-january-22-28-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
What a coincidence! I don’t really have much to say for the intro in this newsletter, except that it’s a coincidence that I’m doing—like in the last one—four shows in the fourth newsletter. Okay, I’m done with confusing readers, numerology and corny jokes (or “dad jokes” as we nowadays call them)…
let’s get to the newsletter, shall we?
ICW Fight Club The episode took place inside an empty Glasgow Pro Wrestling Asylum; there was no fans because of, sadly, a COVID outbreak that occurred in Scotland.</description></item><item><title>Issue 2 - Shows of January 8-14, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-03-24-issue-2shows-of-january-8-14-2022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-03-24-issue-2shows-of-january-8-14-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Round 2…fight! Hello, once again! Yes, this is me—Darin—again, and this is the second issue of my Pro-Darin newsletter.
I’m definitely excited to tell you what went on in the European indies as well as the three WWE shows of my choosing, but this time, it’s going to be much different than the first newsletter.
I realized how lengthy my first newsletter was after posting it not too long ago; in the first newsletter, I went through every detail of each episode in chronological order, from promos and vignettes to interviews and to results.</description></item><item><title>Issue 1 - Shows of January 1-7, 2022</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-03-23-issue-1-shows-of-january-1-7-2022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/pro-darin/2022-03-23-issue-1-shows-of-january-1-7-2022/</guid><description>![pro darin](/assets/posts/2022-03-23/pro darin.png){:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
Introduction to the newsletter Hello, everybody! My name is Darin Adamczyk, going by the name “Pro-Darin” in this newsletter. For those of you that have seen me in person, on social media, etc., I like to talk about many things such as my family, music, Philadelphia history that I like to learn about (especially what occurred during my lifetime in the city or before I was born), auto racing including NASCAR, the outdoors (such as fishing), and anything else I like to mention like a video of commercials from before my time (or during my time as a kid) on YouTube.</description></item><item><title>British Wrestling Isn’t Dead!</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/michael-jolly/2021-03-03-british-wrestling-isnt-dead/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/michael-jolly/2021-03-03-british-wrestling-isnt-dead/</guid><description>“British Wrestling Isn’t Dead!” {:class=&amp;ldquo;restrict-width&amp;rdquo;}
So as of writing this we are now coming up to one year since the world was hit by something we’ve never dealt with before and it hit us all hard.
Businesses and people from all walks of life were affected no more so than the British wrestling scene, where we saw the closure of various companies who were no longer able to carry on, as they didn’t get the financial help from the government that was needed.</description></item><item><title>Post Title</title><link>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/yyyy-mm-dd-template/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wrestlingwithjohners.com/podcasts/yyyy-mm-dd-template/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>